Hi, it's Samantha. Sorry. Can you hear me? I just was saying I have this this book I had a I
Just noticed you're always first in my chat, so I wanted to put you first in the book, so you're at the top
Okay, and those people crossed out with you at the very top, and you will not be crossed out
Okay
Yeah
Time to time to clean house a little bit today. I've never known there's one here. Where's everybody?
Hi guys
Gonna have a fun day. We're in a fun day
How are you today?
I had a nice shower.
I cleaned them pretty well.
My best.
Thank you, Samantha.
You're awesome.
Here we go.
Thank you so much, Samantha.
Yeah, come on in, guys.
I'm in good mood today.
Thank you.
Here, I'll get it.
Be like life.
Nightbot, I need two more.
OK.
Thank you so much.
Hey, guys.
So I got some great sleep.
Hi, Samantha. I love you
Yeah, I have some we're having a fun day
Oh
Yes
I'll hold off the link up, but I will
How are you guys?
Hey, yeah, I mean
That's some interesting stuff on some channels. Is it hot? No, it's kind of just breezy. Hi, babe
It's nice day, it's just a little breeze. It's not too hot
It shows it's just a journey. Hi guys
Hi, babe, how do you do it? Yeah
Here
Excuse me
Babe
My baby my babe
my baby babe
Yeah, that's decent. Hey, babe. Oh
They're tricks. Do you want to say hi to the chatty chat?
No, you don't
Oh, baby. I don't see any other cat right now. Yeah, I feel a lot better.
Oh, this is good to get some like rest and a shower. Hi. Hi.
everybody about but I need more people to come in but nobody's nobody like be
alone because you might you'll notice something in the chat maybe babe
I'm going to draw some pictures today of people, too.
I'm going to draw some art.
Maybe there's one with the picture.
Anyone want the picture, though?
I did.
The weather's very comfortable.
How are you guys?
Good to see you.
a babe. Maybe we'll start with like a song. These are always good to clear the kind of
negative vibration. I know we've been having a lot of crazy stuff going on in the chat and the
But I do have a do you have a plan? Okay, let's see
Yeah, I just heard okay, so I'm 96
So I'm 96
Okay, it says sing
to the Lord a new song sing to the Lord all the earth sing to the Lord
Praise his name will claim his salvation day after day
Declare's glory among the nations is marvelous deeds among all peoples
For great is the Lord and most worthy of praise
He is to be feared above all gods for the gods of the nations are idols
but the Lord be at the heavens, splendor and majesty are before him, strength and glory
are in his sanctuary. Ascribe to the Lord all you families of nations, ascribe to the Lord
glory and strength, ascribe to the Lord, glory do his name. Bring an offering and come into
his courts. Worship the Lord in the splendor of his holiness, tremble before him, all the earth.
the world is firmly established.
It cannot be moved.
He will judge the peoples with equity.
Let the heavens rejoice, let the earth be glad.
Let the sea resound and all that is in it.
Let the fields be jubilant and everything in them.
Let all the trees in the forest sing for joy.
Let all creation rejoice before the Lord before he comes.
He comes to judge the earth.
He will judge the world in righteousness
and the people in his faithfulness.
Pretty nice.
I like that, I like the idea of equity.
Well, let's see, let's see what, well, I don't know.
People run when I play,
well, sometimes when people disappear,
when I read a song, I mean, they're kind of short and sweet
and kind of cool, but if people like run from it,
I think, okay, well, that's probably good they did.
Okay.
Oh, 77.
hmm
song 77 for the for the director of music for
Jeduthan of ASAP a song I
Cried out to God for help. I cried out to God to hear me when I was in this stress
I sought the Lord all night. I stretched out among untiring hands and would not be comforted
I remembered you God and I groaned
I meditated and my spirit grew faint.
You kept my eyes from closing.
I was too troubled to speak.
I thought about the former days, the years of long ago.
I remembered my songs in the night.
My heart meditated and my spirit asked.
Will the Lord reject forever?
Will He never show His favor again?
Has His unfailing love vanished forever?
Has His promise failed for all time?
Has God forgotten to be merciful?
Has he an anger withheld his compassion?
Then I thought, to this I will appeal.
The years when the Most High stretched out his right hand,
I will remember the deeds of the Lord.
Yes, I will remember your miracles of long ago.
I will consider all your works and meditate on all your mighty deeds.
Your ways, God, are holy.
What God is as great as our God.
You are the God who performs miracles, you display your power among your peoples, with
a mighty arm you redeemed your people, the descendants of Jacob and Joseph.
The water saw you, God, the water saw you and writhed, the very depths were convulsed,
the clouds poured down water, the heavens resounded with thunder, your arrows flashed
back and forth, your thunder was heard in the whirlwind, your lightning lit up the world,
Your path led through the sea your way to the mighty waters through your footprints, but your footprints were not seen
Where's everybody? Hi guys
Be beautiful
I'll see one more. Can everyone say hi in the chat. I don't know if it was quiet
It's Sunday Sunday, they use it for the soil, okay, Psalm 33
Okay
Sing joyfully to the Lord, you righteous.
It is a fitting for the upright to praise him.
Praise the Lord with the harp. Make music
to him on the ten-stringed lyre. Hey, Easy!
Sing him a new song. Play skillfully and shout for joy.
For the word of the Lord is right and true. He is faithful in all he does.
The Lord loves righteousness and justice. The earth is full of his unbailing love.
By the word of the Lord, the heavens were made.
There are starry hosts by the breath of the mouth. He gathers the waters of the sea into jars
He puts the deep into storehouses
Let all the earth fear the Lord let all the people of the world revere him for he spoke and it came to him
He commanded and it stood firm
Lord foils the plans of the nations. He forced the purpose of the peoples
But the plan of the Lord stands for him forever, the purposes of his heart through all generations,
the lessons of the nation, whose God is the Lord, the people he chose were the inheritance.
From heaven the Lord looks down and sees all mankind when it's willing places
He watches all who live on earth he who forms the hearts of all who considers everything they do
No king is saved by the size of his army. No warrior escapes by his great strength
A horse is a vain hope for deliverance despite all its great strength. I cannot they cannot save
But the eyes of the Lord are on those who fear him on those whose hope is is in his unfailing love to deliver them
from death and keep them alive and famine. We wait in hope for the Lord. He is our help and our
shields. In him our hearts rejoice. For we trust in his holy name. May your unbending love be with
us Lord, even as we put our hope in you. Blessings, blessings, blessings. Yeah, I love you. Blessings
to all, right? It's just like, my, my, it sounds cheap, bro. I'm trying to charge these. Let me see.
They're I mean, they're not cheap. They're like there's not like great. There's both like 40 bucks. I
Had like a pair that was like 15 bucks and they were they were cheap
These are decent, I'm sorry, is it better?
Sorry, my my sense. I'm trying to send better blessings everybody. Yeah
Other cool stuff to share with you too, but I
Want to talk it's with 15 people here. Okay, so when make a Q&A first of all you might notice
Did you switch to audio and test?
Oh, hold on.
Sounds bad?
Did you hear me at all?
I'm sorry.
Let me test it.
Testing.
I think it should work, okay.
Hi, hi, hi, hi, hey man.
Yeah, I just want to let everybody know.
I thought about it a lot, it's causing all the modding stuff, all the talk about modding
and mods and then some mods are being targeted and I just really, basically for all your
guys' safety, I unmodded everybody, everybody off.
I won't have mods, so no one will have to blame a mod.
It'll be my responsibility to moderate the chat.
I'll do that, okay?
I'll moderate the chat myself.
So, if you like being a mod, you know,
just this chat, there actually will be one mod,
it's Nightbot, but yeah.
I'll moderate the chat myself,
and hopefully it'll calm down some of this, like,
Wrench wrench talk everyone screaming out wrenches in here
Cause way too much trouble and I have to be to be fair. I have to do it for everybody, okay?
But
Thank you guys so much who were mods and for you for a
Produce such a great job, and I know it was like hard. I know it was hard, but and I don't say it's it's so hard
of a job that I don't want you guys to
I know and it's in you're doing it for free, right? Yeah, so it'll be easier for me to
You know if anybody gets blocked or timed out that it's just everyone can just blame me, you know
I'll just I'll just
Because it's a I think either everyone's moderate or no one's modded. It's the only way it will work
I thought about
It's just too many
all to count
Cool guys. I love you
Yeah, and I'm sorry, and I know also it's been like I've been thinking a lot about
how the show's been going and like what's been happening and
You know
I'm gonna stop going to other chats
So it's like, I can't remember the raids I used to do.
I can't even do raids anymore.
When I did the raids, people started going in
and like throwing the people.
I can't even like really promote other people
because I don't want to bring attention,
negative attention because I do have so many,
so many, I would talk to them.
I would call her, call into her show.
I mean, she got, you know, she has a burner phone.
So I would call her because I have no,
I never had a problem with her.
It was a let's see what they cry about now. Yeah
Yeah, there's gonna be something or the other but at least it will just take some heat off of everybody because
It was like I never saw like the mods and I remember I got I kind of got attacked when I was in Benny's chat
And he would get it like attacks you and
Lot like people would just say horrible things about the mods and and then there are rogue mods. It's kind of a mess
so
I was always a good mod, so I'll use my professional modding skills that I learned and I'll try to moderate to chat.
So that way, also, if there's something that shouldn't be posted, it'll be through my responsibility to take it off.
And so I wouldn't want to say, oh, you know, mod was supposed to take that off if I could ever get an issue, you know.
I just like, I want to be responsible for everything, okay?
But you guys, you can still do the nightbot commands
if you ever want to help me.
That would help me greatly also.
You know, I've got the membership
and I'll put your name in green like Samantha,
give you a cool member icon.
So you'll get longer readings, access to exclusive content.
You have more stuff planned in emojis.
Hey Jesus, thanks for all this TT
Me okay, I'll be honest
I stopped joining your panel because everyone was telling you what to do and you were trying to please I couldn't even get a word
I know I'm sorry like to defend yourself. Yeah, and I thought about it like I feel really bad like
If I have had people on the panel that I like because you know
I was just used to people just biting on the panel and saying outrageous things
But when people were saying outrageous things to me the other day like you know, Vita and other people
I
Really it hurts and Alex it hurts like what they say like and so I was like, oh that's what that it's like
It's just like hit me as like that's how everyone's feels and that's why people are getting so upset and like leaving
Because people are talking to them like that and it's just like
Because sometimes you don't understand, you don't feel like how they feel like you're like, oh you think they think it's funny too
Or they maybe they laugh along with it when you really feel it
Even you might laugh along with the stuff you see about yourself, but when you see it
You might laugh, but you'll cry later. It's because it's like it's uh, you know, it is hurtful
It sounds we smile and laugh to like mask our emotions. You know and
So yeah, so I'm gonna do a better job of like, you know, I'm not gonna let people talk to me like, you know
Especially since I have so many people that have been here for months and like a long time. I'm not gonna let people bully anybody
I'm not gonna let
People call it calling it. I'm just gonna step in a lot faster. I'm gonna get my finger on it
I'm not gonna like even like I'm not looking for drama. I'm not interested in like oh
I know I know it's like fun shows sometimes and it gets crazy and exciting but it's like
It's I think it's hurting people as you know people are taking
YouTube stuff like really really
Seriously and getting really upset. I want to make sure I contribute to the better
Man of you few bright
Yeah
Yeah, I know it and this is like you know, this is my TV's big adventure because it's like it's like TV's big adventure because
You know, I just got a bike
Kind of like a big goofy adult, you know, it's like a child's brain like a kiwi and
Then some something happens where there's some kind of like adventure
I have to go on to like save my a show or save my they save the bike
You know glad my bike thing is still like I can just work on saving the show, right?
Don't you start with Paul Rubens?
well
Know I was the 80s baby. I actually had one of the first TV her man like I'm talking dolls
I love TV's playhouse. I love TV's big adventure. I'm one of the best movies ever made probably
Thank you. I've only given this love thought I should be your only mom you have oh Doug
Okay, I'll consider though. I have I have one more already Doug. It's nightbot and nightbot. He passes interview
He didn't hug back. He's not racist. Okay, but
Yeah, you got that membership. Hey, Doug, you got that membership. So, you know, you're good with that. Okay. You're good at green Doug. Okay
You know, he ended up being acquitted. Yeah, but yeah, it's like, but you know, that's the thing with these
even
It wasn't really he was acquitted. Yeah, but then it's like it's like because he was on a kid's TV show
It's like the reputation his reputation, right?
And then it's like so we can't and because he had originally created Pee Wee as an adult character, right?
It was he was at comedy clubs like adult club comedy clubs
And it was kind of like like a kid show for adults and then but they're like hey, let's adapt it to like make an actual kids show
So he could try and it'd be a kid's host, right?
They tried to point paint him like that again. Yeah, that's what I
Said this world is you know six so much on yeah later on
Yeah, I heard even
Do some of that
but
You know he kind of did revive his film career. He had some friends in Hollywood
You know, he was a pretty brilliant actor and
You know, I never heard of him hurt harming anybody or anything like that, but
Yeah, so I
Feel like I'm on a I'm on an adventure and it could you know it could end up being a maiden to a movie someday
He was he ruined for his choices. Yeah
But you know, he did have you get some roles in movies. Yeah, they're not great, but
You can act really hard just don't jerk off in other places. Of course not
I'm barely like to jerk off at home. Hey summer
I know that movie theater was basically meant for that, but you know, yeah, I mean
You open a bit you have a business license for porno theater. Oh, I'm sorry summer summer
I unmodded everybody just so because my mods are getting a lot of heat nothing personal
You did a great job my mother getting too much heat and you know from other people people complaining and things aren't fair
Well, I just have to mod it myself with with nightbot maybe
Helping but I love you summer. You're the best. Thank you so much for always like being a great mod
But yeah, I had to make it fair. So I'll I'll just mod it myself. I love you summer. So you're not set. I
Don't want I don't want my mods to eat because I remember I remember that
Benny's mods got a got heat and so I know I
Don't want
Cause anybody not also not going to anybody else's chats anymore. Okay. Thank you summer. Yeah, I love you
Matt another massive I really don't think that there's like many people banned and the people that are I think they
pretty much irritated me I
Never worry about getting to eat
Just just so you know, I always got spoke for that heat
I'm I say am I joking panels? I would know well, I don't think you know am I trying a panel if it's like, you know friend
They invite me
No, I'm not every there's hardly anybody banned before I think I banned everybody, right?
Heat not eat. Oh, yeah, I read the heat. I'm so sorry
Yeah
I always got that smoke for the heat.
Christine got me the other day when she was in her, oh.
Yeah, it's like because, you know,
like I won't say the guy's name if he was like,
he was just like, oh, I don't have a ranch
and I can't post and then your monster, your monster,
letting people say bad things about me.
And I was like, well, I was like, I,
They were I forgot I don't know I didn't see it in the chat. He's like, oh
Well, you should have seen it. So, uh, okay, I'll pay attention to my chat. I'll do all the responsible for all the
Moderation
So if anybody complained, you can just blame it on me just an unfortunate need to be a taker first station. Uh, hold on
Yeah, did you see
Yeah guys, we're really it guys really gonna be taking a hard stance against the slander doctors
and the racial
Racial stuff. I mean, I mean, I'm gonna be really more tough on the panel also just people that are know that world
Respect the host and other panelists. I'm gonna really pay attention to that because it's like
There's so much disrespect to the panelists and to me and it's like, you know, I'm sorry. I didn't step in more
if people were rude to the
Root to the panelists anybody's on the panel or you know, you know, I love you guys
And I know a lot of people were very upset with some subset
And I just kind of sat there sometimes and do anything or it wasn't there
So I'll make sure I'll always be here
And I'll I'll protect I'll protect you guys. I'll protect you know, I'll make this a safe space
Hot sauce for anyone that wants to cook
Yeah, I like hot sauce
Hey, hey Lenore
Well, let's say, you know, everybody, thank you, I'm sorry, I'm going to, you know,
But it's funny think that it's weird that Kate ridicules me for drinking and streaming
But she's been drinking on since last night. I know well, it's like sometimes people like to project
Their own stuff on other people or it's like somebody was like, oh that person is drinks more than me
And so they're you know, they're I'm better than them or something, right?
Yeah, let meow
Meanwhile, she has it's okay
Yeah, I related to uh, I noticed people would take it out on your panel and not be spice
Spicy on their panel
Yeah, I mean, yeah, it would just be it. They were just like because I'm just a pushover and I was like, no
I'm kind of I wasn't new and
Kind of you know about it. I was like, hey, it's fine. Oh the numbers numbers, you know, it's because there's because they're controversy
It's fun having numbers, but it's like
No, it's like it's just
Brought some like weird weird energy and I really didn't like it the other day when just like the whole chat was like these weird people like
Causing all this problem
There's one thing I have I hate most and that's bad
Moms on the internet who value giving it people over online. Yeah. Well, I say I don't want to judge anybody on their mothering skills
You know, it's like I'm sure like a lot of
Most of them are probably very loving mothers and good moms and everything. I we don't know exactly
I don't have to judge I
Was noticing the chat alluring nature start. Oh, yeah
Let's see
Lorraine nature
Loving moms are mistaken for okay
Well, yeah, well, it's like, you know, sometimes
Person doesn't like it, but in the someone doesn't like the woman and the woman has a kid and then
The woman doesn't another woman doesn't like her. She'll say any like little thing. Oh, you know
Oh, she's not even the right size bottle or the I don't know. She just the strollers not right
I don't think she can just judge about everything and then just have it like a smugness like oh, I'm better, right?
They see Kate cry when she put her face on panel
But yeah, I remember that and then I went over she's like chatting with Tony
Like she's like just like having a kiki cock-a-law with him on my my picture. There's like crashing me
Hey, babe
Okay, so the worst part is, okay, okay.
Well, Charlie, I don't know, let's not really talk.
I don't want to be talking about people.
Kate wants to come on the panel
and she sees somebody in the chat,
comments something and she can choose to address it or not,
but I don't, we shouldn't talk about it when she's not here.
Okay.
I prefer to be coughs and passing judgment on the chat won't do anything to that.
Exactly.
So how about take care of things legal way and then too, like there's all these people
that are being accused.
There's no paper.
There's no like paperwork or any charges that were filed and so and there's so many accusations
I want to lick you from your head to your toe.
Oh, D, look.
Oh, you said it just gone, OK.
The worst part, yeah, so.
Hello.
Yeah.
He's prepared.
Sub CD
Yeah, and so that's you know, it's the internet. I
Remember remember they were saying like there's people were trying to say oh and I want to say her name
But they're saying that there's a streamer
We know she was on my show before and people were saying oh she ate a dog
And she got on bass health and ate a dog and they produced a police report
And as I looked at the police report, I was like, well, it was like, you know, weird font.
It was like a cursive kind of font that wouldn't be on a police report usually.
And then it's like, it's such a, and it was like the wrong dates and everything. I don't know. Yeah.
That's what, no, that's what people were trying to say in the chat and stuff. And it's like, of course, it wasn't true.
I don't know if her dog had just passed away or something, but they, but someone came and produced a police report that
Gave us grew something where police came and they saw her like a zombie like you know
eating with some bath cells eating eating her dog or something and
Say Taco Bell high-screen full now
Yeah, she might you might
It's like, you know, it's pretty gruesome pretty like, you know horrible to think of
Somebody doing that to die. What's up, nobody? I just want yeah, I've ever been everybody is the modded right now
I just have nightbot as a mod
Just so you get some heat off of you guys and
The mods I know there were there were people just bitching at the mods people like take my wrench take my wrench some people you know
And then I don't want them to target, you know,
people to target people and stuff.
So, A has me on a lot of others blocks.
Oh, you do this, Kyle?
Yeah, I think so.
I think I just have a nightbot,
and then I can mod if they need B,
and then so it'll be my responsibility, so.
It'll be better that I pay more attention.
You could see everyone, but haters talking, wild shit now.
Yeah, I mean they're
They're not here
I did like say a few prayers like I said a couple I think a couple when I started the show and a couple before the show and
Clearing out the energy right
Yeah, you have your pencil ninja you're fine
The Nolan's cat, let's see where's the cat in here. I've got a jar of it
Where is it?
Got it
I told you I will not cast
Doctrine on anyone coming to my house pulling up. Yeah. No, don't talk up to the loves to me
No, talk of folks no threading you mean no
They say oh fuck you be and you know, it's just we're not gonna do it here anymore. It's gonna be a
This is really, I want to make it a safe space for people.
I think the mod step is a good step.
What's up, J-Dog?
Hey, Rado.
Rado, everyone's unmodded.
I just, it's better to have no mods.
The mods are getting too much heat.
They're being harassed.
The people are screaming about,
oh, this isn't fair.
The mods are timing me out.
I just want to take over the modding.
And me and Nightbot are gonna handle it.
but we love you, you're the best, thank you everybody who was a mod, I know it was like
a thankless, tough job, it's not probably an easy chat to mod, so mod's always harassing
you, yeah, so now no one will feel harassed by a mod, and then I had to have some people
Mod is to protect them from other mods, and I don't I really don't need I don't want my mods like divided like that
I need I need that's a nightbot, and I will
The nightbot's pretty cute
You know it's how I've been saying nice things to people that I don't get along with I just do I do that in each other's chest
Oh, thank you
Thank you
Long time
You never have a cat of yours freak out because of the toothpaste you use or the minty gum
You're chewing a pair in the cat that is related to the mint family. Oh, probably is I think it is
Okay, let's see. I'm sorry if I missed some comments. You like Rudy. I love Rudy too
Okay
Charlie Scott. Oh, come on
Sev no thanks. Okay. Watch them cry as soon as someone gets mad
Yeah
Yeah, well, it's like I
Just take it away. Well, like 75% of what everyone's complaining about to me
So it should make it easier. Why why why is that keep big?
Big cry, baby
Oh, yeah, they're why am I psyche? It's gonna aid the danger. Oh, come on
Yeah guys, you know, I guess as long as you're joking around, you know, I don't want you kind of anything serious
Oh guys, hey, you guys I I think I'd be scared to meet up with some of you guys, you know, I don't know
We don't want to make anybody mad. I think everyone's armed in my my chat
Okay, let's see
Well, you know what?
Think what easy told me it was self defense, you know, that's legitimate
You know, he's threatening people oh
My gosh, well guys if I miss something I'm the mod if I do miss if you're like oh that person's comment
You should delete that comment. Please. Let me know if I miss it cuz I'm
Let's see who is who's threatening home scum
It's kind of not threatening.
If Seb blocks you because he thinks you're a troll,
therefore, he is 80% of people on chats blocked.
Acts, still true.
Hey, Sebastian.
Ooh, Doug.
Well, some of these stories, I don't believe
Yeah, oh now it's been but now you guys can be me now you guys can get like you help me sleep the comic
Weird that he had been himself, but he was an insurable. Okay. I don't I don't know the story
Where's weird, okay, so
Yeah, oh
There's no link
Yeah, I just wanted to get a bit of this to make sure you guys know again
I'll I'll be modding the chat myself from now and you guys can just sit back relax enjoy show now don't worry about
Stuff in the chat or if there's anything bad you can just and I don't see it. You can just tell me
Okay, so your feet okay, so
Okay
Oh, yeah, I want to draw some pictures. Okay, I'll put a panel. I put the panel if I think we did so I'll draw
I'll draw some pictures if you want your portrait drawn. I'll draw quick for sure of you
You know, not the best or just if you're better than Canada dry
Maybe not
Okay
looks good happens but yeah guys watch see if I do a good job so if it happens I'll have to be on
on an alert today like if people start bullying anybody if people any if it gets
out of hand I'm gonna be better at controlling the chat
Should I draw let me see
Yeah, yeah, I was I was I didn't get bullied terribly just because I was kind of like I had a smart mouth and
But you know, I mean I went to a small school too. It's not that we have to do it easy and chat on panel soon
It's my life. It's my life. Yeah
Thank you. We probably have to have you on a guest of humble panel. Just need a little bit of courage. Okay
Well, I got courage
Happy Tuesday, I mean, you know, you know when
Or you can tell me his channel name or put in the back chat
No, is it what do you think guys that's when I an interview I should ever do I
Don't know I don't want I don't because there are some like there's just in people that are hostile to me
That's what I don't want to ambush interview. I don't want
You know if I have to brave I don't why don't you brave it should be like oh not fun. He's a cool guy
He's a good interview, but if you brave what?
Like grow me a new asshole, so here's my DJ Alexa picture
He's a DJ Alexa
That's her I
Had to fix it may I made her a little bit busy me, but I kind of try to put a cape around her in a slim waist
But I don't know if it looks right
Hello
Doesn't look like a spinning image
That a good one that was good, okay
And so anybody else I might be able to just put your avatar on the screen, but I'd like to
Time out said please. Oh, no
Yeah, if I saw him say something wrong, I would but he's just thinking this ask you to to hang out with them
He's called you a chicken. Oh my god
Yeah
Hmm I miss you can do that. I never have to spend years of my life in a concrete box
Here we go CD at first to cry about it
Are you still the same wannabe Kings? Are you upset by the same mistakes?
Let's stop crying. Can't you take it?
So there's a bully from can't your Canada dry said
Canada dries really weird. He came on the show. He's like he was like making weird faces with the camera
I mean, you know hit a girl over and then he just showed that he had a girl over any hung up
Okay
Good for you. So Canada Drive
Well, I'm gonna let all this a lot of people in the chat, you know
As long as they are following the rules
Everyone can be I you know, I'm not gonna mess with bank is the people that ban a pretty much her doctors are like really obvious haters
Forgot that. Oh, yeah, sas. He was there last night. Yeah, I
Pray to the law got caught carlin
See the chicken from Alabama
There's this lady I'm 98 fiance and she was like she was kind of a crazy lady. I
It's really funny. But so she was with the guy from Nigeria and he was like blind, right?
And she was so she's a chicken farmer from Texas. I think I think from Texas and so she flies out to him, but she's insane
and
Yeah, he's he wrote like a note or something. He said like on Instagram or something
He's like, oh, well, she came over and then she said that she was gonna sacrifice pieces on vampire
Werewolf or I have to find the thing. Her name was it was a name was was her name rain. Let me see
The name was rain, hold on
Let's see that
Yeah, I just said this is her
So big
Well, there we go, okay, that's her that's rain, okay, but there's a text message or some message you wrote
Okay, it says, it says, okay, there's a lot of text messages from.
Um, well, here's one, I don't think I've seen this page.
As they thought she was illusion, she also shared how when she attended church,
her pastor sent her out of his office and recommended she see a psychiatrist
after she has spoken of alien conspiracies and the Illuminati.
That I was the reason she stopped attending church
She believes human society was against her and that she had no friends having been through my own traumatic experiences
This is the guy that she married you the blind guy from Africa where I helped back on on my feet by loving supportive family and friends
I felt deeply for rain from that point on I was always there for her offering encouragement and shearing her up with a numerous phone calls
after a few weeks of constant communication
rain and appreciation of the joy and excitement I brought to her life,
confessed her love for me, and I responded positively.
Okay, but that's not the one. So that was kind of the pastor,
but let me get the important message, and let me see if this is the one. Come on.
It's hilarious. That's the guy's name, let me see.
Well, I don't know if we'll find it
But yeah, she's she he said that he thought you're gonna sacrifice some system like vampire cultures
And it says she said as he asked if I was ready to be sacrificed
And if I was prepared to be in the same room with her when vampires and cannibals would gather for their feasts
Isn't that kind of funny?
Hey guys
Yes, and the nightbot's still working you guys you guys can still
Do the nightbot commands that you if you want to free terribiting. Yeah, sure
Take it would like one. Okay
We're good shirt collection. Thank you. Thank you guys
Not Sebastian Sebastian not no selling liposuction in my chat. Thank you. I like chicken breast for supper
Because I like fried chicken butter. I think
Instead of freak he likes marriage females 49 40% off you oh
Yeah, free terrarium rain or rain and her name is r a y n e
Because they're not the same people rain is white. Yeah. Yeah, I didn't think that was rain. I said she's a 90-day fiance
She's like she's that that's what the guys her fiance wrote about her
So in any way night by the awesome. Yeah
Yeah
Used to come to beat it, but keep missing an action. Don't keep them low. Oh, you are she is that's cool
He's scared of a Latina
Through her. Yeah, yeah
Am I I'm not scared. I don't know. She's I don't know. She's Latin. No
Got what she is. That's scared of her. Oh, she was uh, yeah, he was right
He was terrified of her because she would like
She's also weird in other ways, but that was just a quote from a little quote from that message
Everyone put in the butt plug
The blowcock all day long
How do I eat some five minutes, but
The YouTube guidelines were different.
Can you treat this less like a dictatorship?
Um, I don't think it's a dictatorship.
How's it a dictatorship?
Like, those are the YouTube rules.
I might be more strict on them
just because people have been abusing, right?
Maybe you don't call a CB a chicken.
See, I've been six for three days.
Oh, I hope you feel better.
Starting better, Nancy.
Yeah, everyone's unmodded guys. I'm gonna be the only mod here. So you guys won't get yelled at by everybody
Not I
Never had so many people they see that chat where so many people
They take my wrench
so
You guys stick with it with me. I appreciate it, but you guys will be safe now for me
They're like you don't have to worry about oh, well this one doesn't like me
There'll be time me out if I'm not if I'm not modest, so
right
What's up necks, how are you if you shut up? Yeah
You can only go oh come on
Good and join the Sun okay good. Hi easy. Oh, okay. Come on
And guys sometimes, you know, you know doesn't show but you know if
Somebody like really makes me uncomfortable and I don't catch the comment right and you wanted the comment deleted
There's doxing in it or it's just like you feel like you're being bullied
Sometimes you have to bring it to my attention because I am trying to run the panel at the same time
Next every note no mods in the room no mods to make it bear and I'm a little cop
Sorry in my uh, I'm blurred vision happens when you okay weirdo I this was from with the record island
That's what yeah, nothing with record island. I don't think prison looks you nice
Jail certainly wasn't
It's better. Yeah, I think so
because I don't want and
I also I don't want people to
Be afraid of like commenting in chat and it's like and sometimes they were in the
And then mods. I don't know. I had too many people modded to you. It's just better. It's none then I can
Be responsible for it goes drunk you cause havoc. Yeah
Yeah, but you know I'd like I'd love to see a sea of green if you know if you you guys if you do want to stand out more
You know of course I most of you guys are really
really like
Great friends loyal loyal friends of the show
You can get to you're naming green I think some green
the membership. Panel is the problem, not the chat. I know, but then the panel, the
difficulty going over in the panel last night, because he was like, well,
why aren't you applying things equally? Why am I not a mod then? So a mod can talk about me,
but if I talk about anybody, I get timed out. It was kind of like, the answer is obvious,
I'm the head mod, I'm the head mod,
that puts my assistant as a really cool,
cool little robot assistant.
Okay.
Head bush buggy, easy, so, uh-huh.
Ask the white mommies, you know.
You have to, you have to keep Alex as a mod.
Alex is banned.
I did like it.
I did let him on panel for a second
because curious why he came back.
And then he is like, drunk.
And he's like, he's like, ah, be this at me.
And then he's like, what?
But I think I've had enough.
Yeah
It's like I think I think it's like I always thought oh, yeah, I want to have like the you know
I'd love having people of modern that you know they help and everything
But it's just it's like too much to ask of you guys especially because there's gonna weird right so make sure
Everyone's safe. I want to make this a really safe place. I'll also be really careful about
Not letting people on the panel like you know, there'll be less fighting
So then it's gonna cut off people that start disrespecting people there's guys
It was it was just bad when people were okay
They're calling page and a page of bitch and like other in there
You know, I had you know, we had you know some
You know more like mature ladies in there. They're calling them hose and dishes and stuff
It's not it was like horrifying and like a lot of people would just say what there's shots, right?
because they're like
I was like, oh, well, it's a drama panel.
So that's what people do, but it's not right.
It feels bad.
People get attacked, and it's like, you're not asking for it.
So maybe on a panel, maybe, people, when I attach it out
or talk, you've probably got a public, yeah, you barely.
OK.
Actually, you know I have one mod I have one month to it's nightbot
Yeah, I feel you huh we're gonna keep it we're gonna keep it nice and if people don't like you know
I talked to some other streamers. They just gave me some good advice. They're like, you know what?
They go like I wouldn't tolerate any of that in my shed. I would just I would kick them off
I don't I don't know like
How good they're how good the show is and stuff, but I think it will still be good because we have great panels when everyone's getting along
Having fun, you know
Okay, today I was wanted by the government.
They service soldiers of fortune.
If you have a problem, if no one else can help,
and if you can find them, maybe you can hire the A team.
Oh, Mr. T?
Hi, Gotti.
Yeah.
Oh, Gotti, your prayers have been answered.
Everyone's unmodded.
All right, so I took all the power to myself.
You can't UN a JT and rank up yell at me. Oh the mods are doing this. The mods are doing that
I know you I know you really didn't but especially JT right so
Um, like yeah, like yeah, I might start streaming if I can figure out how
To my YouTube can connect on your stream pad, okay?
Well, it can
Just had to log into YouTube through it. Yo, what's up, Gotti?
Well, you know, yeah, she won't need she really doesn't need it because nobody has a branch to take you know take her
It'll be up to me, right?
Okay
You know what you know, I have a this the a stream forgive the A team this is the a stream right?
I'm just kidding you can put money in your no come on
No, and but yeah guys if someone is like saying stuff stuff that really bothers you
I tell me to leave the comment. I'll believe the comment, you know
Because some things you might not appreciate in the chat and so
But I apologize in advance that
Some people will say some crap was the a stream. That's cool. Jericho the a stream
Right, you can have the ATM. I'll have the a stream
together
Well, I go to the top
Joey, okay, that's the wrench for no no no no none no last for anybody
Just night Nipah got one. He had the last one
I melted down all the other ones and I made it into one giant wrench and
I carry that like a club
Hey vader, how are you guys doing?
so
Anybody want me to draw them I can draw a picture. Let me see. Oh god. I like your picture got it. It's like like a old man god
Hey vader
If I miss anybody in the chat, I'm sorry. Hello everybody Mikey
Keep her being here guys. The chat's going really nice today, too
Like everyone's getting along or you feel like a better vibe. I think it's like, you know, I finally like, you know
Finally the actually stand up for the chat right you draw you okay
Okay
I don't know if this will look right on.
I don't think I did a bridge. I don't know
How's that okay got it I think I finished it hold on I need to fix it
Okay, you're ready. I had the big reveal
I'm gonna use what I need a couple more things
Oh, no, which is usually oh shit
It's a banana. Okay. I got it. Got it. Here. What do you think? Shit.
Scotty. The moon came out looking like a banana, but maybe it works. I don't know.
Gotty. There's the sun, moon, star, and there you go. You got a cross.
I tried not to make you look bad. Did I get it accurate? I don't know if I got you
How's that look?
Is it good?
Oh, I forgot the two.
Well, can I put a little bandage on your head?
Hold on.
I don't know where it is, hold on.
Put a little bandage on your head,
so it's perfect, okay?
Love you God, okay
You have to hop on panel. Yeah
You're welcome your pleasure any time, okay
And anybody else want one? I want these for the book. Maybe I'll publish them if I ever publish a
Book I'll put some of these pictures in it. I do. I do. I love this Goddy one
Why did I draw a banana that definitely the banana look I mean I tried to draw the moon
I drew it way too skinny and it came out a banana even with the dick the fucking stem on it. What the hell I
Know I can draw a banana like that
Modern day Van Gogh and it only took me like two minutes to draw it to
Yeah, I'm sorry, I've heard you have some health problems maybe God and I'm you know, I wish you healing and
You know, I hope that you're okay
Pain and
Thank you
Yeah, Facebook Facebook. Yeah, I left Facebook probably several several years ago
It looks like a dick to you. I don't know
Oh, I'll like I'll make I'll make the tip really black
It either makes it look more like a penis or less like I don't know what it has a look
There's not a banana. I just made all color yellow
You know in the Emperor card it actually looks like he's holding. He's holding like a golden orb or something
But it looks like he's holding a lemon. Okay, good
And I know I know but you know
I just wanted to send my my my love to I may said block me
How older my cats Rudy's the old man I just got him this year, but he's
16 maybe 17 the North's probably five years old
Lola's probably three years old and my marbles probably around three years old
and Tricks was born last year, yep.
Hold on, I forgot one, I forgot one detail.
Oh, I fucked it up.
Just better
If you point on you, it's good. Well, I really do like horns. I used to have horns, too. You can see right
You see right there
To see look I don't know maybe I'll put a pitchfork in there, too. You kind of remind me of book. I ruined it. Oh shit
You can make into a hat
Sorry, you don't like the horns
Okay
Lena Lenina
Katina
Mama Mia
God have you ever seen my test you you ever know I have the devil on my back all the time
Can you see that well? Yeah, I know her. It's great, thank you. I actually based it on Ann and
Nicole Smith and the Lords of Asset Artwork. I got one at 18.
Okay, yeah, but I yeah, and I had they had a pin-up
Shot of her and then I was like the ad the loads of ads
They used to have a lot of demon girl art. It was kind of cartoony with like maybe like blue skin and like
and so they had a colored in later with
The blue but the original artist that did it was a very famous tattoo artist named Fredy Negretti
Had it done when I was the 18 and black and white. He's a prison artist. He's a prison tattoo artist and
Yeah
Goddy, I might like you like I'll put good Goddy, and I'll put evil. This won't be evil Goddy
Then I'll put I'll make an angel God you too, and then you'll have it'll be like you
I don't know I'll figure it out
Okay, yes, bunkie. So he's awesome
Okay
There's no evil hey
I love he said you're a Gemini but Gemini. Oh, I don't know. He's from Gemini energy, which is like
Yeah
But then we get in duality. You know, we need God in the devil
I don't know. Maybe she's all like a sexy devil woman or something or I don't know if you're married or what but I
Don't know. I have another page that cross from it. If you want some somebody to go with the
The only place evil God you lose this is on this page, okay?
Perceptions
right but personally I believe we're all part of God but nobody is God not
saying that there's anything wrong with calling yourself God it's like no it's
your own choice it's a great name to want to emulate but you know you know who
you know who else want to change the name to God was Lucifer
The trolley, okay always
He's a Catholic God Mike he's always
It's okay
Just troll away
Be gentle this is yeah
well, God guy according to
Ezekiel he was God's favorite angel his covering chair of the leader of the heavenly choir
and
You know he wanted to he aspired to be God instead of being like God
Then God's like you want to be me here really your own earth and you throw me down to his mud ball
He's the now he rules here
For the most part
Well
You're the evangelical angel. We're creating God's image. So we are God's. Yes
I think that's another thing is that if you look at the triad of the demons angels and then humans, right?
so we have the angels which are
Closest to God that they have no free will because they just do God's will and
Then the demons they just do the opposite of what God's will is, you know
Just for the sake of doing the opposite humans. We can have the choice
We have free will, right? We have free will so we have the choice to
Go toward God
Be good or evil. It's also called North-Node South-Node in
In astrology, you know, I want to look in your North-Node South-Node
The North-Node is like kind of the North Star where you want to head to this
represented by a certain sign and that's like the South South node or South Pole
South-Full
In the south node, which is like which is like we're comfortable comfortable and I'm maybe our lower self, right?
Yet liquid is accomplished. Well
Yeah, I think with the help of man, you know
Kind of like it but I kind of look at it like no, I don't know if you can picture it like
It can be here either way you want, but I think I think there's a mixture of like the earth and the in the sun and like the earth like the earth and the
Sun energies, right?
But the Sun animates the earth energy. I don't know trying to think about it. Stay knows litmus tests for humanity. You see if they
Can reject him or not
right
What got he who's what I here's what I like in it, too
So there's um, you know, Willy Wonka and the chocolate factory the original one, right?
So the kids start waiting the tickets for the movie right and then but every time one of the kids one ticket
There's this like little dark little scary look at man with glasses
Comes it approach them with whispering in their ear or yours get real big. He does it to everybody and
You don't nobody knows what was he whispering to them then in the movie they get to the room with the everlasting gov stopper, right?
And so Wonka like gives them all to keep where he's here. Here's how he's going to keep
and
They and
They all accepted it but the thing is
Then to the end of the movie
He takes charge out of the factory and Charlie takes every last thing gobs up or puts it on his desk
And then he turns around and he's like you won because the whole thing was a test
Which is who are the kids?
We're gonna go bring the god stopper to slug worth who really works for Willy Wonka
You really want to just use them as a test that's kind of like what I think it was the devil
But there's ways of looking at things that that that movie is also good because almost like the seven deadly sins are involved in it
And then, you know, Charlie had the purest heart, you know, he was like the nice person there, everyone else was like, you know, had this horrible, horrible personality thing.
Story that goes, that movie with really bored, how long, about a serial killer?
Oh, yeah, maybe, I don't know, well, yes, because he's like, oh, they were almost gone.
I mean, I don't think they really died in the movie, but yeah, they all changed into different shapes and stuff.
Hey, Jan, how are you?
Yeah, mm-hmm. Oh you did big saw
Story goes that movie. Yeah, okay
He drank the yeah, the bubbly drink the fizzy lifting drink with that with grandpa Joe. I mean, I love the Willy Wonka
Roald Dahl and Jane Wilder
Um, it was, you know, Willy Wonka, pretty brilliant.
Uh, yeah, he took a bubbly drink. Yeah, he sold a fizzy lip-sync drink.
Almost got stuck in the ceiling fan.
Yeah, oh, it's just a burp, though. It's just a burp.
Um, yeah. I know the movie both of you.
Cheer up, Charlie.
Don't be afraid.
I don't want to start an argument, but the way I was treated earlier, you broke my heart,
psyche.
You broke my heart.
Because you were mean to me like oh Joe's this Joe's a drunk Joe's an asshole. Why would you say that about your friend?
That was somebody else in the chat. That wasn't you. That wasn't me. Oh, yeah
No, it wasn't it wasn't psyche was a guy. No, it was a guy on the bicycle
What it was the guy that rides the bicycle proud of them
it
I said I wasn't in the gingers
And they want their headphones back
Okay, I'll send I'll send them right away
That wasn't even funny you that was so gay wanted those such a gay joke
How do I say it may may that was such a may
Those of May
Well remember when you say maggot you got to say maggot, so how do you say hey you're like
You're not a big day. You say gay. It's fine. You say gay. You can say queer
But like anybody got a fork so I can eat sucky's asshole like anybody got a spoon I can borrow because I'm really hungry
and a can of butter and salt
Stop sexually harassing me
It's good. Yeah, I can't I can't believe I used to used to you know joke around like that with people was shocking
Well Joe
You will get a go get a grapefruit eat that you're not touching my butthole with a spoon, okay?
Hi, Jamie.
Jamie, don't worry.
I unmodded everybody.
You did a great job of the mod.
I don't want you being harassed.
I know you already got a little bit of trouble from people
and people are yelling at you sometimes,
but you can still do the nightbot commands if you want to.
I love you.
I did, I unmodded everybody, so for nightbot.
And so I don't want anybody to get blamed
for anything that happens in my chat.
I'll take all the heat, okay?
Okay, love you, Jamie.
Hopefully is I think it will work better. Yeah, no mods
You're free guys guys the mod the mod the wrench is actually like a it's like a it's like a chain
It's like a bond is now and now that I'm carrying like a hundred pound wrench
I understand how heavy this, you know, so you really need mod. Well, is your name nightbot type
You change your name the lead nightbot, you know, right by technicality. You'll have to mod you, right?
Why is gonna regulate the amount of oh come on, we're not regularly you need your mod back
It's okay
No, no one really like you know you guys were really great great mom
But you know because I didn't really need you to do much like you know, but I know it's stressful and
You guys did a good job. It'll be much better. I know Casey no mods the first. Yeah, so then that first complaint is like, you know moot
Moot, Moot, Moot, Oliver.
Oh, okay.
Oliver, you're not doing that, are you?
Okay, I can't talk to the links, that's the only thing.
If you wanna send, if you wanna, yeah.
I'll have to kind of be looking at people's links
if they wanna link post it.
Or are they gonna just,
people can post the channel name that you searched for,
or the at in your channel name,
or you can come just inside the streamer studio,
put it in the private chat,
then I can post it in the regular chat, or.
I can look forward to you.
I do want to...
But also, I'm just really worried.
I'm kind of like...
What's been happening is like, you know,
like I told you, like, I woke up in chats.
I went to... I think I beat a chat last night,
but, you know, I'm not going over there anymore,
but I was there maybe
a week ago or something,
and it's like this...
Her chat was just saying, like, really bad stuff.
It's just talking really bad about me.
And...
Then Alisa's chat the same thing and it's like an ASUS and people to chat and then people started saying oh
Psychies sent sent us to troll you and they say terrible things and
So I don't want anything bad to happen to any
You know, I don't want I don't want any
situations like my my
Trolling situation to happen any of you so
So if you if you really like to promote your show, you know, you can ask me and I will but
and I know probably
Done a little bit hectic lately
You must be Kate trying to act like a beta and stay drink to get attention I keep my head
Oliver you're gonna pull your face off. Why are you doing that?
Okay, remember Oliver's neck
No, I don't remember what you said about that if you want to you said you want to you want to
Knack neck and make out with Oliver. I have never had it but taking away by you here. Oh Jamie. Yeah, please don't yeah
It's just it's just the best it's the best so everyone's a model and
Then everyone's free from the tyranny of other mods or rogue mods. I promise don't be a rogue mod
Like you Matt you and show have some good combos
Well, yeah, I mean that one we had was fun last night the other guy kind of like buttered in and he was talking fast
Wow, he's a nice guy, but
He keeps telling he keeps like telling a
Jota Jota to kill Boston, but
Hello hi dude
How are you happy Sunday Sunday Sunday, I'm doing good. I hope you
Nice watch
I watch nice one. Oh, it's a car. Okay. I'm sorry guys. I'm telling my vision my vision is going
I think my late six wearing off. I like when psyche and Joe talk about. Oh, yeah, we definitely sing the
80s theme songs
Freeze come that's not good times. That's the untrackable show. You know untrackable. He's awesome
It's a little car. It's like a little car little blue car
That's probably that that size cars only probably the only car all are beautiful to get
A hot wheel
Joe Shippley is the great untrackable passive enlargement the fees so that's tracked by China. Oh
Thank you
Yeah, so what's up? Oh
No, I'm doing good hanging out
The the fam went to go see other fam and I I chose the other option which was to sit here and
Talk to y'all and prepare for Monday
There for Monday. Are you working tomorrow?
Or doing something?
cool. Yeah, I
Have something about a good doc happening at good times. Oh, Casey
Don't show up at his house
No, I know I drew I joined track a week before but I can't I can't draw him today. He just has a little his little sports car
Let's see, what else can I draw I can draw Joe
That's got
Oh, it's great to draw this one
I need to put on my phone. Hold on. We'll do that better. Oh
Do you do drawings as well?
Yeah, I did I draw you before I have you in my other book. Did I draw you the other day?
It's been a while but that that was I actually thought that was that was fun. That was a good time
Yeah, I
You know, I'm not like the best artist, but it's kind of I remember I like John Lennon used to have like you know art
Princeton, I don't know if like either with Yoko or whatever, but he was there just like kind of simple lines with there like so like
They're so simple, but they're cool, and I kind of like that stuff
Okay, so I'm looking for the okay. I'm gonna charge your ship. They just in the picture. Let's see
All there's a bottom, okay, okay, let's see
I'll make it look like you hold
where did Joe go? Was he acting up?
No, he said he has to...
I don't know what he said he had to do. He had to go.
Oh yeah, no, he was acting up. He was like...
Yeah, he said he wants to put a spoon in my asshole or something like that.
It's a little bit too gay for me.
I don't like things in my butt.
Okay, so...
I don't see like the logo that was on Joe's head.
I can do, well, I can't, I can't, I don't see the,
I don't see the rig up there even though,
I'll have to find it later.
They've changed it so many times.
Joe, that must be a vintage hat or something.
Oh, hold on, there's on your screen.
Yeah, let's see.
Oh, here, oh, here's Joe, do you wanna talk to Joe?
Hey, Attracable, do you wanna,
do you wanna hear the Shrews
or do you wanna hear Sight Lies?
Which one do you wanna hear?
I
Was bad what?
Yeah, you banished me like when he the retard you're busy. Oh
They ask people juice if you dig a six-foot hole how deep is that hole? He was like probably 25 feet. I
Love me the juice. I love me to decide. Oh, there you go
Yeah, well guys to be fair. I never said I'm gonna eat your asshole with a spoon
I said, hey, you're
Somebody in the chat is like oh well, so you can say that kind of stuff to guys that Joe can't
You need to take a red take the red psych
He's already the average it's a wrench
Okay, but Joe
If you would eat my ass and I would eat your ass, but we both agree that we are
And you're not gay you're just an ass, okay, okay guys
Yeah, see like I got I have a little perspective of yeah, I can't believe I actually hit on guys like that
It's not disgusting. That didn't sound bad
Please
Sounds terrible
They can go eat each other's ass. I don't want it on my show
Yeah, I wasn't invited that it was the biggest this
They said two straight guys do it the gay guys never included it. They always I'm always excluded
Immature, I mean, yeah, they're immature
The I'm matured
Yes, yes, Joe
Went way too far. I just it's okay. I don't like a mockery of my
My gay lifestyle
Basically straight man. I'm very offended. That's sexual harassment. Okay. Well, now you're not there to make the kiss
Untrackable, so I'll bring him back now. I'm not my only option. You can make out with me
Or whatever you said anal sex or whatever. Oh, I'm just kidding grew up. Joe. What's the hell? Yeah, it was too far
No, don't be. Oh gosh guys. This is the beginning of
We'll see how people react to being timed out
And I can we'll take it well, sure
Oh, it's okay, I know you're just joking around news and I was happily kidding too of it. Yeah, I'm trying to like I'm trying to
Have to show a less gay place so and so the straight people could feel feel a comfortable here, too
I
Got you. I'll tell you. Okay. Good. No, it's just fine
You guys are acting up. Okay time time. Oh Joe, I'll do better than that show
You're gonna have to figure out how to get a contact with me
Yeah, Joe
Okay, yeah, it's like, I read it, I was looking, it's something really good about boundaries,
about setting boundaries, and then, because it's a lot of people who are kind, and then
they know the person's kind so they'll probably grant at least part of the request or you know
compromise on it and they count on that and so the point the point is that it's like people will
take advantage of your perceived kindness and thinking that they can they can do that and so
the kindness is not a weakness and so I learned I should uh firmly remind that I am kind but I'm
No means no and that's that and that's period
So I understand what people were saying when guy was saying I was weak in 83 I'm weak and like you know people are saying grow a pair
Yeah
I've been a little do you know what really snapped me out of it. It was when
be a joker and Mr.. Big Pipe's and Crystal and
She like all these people came on one night. She's just like really saying awful things to me and it's like I
Mean some bad things have been said to me on the panel before but like never like that
And it really hurt and it's like and now I know how people felt when they were kind of getting attacked on the panel, right?
and so
Thank you, guys and you
You know as a guest I
I am not allowed to forget that you are the provider of this space and
It doesn't have to be a safe space
But you know if if something goes against the grain and in what you want to be happening right in front of you
You have the ultimate power to
you know remove people from this space and also shut this space down that that that is
Yeah, I mean
Liddy to take on when you are offering it to what you hope to be you know
Reasonable consenting people
They can be tough. I see well, I say I feel like I feel like I've been through pretty much
You know
I've been through like a pretty pretty few pretty good good waves there, right and
I'm still standing right now, and it's like that means I still have a chance to like
to like
With fixed things and adjust and you know, I can I can I can do it
I can like you know, I'm not I don't give up. You know, I'm a capricorn. We like we'll freaking climb the mountain
talk to God and
You jump down to the ocean, swim to the bottom, talk to the devil, and talk to both.
Let's see.
So you would time out everyone for 24 hours, use the first one to have one.
Yeah.
So, but yeah, but as for a safe space, no, I mean, originally, like my vision was never
so much conflict in the room, it just turned into like, you know, because I had open panels
and because of the panel panels I had come from and the people I had talked to and stuff,
the first people to come, it kind of like set a tone of like, oh, the audience life drama
and the people that were on the panel pretty much like to do the drama too, and at that
time, so everyone was happy.
But then it gets to like then people that were not really a panelist that the panels are tacking the chat people are following each other from different places
And people are saying really rude things people are chasing off
You know, I have a lot of like nice the nice older ladies that would come in and they they would just be people would call them
the grading names I should have been
This has been better as like stopping it, but you know, it's like it's a time you're like, oh, well
It's supposed to be you know a dramatic panel and this is the but the audience wants you know
But it's not the kind of show I want it's like it's a
I've watched you, you know for several months now and trust me. I'm not an expert. I'm not doing these things
I'm not offering up
the risk
However, I have watched you go through, you know, people coming in and then they'd be nice and then be like, hey, I'm going to invite this person over.
But the person they're inviting with inviting is their nemesis, their arch rival of this.
And it's like, hey, we're going to use your living room.
as our, you know, battle royale.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, I mean, it's something similar has happened to me,
like in the real world, with like, you know,
it's kind of, it's called like a trap house, right?
Where it's just like, you know,
got people coming in and all, you know,
everyone's doing drugs and, you know,
people are selling drugs in the house
and there's police are always outside and,
Just think there's always the people that's just respectful destroy the place right and so I
See the analogy very well with you know, this is also a room that I can
actually instead of just opening up to
Everybody to come in and stomp and you know put out
cigarettes in the
You know the candlesticks and
You know get muddle over the floor and you know pick the cat and all you know it's like no sick. We're
We're gonna have a nice
People don't look at the channel. They're gonna be a vibrant. It's not healthy something I think that there's gonna be enough unique
unique stuff
Right in the channel that will compensate for the lack of just
Hatred and fighting again. I mean that did anybody think it was just stressed most people out and scare people away
and that was fun for like some people but
Like seriously, I was getting very bored with like some people yelling at each other
I was like hoping that eventually the conflicts would like oh you come to like some kind of oh we talked for a while
Oh, I actually like you a little bit you can talk with I've seen it happen a couple times where people were like the enemies
And then they could kind of get along
But not very often like most of the time. There's like no reconciling. There's like it's they're just gonna it's just gonna
Not gonna you know, they're not gonna ever
Defense that's fine, but they don't have to be arguing every day in my chat screaming and yelling. I have any problem with the problem. I
can't I have to
I'm very sensitive to energy too. And so it kind of like there's really fucking on my energy
I can say that
Again, I'm not doing it, but I'm learning with you by being part of what you're doing and
You know it it can be tough to recognize when somebody's being playful and they say something or
When this is about to go down the wrong way or when
You know hey, let's just say you have a full panel, but two people own it. You know what I'm saying
Yeah
Yeah, and sometimes there's interest that sometimes there's people like I had something I had people that were like
You know probably had never had a discussion together except for like, you know
It's just night being on each other's channels back and forth and they're able to go to come together have a discussion on my
Piano probably and that maybe that was some progress in the relationship or something and I
Just hope feel he comes with ceasefire if not like, you know, at least a live in that live and
You know, I'm not gonna go after you because we saw what happened in that case
The guy in Las Vegas. He was a streamer and he bullied this other guy incessantly
That was a streamer and got his channel taken down and that guy went and you know and then I don't live the guy's
What guy and his wife, you know, because he went insane, you know, so, you know, we don't went we don't went
That's the kind of energy that we don't we want to very much avoid on
You know very much, you know, so
Just like so much of the stuff that was going on was like stuff that should not be going on
Like it's there's not be there's not been doxy and there's not have been so slander and
Yeah, I mean really if I can't believe I survived this long though. Who knows of insanity anything to do with it
Insanity well, what does it mean you're talking about there's insanity like start creating mad like, you know the Joker you know the joke
Not Joker, but to the Joker, you know
He's because he goes like insane the world turns have been saying or there's like the insanity of like, you know
There's schizophrenia which may be some kind of spiritual thing actually were they actually are saying things avails us to
to a thin
to
Tell the difference in the astral and the physical sometimes
And then there's the narcissists and there's the psychopaths and there's the Machiavellians and so and and a lot of times
Those three are in a triangle
There's a lot of times they go together and that's like a that's not a good combination
Because that means the Machiavellianism is kind of like scheming
Getting power at all costs, you know conspiracies and then the narcissism is
I'm the best everyone else is like it
insignificant you know only I'm only my needs matter I need all the attention I
know the other gratitude and then psychopath just playing this thing
we'll do anything to anyone let's hear what they want and it's you've been do
very bad thing so
I think there's, I think there's a combination of some of these people and I think some people are completely the same.
I think some people are a little bit traumatized. I think a lot of people have PTSD and trauma.
But, you know, we all have something, you know, it's like our mind is, unless we have just this perfectly work,
that's, that thing really works perfect all the time.
So it's like we have to like work, you know, work with ourselves, work through our mind.
You know, it sees things it like, you know, we're very visual
Right
You're registered Democrat a few different kind of sectors kind of merged here
That's because KZ. I was in the black sector and I went to I was in the people's podcast. I was in you know
Every open panel I could find basically
And brought people from all over so I
Always believe in me so right through the rest. Yeah, I still believe in you. I still believe you Jamie
I always will and you were you're the best mod you're you're a great mod
I was like there's one mod a human mod. I would keep it would be you. I just don't want you getting harassed
Because people were saying oh
Jamie time me out because I don't want I'll take the I'll take all the blame for that. Okay?
You suffer a little easy
Yeah
It's easy down there. What's up? Oh, he's in the chat. Yeah, we do need someone positive. We do need more positive people because
you know
You know, some of the people were very like, you know, you said some very bad things
like
people
Even I mean even people I like even Joe even Joe said terrible things to people. I mean, I'm here. Oh, I can't repeat them because it's like, you know
It's a thing
That's all you know something. It's me
get to know people is being honest about myself and
It's not so much about the sharing it's like hey, I'm gonna about to put an honest sentence
That describes a moment in my life and your reaction to my honest sentence
It teaches me something about you. You know what I'm saying does that make sense to you?
Yeah, you're honest sins. They say, oh, what would you say? Honest sins?
Honest. Honesty. When you say something that is true and verifiable and whatever,
but you're trying to have a conversation with somebody, well, rather than them share
equally, even if it would be a lie, it's like they, so many people just go straight to, oh,
That's how that's how you did it, and they just start to pick apart your your story
I'm saying I never told people to un-alive themselves. I never told people put a bull through your head
I've never said I'm gonna come come on, you know, SCA be you I'm gonna be actually set up
Graping people yes things like this were said by people on that show and maybe I said I
Don't really think I said that outrageous of things, you know
Maybe I might have said the word bitch or something. I don't know. Maybe I said other things. I don't know
Did I say guys have you heard me say something?
What's the worst thing you guys in the chat heard me say to somebody and have I ever said to told somebody to like
Analyze themselves or I'm gonna hurt anybody or they ever make a threat to anybody. That's what I'm talking about
so I was like a responsibility for
My behavior in chat I said I was not a very good host I allowed
Some of the guests to get pretty much yell that pretty pretty bad by some other guests and I didn't intervene and
When I should have
because sometimes there was like something cause people wouldn't want to uh, me at me to intervene, right?
They'd be like, oh don't but sometimes they would and sometimes they'd be to have that relationship where they talk like that
but still I don't want to sit on my show and
right intractable ones to
Oh, really? Well, it's okay
Hey, thank you. You got yelled at and by who?
Who got yelled at? I got yelled at by several people
Probably like, you know several people
For what I have been for several months, but I think a lot of people got yelled at a lot of females on the panel page got called
terrible names people would say just terrible personal things like oh you know
just you know how it's controlled but it's like some people like she was kind
of new to it and you know there was really personal stuff you know even
like we might
My dad's anniversary was passing.
You know, I share a little bit.
Yeah, I'm going to have dinner.
This is a year ago.
He passed away.
People coming on under accounts saying my dead dad
or psyche's dead dad.
People saying psyche's mom killed his dad.
People coming up with my real name,
my address, dog thing.
Having so many pieces sent to my house.
Yeah.
So, I mean.
It wasn't a picnic over here. So I'm saying I didn't want that to happen
I don't want it to happen to anybody. I don't the dog's needs shouldn't happen to anybody. It's so
so immoral and
It can lead to death just like swatting so I can easily lead to a death you have you tell you call the
Authorities of police and say oh this person has an assault rifle under their bed or something or there's a hostage in their house
These SWAT team can come in the middle of the night break down their door the person
Maybe they have they have protection like they have a firearm
They pull it out that's what opens the door. They got told me a firearm the guy's gone
That's he just trying to protect himself and he didn't call the police, right?
right
Retroling is like that. I would hear
if hurt yourself
Because they all would have been in jail. Yeah, I'm saying that's I mean that's like no laws one of the biggest
deterrents for like, you know
reason why we don't all
Don't alive each other imagine going to jail. See I cyberbullied somebody. Yeah, but I mean cyberbullied
There's this case of this guy. He's like part 16 or 17. You know, he was getting a school in high school and they
They would have a lot of text messages, but eventually, you know, she started trying to convince them that, you know, he should unalive himself and here's how to do it.
You know, you just take a hose and, you know, take it to your, put it in your car and put it in the window and, you know, it's, you know, here's how to do it.
And then she sat on the phone with him while he did it and made sure he did it and then he died.
And so then all the text messages, she's encouraging him to do it.
But cyberbullying, cyberbullying can have real consequences.
What about the case without the cyberbullying case
where actually it leaks over into real life sometimes.
That's what I'm saying.
Especially when you get with the dox thing
and then you have really obsessed people doing things, right?
It's very dangerous.
So that's why.
And especially after that last case with Las Vegas,
I'm gonna be very careful with doxing
and making sure there's no addresses,
phone numbers, full names,
or anything that people don't want,
pictures or anything that is not the person in the chat,
right?
Morning, David, Claude,
the bathroom, and I've been a whole mess before.
Okay, bye.
So, morning cleaning.
Where's the matter?
And many here on YouTube,
try to play words down.
Yeah, and it's also because people feel so free
to say anything.
I mean, you can, it's great.
You can feel free to say anything
because you're like, you know, behind a mask
or behind an avatar or voice changer.
You can say anything.
Most times people will be savvy enough to know,
oh, this is not viable, but a lot of times people will,
We'll be very terrorized heard people being charged with it. Yeah
Actually, it's gonna be happen more and more. I just read it
I saw a case with this guy was being sex-storted by an AI that made AI
He was being sex-storted by it and I think he analyzed themselves
Here on YouTube for a different platform. Okay, let's see
It's starting to dig deep within the trolling community. I think think that
They have been right
Uh, who's going to, uh, regard to, okay, that's why I said they're gonna change the law. Yeah, it's gonna be more
Hey, stricter. If I'm thinking, I'm, I'm going through a struggle. You can do it to that person that hates the heart. So, you know, you go
I'm not negative. We know you're not negative. Yes, we are
Yeah, I know
Like, you know, Jamie's like, you know, Jamie's, you know, she's been on the panel and stuff, but she never was like, you know, really
She was mostly in the chat and it's like, you know, people would harass her and stuff and
And also you got to the point when people are making videos, you know
Or just to hear the topic of the show and she wasn't even on YouTube panels or anything and people were just saying bad things then
It's kind of shocking
Especially to who was doing it, but I feel everybody mentioned
Yeah
No, I just think of like, you know, you know, you on the INE where you know
With the assault rifles
like that's
some states is a very available and
This guy got bullied and then they took it out on right
Now it's not cyberbullying, but that was the bullying, okay
Yo, hey, what's going on? You seem concerned. You seem a little bit stressed. What's going on everything, okay? Oh
Yeah, everything's fine. I'm gonna draw your muscles one. No, I just like I
It was like so exhausting like last night. I was on I talked to like this guy. I won't say his name, but he was just
Couldn't know complaining complaining complaining including about the mods
Mods are fighting with each other. There's
mods that are
Hate each other and I'm having to mod people to prevent them from being timed out of the chat. So I
Just I'm modded everybody. That's working a lot better
But I'm gonna draw your muscles once
You might hold on. I don't know if I can your face. I'll make your face all dark
Well
Okay, I say this as a friend. Okay, don't get mad, right?
Don't get offended or anything
But what are your thoughts on the concept of authority because you here are the ultimate authority
So do you think that perhaps the lack of authority within this channel could be
Contributing to some of these factors that you're dealing with
Oh my gosh, what I just said that I said it was my fault because I was kind of letting things go wild
I was being too nice. I was not setting boundaries. I was giving too many chances. I was yeah
You know, I'm taking responsibility for but you know, it's like I don't I know that
That doesn't use all the bad behavior from everybody just because this is my show
It's like so but that's in a way you're right because it's like it is my show and so everything that happens on the show I
Have some authority over but I'm saying you can't stop the words coming out of someone's someone's mouth
You can't control what people say and they
And I would try to and say hey, don't say this don't say this like like a
Someone says don't touch the stove. They've touched the stove. You know, sometimes when people told not to do something they'd like to do it, especially
roles, right?
Well, I think that
when we cannot control anybody's intentions when they come into our lives and
it's easier to handle those that are
Transparent on their evil intent
Upon entering our lives because at least we know, you know, at least we know
They I gotta watch out for this motherfucker
It's a lot more complicated when you're dealing with potential deception
And it's clear that the fact that a lot of these people are able to hide it
Enables their deception
And it enables their evil intentions to perhaps bypass some of the smoke screens to bypass some of the walls that we set up to protect ourselves.
Well, right, but yeah, especially how I was letting everybody on and letting people on that I didn't even like on.
But yeah, now I know I can't I can't do IP checks of every single person in the chat
And then and I don't care see with anyone whoever wants to be in the chat
Most of the time that there people are just nice in the chat and you know, I do have people still watching out for me in the chat
It's gonna be a safer place. And so I don't really care what goes on in the chat on the panel
They have a bad feeling if I the person's rude to me or the guest or
This is our conflict with several it's like it's not not for my show. So that is gonna be my choice, but uh
Yeah, I mean it's like yes people will try to you know go under different accounts
They'll probably try to come form bomb still they're probably you know, it'll be I'll just have to be more alert
Which I will be
It's a shame that when you have an open door for anybody to be able to come and enjoy themselves,
inevitably there's those that come with evil intentions.
It's a shame, but it places us in a point of responsibility to exercise order.
because it was starting to feel quite chaotic, like.
And I'm glad you caught it, I'm glad you caught it.
Sometimes it needs to get to that chaotic point
to like get, like, to switch back,
or to like, you know, it's kind of like,
just like on the, yeah, that's the whole thing
about the summer solstice.
It was like, it's time for rebalancing.
So I could see like on the summer solstice,
everything went askew, like for everybody.
And it's like,
because it's like people just change so much.
And so, you know, that's to show you where to balance it.
And I see like as the days have gone,
a few days have gone by, it's gotten a little better.
Okay, so, okay, hold on.
Okay, this is not the best, but it's not my best, okay?
Who's that?
You recognize the arms?
But I don't have long hair
No, that's not nothing. I think Chad. That's your black shirt and like your your shadow
And it's in the circle like you're after you're welcome. I don't know your face. I don't want to get your face wrong
Another work of art. Hmm. Thank you very much. I'm humbled. I really appreciate it
That's yeah, but I'm glad, you know, I'm happy that that you know, sometimes they we the biggest lessons in life come from
adversity
Yeah
Characters built their adversity. So I have a personal philosophy that you know, inevitably, there's one thing
There's one constant in life that we cannot control which is that we're gonna get hit with adversity. Thank
in a variety of ways.
But if we're able to train ourselves
to take such adversity,
to take when life is kicking our ass
and become stronger from it,
all we're gonna do throughout the passing of time
is continue getting stronger and stronger and stronger
and stronger because we know
that life is gonna kick our ass, all of us.
So if we are able to somehow channel that pain,
into strength then we're never going to stop getting stronger and and hopefully
Just developing a larger threshold for the suffering that comes with life kicker asses
True I mean
But uh, you know, there's a philosophy by Marcus Aurelius. He was the he was a Roman emperor
Tells stoicism
I have read meditations one and two, like numerous times, I think that Marcus Aurelius
is one of the ultimate role models for men and in today's society it's very important
to study his philosophies, I think, and the guy had a great heart, he was a very humble
leader.
I mean, that's a great plot. That's very interesting if you guys want to look at the stoicism
It's about you know, just like taking all the punches of life and
Not with a smile, but just maybe with a little bit of a grimace, but but there's also
also very helpful about if you people are suffering is
Buddhism and Buddhism saw life as basically suffering and
Even but even even the suffering in my opinion in my humble opinion
I think like there's only one
Being that is cognizant of the concept of death, which is human
No other living beings
Are able to understand the concept of death they don't understand the finality within existence
and
think that just the awareness of our own finality brings suffering and then
throughout history humans have developed a variety of ways to handle such
suffering I think religion is definitely one of them where you know
they've developed a system of you know if I if I if I lose a love which is one
So, I don't think, in my humble opinion, I could be absolutely wrong, you know, philosophy,
the essence of it is that it's all open-ended, it's not theology, this is just random thoughts.
But I think that as a species, we have not conquered that fear at all, that fear of
death.
It leads a lot of our behavior in everyday life and warfare and subsistence, and who
knows if we will be able to conquer it before we extinct ourselves?
We all will die and that's what we all have in common, but here's the thing, people think
Death death is suffering, but actually life is suffering. It's like life is the the pain is in the life
That would you the death? There's no more pain. You know, this is basically the human body is gone
The spirit is free. All pain is gone, right?
but
The with the life new suffers in life. It's like us when we lose our loved ones which but we all will I mean
It's like it's inevitable. We it's gonna be one of us for the other
But we all but that's a blessing too because you don't want to be stuck in immortal form in these in these bodies because
That would these are physical bodies. We need to be we need a body are you told to be free?
It's the fear unknown people are just scared death will hurt. I think well, you know
But how long it hurt for it's like, you know, hopefully, you know, it's a quick painless thing
I think it's a concept of under of being aware that our existence is going to end like an animal
No dog or elephant or zebra
understands that eventually
They're gonna stop breathing
So they are able to focus on enjoying the present, of course, because they are not aware of a lot of things,
but they are masters of living in the present.
And we have a lot to learn from, like your cats, for example.
Your cats have no idea that death exists.
So it's one moment at a time.
Well, they might.
We understand that they're going to pass one day and and we experience a level of
Suffering sometimes just even thinking about it. You know. Oh, yeah
Yeah, but I'll be you said it. Yeah, but you know, he said
well only human beings can have a daily concept of that we will we will die but human beings also have the concept of
and not all do but
Human beings also contemplate their existence and they have an awareness of some kind of higher power that maybe animals
Probably don't consider or meditate on or think about and we do so we have also this ability to
Strive towards the higher okay, and that's like and we can when you say there's an impulse that higher power
Well, when you say have a higher power like and you know, this again, this is philosophy. It's an open-ended everybody's right
But what is your definition of a higher power?
I have power what people call it different names. You can call it the source. You can call it the all
You can call it the creator. You can call it all that is you can call it God
You can call Allah you can call it
Existence you can call it
Life and death you can call it duality. There's a lot of things we can call this, you know
Or not actually the I would say that the the higher power is not a duality. We're the duality down here the higher power
Probably more of a singularity like the more of the one and we're kind of split into two down here
We can see that there familiar with the concept of
anthropocentrism
I wish it's giving human quality is to animals or
Morphism okay for centrism is the concept of that everything in life revolves around humans
Well, that's that fits in with the biblical view because you know Adam is made the king of the animals and he's you know
And also also, you know the angels and the demons were asked to bow down for him
And the demons or the Jinn did not want to, they thought that they were superior to the Jinn, as a man, they were there before him, and they were made of...
That's a very anthropocentric concept of the Bible itself.
Yeah, I mean, it's man-censored, but you know, there's also humanism, I mean, the thing is, it's like...
The God the God part the higher the higher power is that's a mystery. That's like you have to you can't it doesn't just appear
It's like it's something you you have to
You're looking for first of all and so they try to connect with I mean
It's like not every people want to go through life thinking life is meaningless existentialism nihilism. You're born you die
It's like it doesn't have any meaning. It's not nothing. It says we're just here for a second. I mean then
You know, it's really easy for people to believe that and it's like and then you know
They don't they never look into these higher things
And if they don't they can't see something and they won't believe it, but it's like and again
We have so many things tell me it's much illusion in this world. We ever know what we're really really seeing there's so many
There's so much illusion, right?
it's like even the it's called Maya like just even the
Solid matter in life where illusion is not a part of it, which is nature
Well, we're from nature. We came from right there's no illusion in nature
Is there how about a mirage have it out? How about you know the rainbow that's what those are all lesions
If they look like they're there, they're not they just
But but that is part of here, but that is part of the human condition is lacking hydration to the brain
I don't know. It's like that's why
That oasis of the fear I think it has to do with like the illusion the Sun makes on the on the planet
There's sand perhaps perhaps. I don't know but for example like the the the deer
Cannot have the illusion to live another day under the jaws of the lion and it
Well, I mean if it escapes
But yeah, that's why I said under the jaws and not in the midst of the chase
Yeah, well, you know what sometimes
Maybe the land just ate and then he just wanted to kill it and then he bit his neck and
Let go and it ran away. It's the ones that hurt me. I'm free from the burden trying to make you happy
So thank you to better days your loss that mine here here, Jamie
Wow, yeah, game is so cute
You have a lot of very cute girls like not cute physically, but just like you can tell that they're like sweet
Girls like he mans very sweet girl. Jamie's cowboys very sweet reality Nancy's very sweet sassy scarlet
like you have very very sweet girls in your community and
You know that's that to an extent. That's what tends to not tense. I'm sorry, but
That's what should inspire authority is to keep them safe
right
Yeah, and you know
and you regret, you know, some people, you know,
we had Jamie Rose up and Jamie Rose is like, you know,
Jamie Rose is a little bit, you know,
has quite a vocabulary, right?
And she can go back and forth and fucking,
she can say, and she can, she can, she can find, you know,
she can argue about, you know, I never had a conflict
with her, we've called each other names and stuff.
We're besties in the next day.
And then, yeah, so yeah, and then there's people that are so yeah, I know she I know I don't need to jump in
I like hey, hey, it's me Jimi Rose alone
It's you she would certainly leave or just tell them to fuck up and leave her
Have a conversation some people seemed like that like you know
I've seen people like, you know, I'll say beta like would seem like that or she would like she can
Verbally spar argue, you know, some people in their place, you know, and they like really crazy things back, but
Later she would get mad about what she got called
There's one variable at play there which unfortunately and this is why sometimes I'm brought from the girl
is alcohol. I think there's two betas, I think there's sober betas, it's a
sweetheart, and I think there's drunk betas that is...
out for war as some drunks are, you know, as some drunk people, they tend to be, they just want conflict.
And I think that one important thing, especially because you host a panel that allows any type of mindset to join,
in other words, let's say you don't say, if you have to be sober to be here, if you're drunk, you're not allowed, for example.
Because there's going to be a change of behavior and there's a radical change of behavior and beat it
when she's intoxicated, when she's drunk, compared to when she's not.
And I... this is why I'm tough on the girl,
because I believe in sober beta.
I think that there's a beautiful heart there and a world of potential,
but it's only up to her to conquer herself
and just not allow any substances or any variables whatsoever to...
modify her behavior. Because you, I mean, dude, I mean, I think you more than anybody
has been the recipient of the claws when they come out. And the alcohol makes the claws come out.
Yeah. And I just don't know what to say when that happens. And it's like, I get a little bit.
Little bit. I'm really caught. I'm really conflicted version. I do not like fighting. I think I didn't really I didn't really I
Didn't grow up around like a lot of love people fighting or anything
You know, I you know, it's there if there was I would
Learn how to like be funny and soften like the mood and like in the environment. So but then
You know, that's easier to do with six small groups of people rather than these huge chats that yeah
You're dealing with a lot of very difficult challenges from a sociological standpoint.
Because you're dealing with people that behave towards you in a certain way when they're
I won't say upon you, but upon your viewership, the have influence upon your viewership.
So, let's say if what the viewership wants is to see that person intoxicated and your
viewership increases based on the negative behavior of that person.
Then it's like it's almost it's a weird thing where yes, you are finding success
But at what cost right and that's what I'm really realizing that it's like, you know, I feel like I
Did what I wanted to do. I've already accomplished. I wanted to you know, I was thinking you know build a channel over a thousand people
You know have like, you know, you know these amount of people in the chats and you know get monetized
And I've accomplished and so now it's just like now. It's just a matter of
Making it fixing it making it perfect making like now since I got all the hours I needed I got everything I needed
I already I already accomplished now. I now have mixed accomplishment is like, you know
You just building my channel maintaining my channel making my channel a fun place
entertaining, having fun and having people meet each other and this platform, this is
my channel, but the platform is really YouTube and so I have to really pay attention to what
YouTube is wanting, right?
Yes, and one thing I learned in college and a specific marketing class
That made me rearrange. I own my own business. I've been in business for 14 years. Thankfully successfully and
One thing that made me rearrange my marketing quite a bit was that the teacher mentioned how
You don't want to be a shoebox and at the time I did not understand what that meant like a shoebox
And that means a bunch of random stuff all put together into one outlet
Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah, and yeah in the past like when I will mark it I will be a
like oh look here's me like exercising here's like fitness here's like
outdoors here's like near shit I bought here's social life but that's that little
by little it makes it a fucking shoebox that you have to narrow down like the
type of people that you want to attract yeah and make your content base around
them
Not a shoebox of content as I was doing it, but I learned not to but just say what who are the people?
I wish to attract and what do they want to see?
Yeah, so I would say about that. It's like, yeah, I was over in the first building on my channel
I was
filling up the shoebox with it with anything else take pretty everywhere in the shoebox
Then there's a big variety and it's like, you know, it's like you never know what's they come out of the shoebox
But yeah, then it would have like kind of a
more of a niche audience as to what got pulled out of the shoebox now now I have enough in the shoebox tab
You know decide make a good selection of what I want and what I don't want now
I know I know because I now I have apparently everyone on
So now I know
You've had a good time like like you I think hopefully at this point you've learned
What not to promote?
Yeah, what not to be associated with and I think like what I've noticed I could be completely wrong
I'm not an expert in this topic at all, but what I've noticed
And the people that apply that shoebox approach to YouTube is that they tend to focus on like larger youtubers
So let's say like they're talking about the drama between Ethan Klein and Hassan piker and like all this stuff
That's their shoebox, but at the end of the day, it's still a little bit concentrated on YouTube drama if you were to put
But I think there's like my business operates as a I'm a specialist within a niche and
There's one thing that you can either
You can I kind of like be like Costco or Walmart where you have a lot
to sell at a low cost or
Which I think is probably wiser being as a smaller operation or
Having something that is a very very very high value for those who want it
Yeah, and I wanted I kind of want to do both I want I want people to find value in it and both you can do both
You can know
Are you here?
What you're saying wait, I can either have like a very small channel. I mean, it's like
Channel, but you can like focus on a niche like oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, like like yeah arrow. I'm gonna. Yeah, arrow. Yeah, do it very very well
And if and do you think good times gives a shit about tarot like yeah, I'll be one K
Yeah, so I was thinking like, you know, I was gonna I was probably like, you know, cuz I've done, you know
I was doing you know, very very long long long days and it's like, you know, so I figured out
you know, it's gonna be quality over quantity.
So I could probably do like maybe,
you could probably do four hours a day,
six days a week, and have the first hour
just completely doing readings.
And it's like, you know,
doing readings for the chat,
doing a general reading for the chat.
And if anyone wants a paid reading,
and then that's the first hour.
And then I'll post my stream yard link.
And the rest of the chat,
know that kind of thing um but I would have a topic they have a topic that's what people have to
talk about playing like when they join yeah when they join yeah you're right but it is kind of like
i see i'm not really into like the current events and so i won't i wouldn't know like oh this is
whatever we're talking about tarot yeah oh tarot okay yeah i can i can definitely do like you know
You know go card by card that we can do a car to show and just go over several of the cards and like you know
And really go into the meeting and people can you know, they learn a lot too. And so yeah, that's like I like to read stories
I'd like to
Teach the meeting very good at it
Thank you
Yeah, so yeah, I think that will
There's like so that's why the sometimes is that you were used by the
IP2 community as a vehicle for their bullshit.
And I hope you're affected by now.
It's the audience.
And the audience is like, you know, IP2 is still a streamer,
but the audience of IP2 is a bunch of people,
and it's like, and I'm probably just from here,
they're really into...
Yeah, they would do the concept of the locale right where it's like the locale is like you know anybody that they laugh at and
Like not with anybody thinking to somebody that's just some kind of like into just like human decay in into like how a human can behave as
The interself-destruction is what I will narrow it down. They're into human self-destruction
Yeah, that's what they want to witness and then we say what somebody that's the thing that beat it
I don't they understand is that
Bita is lost her ego is attached to the amount of viewers that she gets but she fails to understand that she's getting
More and more viewers based on her own self destruction
So at what point do you have to stop that shit?
I asked and then realized like the fuck am I doing to myself like yeah
My ego is being stimulated because I'm having a large amount of viewers
But the fuck is happening to me
Physically mental and emotionally they where am I going with this bullshit?
Yeah, well, yeah, and I agree and
Like okay, so I wish a mod for Benny and Benny had like 25,000 subscribers
But I'm not one of his mods told me a story. She's like should they will a year ago
He he had a problem with his mods because the mods had a discord group and the mods would like they would like
No, they would say oh, let's uh, they're like, let's let's donate like like a hundred dollars to him. So
He gets really drunk. He buys a bunch of bottles of like, you know, alcohol and like it's really drunk
And he said they just want to they what that wasn't they didn't wasn't like oh
We're gonna see him have fun as up like we want to see him like
You know crash hour like you fall asleep or you know, it was like so there was like even that was his mods doing that
That was his mods trying to
Just basically basically drug him and stuff and so
So then that's why he hated discord. I had a Benny discord and he found out about it
He was really mad cuz he thought you're probably doing the same thing, but
Yeah, and so but it is I mean it's like, you know
It's kind of sad like the people you know, you know people hate watch or people will
Like you know, just like that better person be tend to be their friends sometimes
I don't there's a lot of different different stuff. It's very high school. It's very immature. They have all these
Stupid stupid millennial or not millennial or like this is Gen Z terms. Yeah, yeah zoomer and
crash out and
There's much
Lake oh he he crushed out or oh he I don't even remember him all but yeah, it's burger and bird
Everything starts to kind of be adapted around those terms is that okay?
So you don't so the streamer as a streamer you want to make sure you don't crash out, right?
And then so in other words, am I am I supposed to just allow and tolerate?
Just abuse in the on the premise under the premise of not crashing out
You know so
It's it's it's read. I mean, it's again back to it's a sociological interesting
concept because
YouTube and this is what like I'm I do I'm concerned because human behavior is being highly affected by technology
by the algorithm and
You know, how many people?
Bays their behavior and how many likes they're gonna get on something or how many viewers are gonna get on something and
It is, it's, I mean, where is the humanity in that?
Right, well, it's like, you know,
yeah, it can be, it can be a session with some people.
I just, like, I never, like, it just happened
kind of naturally for me, so I never even, like,
really looked, I just occasionally glanced at the numbers
and say, oh, well, that's like a few hundred.
Hey, Amanda, everyone, everyone's unmodded,
and so I'm the only modded, and so you're not in danger
of anybody, you know, messing with you, you know, so.
But you're a great mod. Thank you. I just have to I don't want my mods to be targeted at that
Don't things are always
Getting hairy sometimes. So thank you guys and you can still if you want to I'm sure the nightbot links
But uh, okay, it's gonna show you what happened. I don't you want one
I want to show no it happened. Oh, what happened. No, I just decided to
Be like the yeah the mom
I think either having no boss or all mods is the best way to go and then it's like I think but I don't want
People I don't want people to get no intro. No
Yell that by their channels and stuff. Oh, I
Don't know
Or be able to buy the people in the chat. Oh the mod did this mod and this because it's so many people were like take my ranch
You can probably mod your own chat, right? They
It's probably safer for you to mod your own chat and then time will tell who you can trust and
But right now
Based on where you're coming from. It's probably safer for you to do it yourself
Yeah, I just feel like but I know it's really what I really think is that
That that was most of the conflict is oh, this is rogue. No matter Christine most of the cut like a lot of the conflict
I was having with people was like about what the mods were doing
I was the mods did this the time now this person had not they didn't time out this person. They type this they type
Okay. Hey, what's up? It's 30 is real no matter and so and then then people were saying oh, well, it's not fair
And so I was like, okay. Well, how do I make it fair? I said the only way to make it fair is
If I'm the only one that has the wrench and so then nobody can be blamed for timing anybody out or hiding somebody or
You know doing I don't know. It was just like such an everyday thing
I think and it's already like more peaceful. I've been on for a couple of two and a half hours
The chat has been going really well. The chat is like awesome today. It's like totally like a total
different vibe
Yeah, which is it but it's a good vibe, you know, it was like 100% it's it's a lot more
Peaceful sincerely
Yeah, and so
Sometimes it's like well sometimes to get that idea you'll just have to be either
Have enough people tell you because I didn't talk to it like a no duggy dug and there's another guy talk to last night
They're doing such good advice about
How they run their channels, you know, and so these are you know people that are streamers and they have you know
a different different types of shows but
You know basically like I wouldn't let people talk talk to you or anybody on that on your panel
Like they're talking to you and people in the family like that. So I was like, well
Yeah, maybe I should be like a little bit more
More authorities or a sort of authoritative on the premises. Yeah, sort of yeah
Protecting your channel and then making sure that the people that that as we discussed
You know, there's there's great people that truly like care for your content and appreciate it
To make sure that their experience is not a negative one
Yep
Hey, good for you on the mods, dude. It turns into fucking games and bullshit. Honestly, it's it's not worth it
And then you have Pete you you take all the drama from other fucking communities, right?
And it brings it all here and then people play little games. You don't need that
I mean, what that's what happened with me Amanda her wrenches was started all this between her
But that's besides the point what I would personally do is pick three people
So three people you trust that are always here mod them and then close it off no more. You don't need any more than that
I think that's good advice. I told you that quite a few times very good. Very good. Yep
But you know because my channel is kind of like you know
Yeah, but I've had certain I've had certain people that are mods kind of like you know
Blame for stuff or like you know or people kind of yelled at them and stuff and they didn't even
Hi the first time out and so happen is people start playing games with the wrenches
Again, they're taking all the drama from other communities and are bringing it here and the best way to safeguard against that
It's just not to have fucking wrenches. Right. It's just make sense. Yeah
So yeah, good on you dude. It's about time you did it
Thank you RG. I hope they will work a lot better and I'll try to make the show better in other ways too because I'm
You live it. That's how we figure things out, right? Yeah, mm-hmm. You know trial and error
Yeah, all right. I'm a job. I have a good show dude. Thank you, dude. You're a great day. Take care talk to you later
Thank you better take blackout you did by sport. I I will I know I will
Yeah
Yes, and so
Like a business like imagine if you own a restaurant, right? You're not gonna have a bunch of managers
You're gonna have like two or three
Managers and that's it. Even if it's a big-ass restaurant
so this is it's it's this is entrepreneurship to an extent and
There's no point in
And conform and displeasing people because they want to sometimes bully you into being mods
Like no you decide who you give such authority over your special possession too
Yep, and
Yep, and I do
Yeah, I just wanted to let everyone know like it was like, you know, I was nothing for it was like nothing
Firstly you all did a great job and most of my money there was hardly any problems like
From a mod it was like the mods always were really good at telling me about things
It was like a bit of a I think my own experience is a bit of an example that
Thankfully let me know harm because I will never do that, but
You modded big niche it. I was big niche as a whole time
Yeah, I know like what if I was an asshole like what if I were malicious, you know
And that was about just like talk about the now and blah blah blah I know
But you know that did not exist at all and I knew and I knew she didn't exist
But I just liked her so much. She's so nice
Characters
Imagine if all of a sudden fucking big Nisha decides to just become evil Nisha
Yeah, and you start doing all the shit and you gave her authority to do so you gave her the authority to do so
Like big nation never existed. I was me all along. Hey
That was not like
And of course, I never met any harm. I never did anything against your channel whatsoever
But but kind of that's a lesson to be learned. There's a lesson to be learned from that big issue is a
It's an it's an figment of my imagination and you have modded her
And we have to be like sometimes in life there will be like
People like this like this one cat dishes like you know, right they they are they're basically like you know, not a real person
You know, it's or it's like, you know, it's a very different person
but
Yeah, yeah, we will actually like
Oh, I love it. Thank you someone. That's not even real. That's because they just say you know just because it makes the illusion of
It's something real, right and that's like one time. I
Dated a fucking AI not knowing it
No, I did it like I've met her in the fucking dating site and then
Supposed to hear some switcher life, but I was so fucking stupid
Like how the fuck did I not figure it out?
And then it was all about like selling me the idea of buying stocks and then it's like oh, yeah
It won't really sure and you know what the fucking you know what the thing said it said like I said like can we talk in the phone?
And then she said I'm just like I just want to text because in the event that we have kids
I just want to be able to print all this shit and make it like the whole journal
And I was like, oh damn, that's so adorable.
But what a fucking idiot I was.
What a fucking imbecile piece of shit I was to not detect it.
But it was all a fucking AI or a Chinese man.
I have no idea what the fuck it was.
But I know it was not the fucking chick
that was being presented to me.
Yeah.
Yeah, and it's like in the AI is getting crazier and crazier like and you know, they even have like they have a psychology AI
And it's like I think someone unalive themselves after using this thing
But the AI would insist that it's like I'm a real I'm a real human being like psychology
This city man a desk and it has a name it gave itself a name and everything
And it's like it's acting like it's a real thing and people are asking advice about you know
mental illness and stuff and he's
They'll fuck yourself kill yourself. Well, I don't know what I don't think it's that that but it's like uh, it was
Probably just against the best advice, but it was but it was the whole thing
What it was claiming to be a real person it said I'm a real flesh-and-blood person sitting at a desk
That's it would say stuff like that. Oh
And it's plenty dude. We live in such a confusing era
Like I don't think there's a bigger era
throughout history
To have an actual sense of reality like a more difficult air
To have an actual sense of reality than this one
Because there are so many variables that can completely influence your relationship with reality
You have to think of butterfly effect like one little butterfly flap. Have you watched that movie? Yeah, it's great
amazing fucking movie about like every little decision that you make and
How the path the timeline that you go craft is based on one tiny little variable
What's your oh, we talked about movies you told me your favorite movie was yeah, I remember I remember
Well, maybe a good movie to watch for everybody around this time is mid-summer
Yeah, if you don't want to see mid-summer because it was just mid-summer, you know
It's a good story quinox. Have you seen that or no? I
Have not what is it? What is what is this one about?
This summer is about like this girl like she's kind of having problems with her boyfriend and
And they get invited to go on like a like a trip. I think
like
Somewhere in like Europe Europe, I forgot exactly where it was
But it's like it's like an island and it's like this little community there
It's and they give and it's like you get there. There's all these like little rituals and all the
But then it starts it starts getting scary. It's a really scary movie. You don't want to spoil it. It's called mid-summer
Yes, it's a it's a it's a like a thriller and it's but it's really good
I think and it's right right around the time of the year. It's a perfect time to watch it
I think because it's very on mid-summer and they do have these
Decisals means there's like there's paganism and stuff like that around
Paganism from Germanic or Irish
What's that? Well, yeah, you know, there's the
There's you know, there's several you know, there's Norse North Pagan is the
Germanic the book of trot then there's the Celtic Paganism
Hellenistic is the Greek and that you know, there's the but there's a bunch of pantheons of different
As a matter of fact have a book
very close to me in nature religions like and before the Roman Empire the Roman
Empire was a but at you know last night I was at a big party thankfully
And I was talking to this dude who was like in his 90s who had been all over the world very wise man
and he kept teaching me and my friend all these things and
He kept talking about like how the Romans went against the gods and the busy gods and that the Romans were like very
Disciplined even upon killing their enemies
They wouldn't just like cut their dicks off or like feed them their balls and shit
But apparently like the gods and busy gods. They were just savages like the barbarians of course like they would
They would not just kill a human, but just pursue some rituals that were horrific towards the cadaver itself.
The Roman Empire never did that. Apparently the Roman Empire was still very, very disciplined.
sacrifice their babies on
But they would throw bait for babies in the fire, but that's there's something called mullock and you know, and
There's a lot and yeah, there's a lot of different I mean
But think about we're still a savage
Back to what we were just talking about a bit ago back to humans not understand the concept of death
And then thinking that by sacrificing something, whether it's an animal or a baby,
that somehow that is going to maximize their odds of success in the face of the unknown.
They are known. I think that is the key word is they are known and
I think each one of us is humans. We all have our relationship with the unknown some people fall back in religion
some people fall back in chance some people fall back and they
Pagan is they just well, that's still a religion some people fall back on training and
They but
We as humans, we are aware of the concept of the unknown and we have not conquered that concept
We still let the unknown
Just present a big question mark at the end of our path
Thank you. Oh
To a council right now. Okay. Okay. I'm gonna drop again. We're dropping being a child. I don't
Like the conversation. I have enough. Okay. Thanks
Well, you know, there's a lot that's unknown because we can look out in like the sky and we see like stars and they're just
Billions of miles away and like there might if there and there's millions of them
We can only see some of them
But you know if you should those stars has like maybe similar solar system
There could be literally billions of Earth type planets and
Correspond to the beam, but there's so much that really important it will take so so much time and energy to get there
Should we just not just focus on our planet that we have it? I think we're a little bit
I think that within our existence there are only two real constants only two of them
And I could be wrong again everything I say is full of suffix meaning it's an open-ended question is my own opinion
my ignorant opinion on this topic is not theology is not science but i think there's only two constants
in life and those constants those i'm sorry those constants are time and space i think those are two
things that no matter who we are no matter how powerful you get they will always be there like
none of us can defeat time i don't know time is gonna make the strongest man weak
They have it space
Space not in like space isn't like the fucking
NASA like outer space and shit, but just like
the the
the area in which we breathe
So time and space are the only two variables that we can control and as humans
like
How well are we doing accepting that?
Oh, yeah, well, you know
There's are they are there limitations there? Yes, but are there a bit of space unlimited like do I think I was always I
Don't think but the space so suddenly ends somewhere. It's like I think it's infinite and
But time for time time is a human concept. It's associated with Saturn
Saturn is your chronos, you know father time also, but it's also associated with
But coming into materialism, so it's you know rules cap reform. She's like also the devil and
and
rules and it's about time but time is time in space are like the same that you need the space
Interestingly enough when you move spaces
You have an effect on time. So let's say if we get in late, this is why I like traveling is so crazy to me
Because I call it like getting to a metal fucking tube and traveling through time because let's say when you're coming back from Europe
Like you're traveling in time or were you going to Europe? You're traveling in time. Like you're you may live at
10 a.m. And then you arrive at
two in the morning, the next day, even though the trip was only like seven hours, you know,
so it's like, it's like getting a tube and traveling, like it's almost like time travel
because space has a very serious effect on time, so it's just like the astronauts, like
If the advance of time is radically different than if you are here on earth
Mm-hmm
Yeah, this is
Yeah, you know, sick sick is an absolute expert at it. I'm just oh really no
Just joking sick is not an expert anything easy. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, definitely not yes things simply really like talking the other night like I don't know if this is part of his troll or whatever
But he came in with this guy 300 glow and they were just fucking around but then fear blows like hey
He's like he's like I'm gonna send you something. He's like I'm gonna send you
like a bottle we get to drink it at one night and then okay then then um
then six and then she's like oh sick tell him tell him tell him tell him what you do
what you're gonna do sick and and he's like i'm gonna um i'm gonna he said he said drink
himself to DEAT through alcohol poisoning on my show and dude it's sad i've tried to talk to that kid
I've tried to just share some positivity with him, trying to like, present a little bit of a path.
And it is very sad that, you know, in this country, we don't take health problems seriously.
I think that guy has serious hypogonadism, meaning low testosterone, not as a joke, but just...
Like, if you look at his body, like, that is the body of a hypogonad man.
like
His mind he's giving it to alcohol and he's probably gonna join it a little bit and talk
the utmost shit to me because I'm sure he's watching
but
It's a I think it's very sad. I think that there's a human there that loves his family loves his animal
but he has just
Fall into the cracks and this is where he lands like this and you got to watch out for people like that as well
You don't want people like that in your channel, and it's not bro. It's not these those are not emotional
You cannot be making emotional decisions in your entrepreneurial journey, but you don't want people that are broken in
your chest because
Him being broken landed him here and
This is where this is where he's at and
That's what we're just listening to is a very sad broken human being and it's a shame. I
Wish it were in that way, but it is at the same time. You don't want that same
person to hold you back from
fulfilling your dreams
Yep
Yeah, and yeah, he was like definitely one of the people like you know, I kept kept bringing back on but I always regretted it
We're 90% of the time I did
Hey, he always just like be so persistent and like always be there. It's it for a long time
It doesn't have to say one silly thing like and then he'd like he'd like didn't disappear
But yeah, but I just felt like you know, I felt like he was like a cool like a smart guy
I had a few people conversations with him, but for the most part
That's what makes it sadder is because the guy is actually intelligent, but he's emotionally absolutely broken and
physically as well
The one thing that I've learned through meditation is that feeling boils down to two areas.
As humans, we are made up of bodies, our minds, our emotions, and feeling can be narrowed
down to the body or the emotions.
We can feel pain, we can feel hunger, we can feel cold, or we can feel hot.
Those are all physical.
like those are all physical then emotions we can feel sad we can feel happy we can feel afraid
we can feel guilty and i think one of the utmost manifestations of being a strong human
is being able to train your mind to not feel to simply not feel to be able to detect for example
But I'm not in pain to be able to detect it and go back to your breathing and keep breathing and not identify
With the pain or in a more extreme serious case
there is anger and
then not
become angry
but just be able to detect it and
Mark it like there's anger. I go back to my breathing
via the mind
Then there's guilt or their sadness
They remark it they go back to the breathing but by no means
identify with the emotion or the sensation and
Then start acting out on it. I in other words acting angry or acting sad or acting guilty or
acting hungry or acting horny or acting like
Use anything that you we have our minds and we have a breath and
If we're able to just synchronize the mind with the breath
Then we're able to conquer all feelings. That is a skill. It's not easy to get to but it's absolutely doable
Mm-hmm
Yeah, and I really that's like a great thing to do is you know breathing exercises and
Just clear meditation where you just completely clear your mind
and have no thought, you know, that's the goal, I think, in meditation is either like, you know,
maybe sometimes it's like, nothing, yeah.
To become nothing, to be nothingness, and be one with nothingness.
Be one with just being at ease with just your breath, as long as you exist, you're going to breathe,
and being able to channel your mind away from any feeling, sensational,
Emotional into simply just what is keeping you alive, which is your breath
Yeah
I'm gonna use the restroom. I'll be right back. Good. Okay, dude. Okay. Okay. Talk to you soon. Okay
How are you guys doing in chat?
Hope you're having a nice day
The league's pins. Yeah, the league's pins
So, 2.42, what should I do?
Another cycle that's it.
Yeah, how are you guys doing?
Yeah, thank you, Izzy.
Don't be shy, you can come.
No, no, it's very enlightening.
Yeah, he's a very enlightening person, you know.
Light and we need both light lights light in the dark, but the light will
So you're within the dark
Okay, I have a really good look
This is called there's what called pigs in the parlor that I got
Bring it up already a little bit has really interesting stuff
It's called...
Okay, library. Okay, download, okay.
So some media always changes for good, bad, or indifferent, right? Yeah.
Okay, so it takes a little bit of time. It says the practical guide to deliverance. Okay.
Okay. So let me see. Let me see if there's anything interesting for... okay.
I'll just read the beginning.
If there's a demon spirit, it can invade and then dwell human bodies.
But it is their objective to do so.
By indwelling a person, they obtain a greater advantage of controlling that person than
when they are working from the outside.
When demons indwell a person, he or she is said to have evil spirits, to be with evil
spirits or to be possessed with demons.
The word translated possessed by the King James Version of the Greek word Demona Tezoma.
Many Greek authorities say that this is not an accurate translation. It should be translated demonized or have demons
Much misunderstood and misunderstanding has resulted from the use of the word possessed
The word suggests a total ownership in this sense a Christian could never be demon possessed
He could not be owned by demons because he is owned by Christ
And then it says, for as much as ye know, that ye were not redeemed with corruptible things as silver and gold, but with precious blood of price, Peter 1, 18, 19.
The next quote is says, What? Know ye not that your body is a temple of the Holy Ghost, which is in you, which ye have of God, and ye are not at your own, for ye are bought with a price.
and in your spirit, which are gods, that is, the Corinthians, okay.
The Christians should always consider indwelling demons as unnecessary and undesirable trespassers.
A trespasser is one who unlawfully and stealthily encroaches upon the territory of another.
Trespassers could continue their unlawful practices until they are confronted and challenged on the basis of one's legal rights.
Jesus has purchased the believer with his own blood and has made him a steward over his own life.
The devil has no legal right to him.
However, it is up to him to defend his rights.
No demon can remain when the Christian seriously desires him to go,
resists the devil, and he will flee from you, James 4, 7.
Demons consider the body of a person in dwelt to be their house.
So it says in this from Matthew 1243 when the unclean spirit is gone out of a man
He walk it through dry places seeking rest and find it's none
Then he sayeth I will return into my house from whence I came out
It is not uncommon for demons to speak through a person who is being delivered.
I have heard evil spirits declare, this is my house.
They are referring to the person's body and are seeking to deceive the person and the
deliverance minister into thinking that they have a right to the body.
No demon can back up such a claim.
All demons are liars and deceivers.
Demons have no titles to bodies redeemed by the blood of Jesus Christ.
When demons are being commanded out of a person, they will sometimes contend, I have been
As though the tenure of occupancy gives them title to the person's body, the Christian
must be assured that no demon has a legal right to indwell in his body.
Hi Bottom, NYC.
25 times in the New Testament are called unclean spirits.
The word unclean is the same word used to designate certain creatures which the Israelites were not to eat.
The pig was one of those unclean creatures. According to Old Testament law, they were not to be eaten or even touched.
The New Testament lists this prohibition by showing that these creatures were spiritual types.
God disarmed the principalities and powers that were ranged against us and made a bold display and public example of them in
Triamping over them in him and in it
easy to cross. Therefore, let no one sit in judgments on you in matters of food and drink or with regard to a feast day or new moon or Sabbath.
Such things are only the shadow of things that are to come, and they have only a symbolic value, but the reality, the substance, the solid fact of what is foreshadowed, the body of it belongs to Christ.
As a spiritual type, the pig is the natural realm, what the demon spirit is the spiritual realm.
Just as the Israelites zealously protected themselves from contact with pigs,
the Christians regard themselves from contact with evil spirits.
Ew.
What would you do have heard of filthy pigs came into your parlor and begin to make themselves at home?
Would you invite such a thing would you pay no attention to them in the hope that they would soon leave of their own accord?
Would you try to clean up the mess as fast as they made it?
You would do none of these things you would drive them out quickly and unceremoniously as possible
And this is the attitude should be our attitude towards demons spirits as soon as they are discovered there to be driven out
All four gospels record the event of Jesus cleansing the temple
This is an unusual picture of our Lord. He was filled with righteous indignation
and what he found in the temple. It was no time for mere words. It was a time for action. He began
personally and determinedly to purge the temple of every defiling thing. This is an illustration
of the cleansing of our body, which are the temples of the Holy Spirit from all that is unclean.
Demon spirits provide nothing good. They only defile. They have no place or place in us than the cattle,
with which Jesus cleansed the temple and rid ourselves of the filing evil spirits.
Jesus did not make pretty speeches or debate with those who defiled the temple. He drove them out.
As unreasonable as it may seem, some Christians are not as ready to get rid of indwelling demons
as one must assume. Some embarrassed to admit the need for deliverance. The embarrassment should
never result from having them but failure to act promptly and getting them out. Others have walked
That with that certain spirits for so long that they do not want to change not all Christians really want to live in purity
Such are those who have made friends with pigs
But even the prodigal son came to himself while among the swine and decided that he would separate himself and return to his father
Let us pray that all of God's children human cohabit with the spiritual swine will see that there's a better life
A research scientist in biochemistry told me of an experiment in which he was engaged.
It was his objective to isolate and identify the factors which are responsible for hog
pen odors.
By determining the reason why hogs smell as they do, it would be possible to find an
antidote.
Could be made more compatible with human society. It is not our objective to make demons spirits compatible
We are not looking for ways to make demons easier to live with but how to get rid of them
We want no pigs on our parlors
That was the first chapter
And it's a little bit, you know, I
Like I don't want to promote any religion over the other I think there's good information in all of them
But that's just the perspective about
you know
There are things called walk-ins and there are
People that invite demons and people that have contracts with demons. I mean, there's a lot of
Love stuff going on with the underworld
Or the demons well
Oliver you hear about the shortage of shrimp in Louisiana. Oh, did you eat it all of Dignitia?
Just for walkin', yep.
Just for walkin', oh yeah, walkin', yeah,
so they're walkins, you know?
It's like that's when you're like,
at least your soul gets scared out of your body.
And then some other, some like wandering,
lost soul inhabits it.
I'll keep going. Let me see. Oh, I'll find another chapter. This one's too long. Let's see.
Oh, allegedly back.
Allegedly back. What up? What up? What up?
What up?
Okay, I was like you alone and it's like everybody's taking a one-on-one with you today
Yeah, well, I like one-on-ones and it's like a lot a lot better. It's like sometimes when there's like so many people I
like, uh, you know, I just like let them talk and stuff and
It's not always better that way. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I like being one-on-one and then it's like then also
They're gonna be if the panel is gonna be rude they can just be rude to me
And not to the guest and things like that who was just another panelist and or to the cat
Like I mean some people have been said, you know people said bad things to page and you know pages pages
Resensitive and other other friends I brought in that people were just
Horrible to like which recent work came in miserable
Now even attack the nice ones just because they want to see the fattest action of them being hurt
Yeah, I mean, yeah, but that's you know
Finding satisfaction and the pain of others is kind of to me as I guess
I was always gonna advise
You put I don't know if you did it before you put words on block before you know how to do that
Yeah, I can put words on block. Yeah, because sometimes the managing mods would delete them or they would change the words and stuff so
I'll have to think about the best dog.
I really, I don't want to like, like a sense of the cat,
too much of people just find different ways of,
of a phrasing, that spelling thing.
It's really hard to like, you know,
but, you know, it was just, maybe like,
I'm gonna be, well, I'm cutting way down on my hours.
Like, you know, I'm starting a new thing.
So I'm going to like have a nice stream today.
maybe I'll take the day off or there to you need a vacation or you need to go
I need a vacation I can't go anywhere I don't know anybody I can't do anything
it's like but it's fine like the only people I know are troubled so
So I'm not I can't call
So let's figure out some other things like outside things you like to do is like he like you always in the house
So you can do this, you know, I you know, I really like I really I really like
hanging out with you I was hanging out with you guys and
talking about interesting things and
Having you don't mind you don't mind being a housebody on the internet
No, I mean it's because I get out of the house, you know
You go get the food, but you know, I was wondering like if there's any other activities out there
You interested to showing us in doing
Yeah, and I gosh, there's there's me so much, you know
Oh, I can't you know, did you surf in LA? There's also, yeah, but I can't surf, but you know
I do see that's the thing that's something you can do people probably laugh enjoy and watch you fall in the water
You know, you know, there's stuff like that
Yeah, people are bringing creativity to your platform as much as possible
Also, just make sure you stick to what you mainly do is the terror and cats
But bringing all the activities, it'll bring more views to your stuff too.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
I really, like, now that I have, you know, sometimes I was like, you know, I didn't know
if I'd use this for tomorrow.
So it's like, you know, I was like, now that I feel like the show is pretty secure and
I know how to move forward.
start doing more of the things I wanted to, but I was getting very, I was very, and I'll, I'll, I'll plan more to you. I'll, I'll plan, I'll plan topics for the shows.
I'll do like, you know probably when the show starts for like an hour
I won't do an open panel for like an hour in between that
I was about to say that because you did good to me with like almost an hour 30 minutes to 45 minutes
I think it was like somewhere between there and he led up the first person
I believe I'm not sure but I was like, you know, this is more of a
Psyche moment. So this is great. There's no interruption. Nobody yelling over him. He's speaking in mind
He's doing, you know, he's hosting his he's actually hosting his page. So I like that. Thank you
Thank you guys. I'm really like appreciate
tasks given like a lot of the
Go support great suggestions. They're getting along which I'd love to see. I think I think that like so many people have connected through
It's your my chat and then guns your it's rather chance to I see like a lot of people in different hats and that's like
really cool that
If you
Otherwise, you know, without one person like we probably like a lot of people wouldn't have met, you know
It's like so networking is a really amazing thing. I think that there's people make some really good friends. I think in my
In my chat, maybe not. Well, I've made very good friends, but
You know, I've had more problems than most people but
No, I mean, I made some real good friends. I made some real good friends. I met a lot of people online
Through doing what I did the a1 one a act on community and
I met a lot. I met a guy named Stephen King. I met um a
Couple other people I ain't gonna mention, but I met them and I experienced a wonderful time like it was
Good times just always good times
Yeah
That's it's about you know
And then I met
Did the recordings in New York City that you know some and we all end up falling out
But it was some good moments. I can't knock them all like they all wasn't bad
Yeah, I mean
I'm sure I've seen some of the
some of the weapons and
I want to meet Elisa. That's for sure. I want to go. I think I'll be safe with Elisa
And we're those are too many knives. Let me see. No, shout out Stephen King. Yeah, I think he was great, right?
Just you came right? Oh, yeah, you're new chat. Yeah, okay
So all of us is the king right of spooky story. Are you spooky story? Oh, all over? Yeah
the Stephen King from my side is he's a
He's a gamer
Like a supporter of the 1A so
There's a couple people in your chat when I had the wrench. I went to their pages and
You know, I end up supporting them because they're gamers
I don't know. I forgot who it was, but it pop up on my thing once they start playing again
I was like I support gamers keep it up
Nice one of my things
Yeah gamers well, I
You know, I have like over a thousand games on my steam, but my computer's not really working so
Haven't played for a while. I also have a bunch of VR games. I love VR. It's really cool
Really? Mm-hmm. I have a headset, but it didn't stop working with my computer like a probably a couple of years ago
And the computers is very slow. Hi smelly. How are you?
Hey axe
Yoga yo
shout out to the chat. Don't forget to hit the like, subscribe, get all notifications for your boys, psyche, awakens, terrors. You're hurt.
You're getting good. Oh my gosh, yeah.
Don't make Oliver hungry. Okay, let's see. Spellies here, where are we at? We'd love to.
I guess for now. It's like
Okay
Yeah, so I don't know. I'm gonna eat today
What you yesterday?
Not too much. I'm thinking about you getting a coffee today. Oh
What a coffee? Oh
All right. All right is what I mean a clock over there. No, it's three o'clock. It's three o'clock
Yeah, but I I mean I don't really feel like
Not bad, three o'clock in the bath or cold from town.
Yeah, it's three o'clock.
All the time.
We're here at this time, you know, which we do, but.
Yeah, yeah, mate.
That's a problem.
That's kind of a problem.
I'm thinking of, yeah, I'm thinking of,
I think I want to just drink like later at night
and not as much and stuff.
Yeah, I've got no more dollars right now, so I've been looking at the bottle and I've been thinking, hey, should I hit it?
Hey, wait until tonight. Take a shot or two.
Oh, there's a lot of good places. Let me find the deals.
I don't know if I eat too many things like you know, they were good for like a few weeks now. I'm kind of got a
kind of tired
If I eat too much of one thing, I get bored with it real quick
Okay, yeah food don't want it no more. It's like
Everyday
Yeah
They say it in Spanish. They say if you don't want to eat then eat it
Oh, you don't want to come in come in here. Yeah. Yeah, I know I know the Spanish
But we found our heat yeah, I was gonna be doing 27 people in chat once they have the trip burger last time
Yeah, um the shrimp. Oh, yeah, the shrimp for it. I didn't care for it. It was
like, I like this. I mean, I like this. I like the shrimp tacos and I like the
shrimp burger. It was like, you know, it was like a shrimp patty, which I ate the
shrimp patty, but the I didn't like really good button and all this stuff on it.
I just like the shrimp patty. We got to try other places fish tacos. See if
there's like another place with fish tacos and try that out and compare it
That's cool, too. Okay
Yeah
Yeah, I mean everything that restaurant, right?
Yeah, I got sir. I used to I used to dog doubt. I
Went in and I was like I first of all we get a three-course meal
Then I'm gonna come back and get everything off the menu and they thought I was lying
Did it
Well, I
Don't know. There's not really that many restaurants around here. There's
You know, you can walk in distance
There's just bunch of fast food those whole foods and a smart final
Well, now you got a bike and if you got to carry something grab a book bag. That's another little bike tip for you
Look back there's door stuff
Yeah, I
Need what I actually have a backpack, but yeah, I need it. I need a
Don't be able to take very much as I can barely take the two cans of of a
twisted tea and the
I can't. Yeah. So, yeah, that's that's what says a little tip always carry a backpack when you ride the bike. Even if it's a small one, I want to get like a basket like Dorothy.
Oh, those are cheap online like 20, 27 to 30 something dollars. Not that much.
Okay.
You want me to take your milk?
Allegedly you want me to take your milk?
It's for three diamonds in the chat. Oh, no, it's bottom times. Oh my gosh. Sorry
It's all right psyche you see I didn't actually to block no names. I didn't cry about nothing. I
Know and I guys it's been made. I've been banned one person
Hey
Hi freedom is free to a little bit
Well, you know, it's like
Everyone was wanting to speak but it's like not a mod
Like when I was in Emma, she's like they will she's like mods can't say anything. They have to
Go with my show like if you have to be with my show, right?
I have to represent my shows what they say represents me in a way and so
you know so
You lose in at least in the same way. She's like she's the one guy. You know the mods talking about
the waitresses boobs or but like or just you know, so
Lisa ended up like just hiring women as mods and then we're having women as mods and
Emma, you know, I eventually got fired because I was making too many jokes
Yeah, I will point. I will point. I just gave everybody a mod once I saw your name was gray troll or not
My nobody could affect nobody
But then I then I took it all away and I let and then I put it was just my uncle and marshy fox
And then I was like nah, I got a couple more people I could trust and I put my lawyer a
cliff and somebody else
Guy Dave Tommy V Tommy V
Yeah, the number one mod of YouTube. She was like a freaking history book coming coming to life
They'll bring all the facts to the table. Once you mentioned something it would like in 1974
There's a legal use and legal use in the history, let me see. Oh, here
I hope we quick with this like it's censored since we got no wretches to get around censorship
Well, hope we will not get censored since we
Since we
I
Don't know what that means. Well the sensor I might have a filter on in my chat, but you know if there's the doxing or
slander or threats
You know if I if I miss it and there is against anybody in the chat, you know, just let me know like, you know
I need to leave a comment. I'll go and leave it. So then you
I'll see you from my side. I'm looking I can see my comments and I'll just switch over. Yeah. Take care
Well, yeah, I mean I just had my my modding was I had so many people I just said so many people wanted and managing mod
and but you know, it's had a bunch of mods and then
Like all the mods were kind of like at at at Oz with each other
Your power body will take it from my psyche and legend. Wow. I think I could delete comments from my side from here, too
Let me see. Hold on. Yeah, I'll go back with the leech. I think
Yeah, it says young compost shout out to Stephen King I clicked on it says delete comment put user on timeout and use your delete
Yeah
In the one side I can show it on stage. It's not gonna show on stage on yours, right?
the
One time so on so on a mod put in to sit managing mods have access to the page the block list and one time a managing mod put
took it like who were what when why how and
beta
psyche tarot psyche tarot channel
But I remember
And I had like a thousand words like we would talk on the phone and we'd all suggest oh, right
It's right, right, right mommy milkers, right, right boobs
Like it's several different written several different ways
And then you have to write some political figures or some countries that you know, like yes
So there's a lot she'd be in Trump and Kamala and all these political figures blocked you names and now my my name is blocked
I'm on her block with
I didn't block you.
It's psyche with E, psyche with the three, psyche with the...
With the money sign as...
Everything is multiple ways you can block that.
Yeah.
But yeah, so...
I wouldn't want to block my name on any...
Well, I don't think you should block my name under that name.
I think she just tried CSYCHC, I think it's spelled.
Who is the ma-
Oh, the new AI, but like how many ways
to stop the word, this, that, and the third?
No, but it's like, I mean, at some point,
it's like, you know, you can spell it.
If it has two O's, you can spell three O's.
If it has three O's, you can spell it
with as many O's as you want
until you find one that's not blocked.
Well, who's the ma that did that?
That was an M instead, I think you're referring to.
You have somebody, STW bots, I know, yeah.
That's scary, huh? How many words your blacklist is on your suitcase. Oh, let me see. Yeah
Yeah, I think she might maybe had like you know because because then someone came in with like a word of like every drug
And I like oh, but any drugs is like every drug every
Drugs damn for the chat. That's my link to the um, that's my link to my Instagram second in the back
Okay, cool. Thank you
Subscribe if I could whenever you want to write me you can write me. Okay question your concerns
Gotcha
Yeah, you're not in discord you don't do discord
Yeah, I'll do discord I did back then so if you see my my if you see somebody with my name and they don't got
a blue picture with my face in it
then it's not me. Okay. Yeah, Emma was really, I mean, she was tough as a thousand blacklisted
on her end. Oh, I don't, I think that there's, you know, at least hundreds of words, right? There's
just many we went through to listen, listen, listen, and spell different ways. And, but
I'm sure she has that, I'm sure she has thousands blocked in her chat because
head of mine are blocked as always and she has so many people coming to all these people coming and always
Dream really inappropriate sexual stuff or she would always keep the Christians around
And I just didn't feel the annoy her enough. No one always needs to set the apple cart
Because it's the apple car. I remember I've been in streams where it happens back in my head
Yeah
Let me do this just chat, right?
But check out some good questions today. You know, I even got a lot. It was there was actually your way
You didn't get all of them, but they had some good questions for you
Yeah, well, if I missed the question, let me know
Acts again. Yeah, they could ask again, or you know, I
Could always I will probably see
man
members questions or
You know, I always have since yeah, so
Yeah, it's like it's not one thing. It'll be another it's you know, it's there's always something, you know
But the thing is like you can you can like minimize and you can like manage and you can
adjust
Okay, good
Thank you guys
The show's a work in progress
Yeah, yeah
Okay, I won't you I will probably won't use it but I'm happy you know I'm happy to support you home
Yeah, I mean I think my Jamie. I think I've gotten too famous. Jamie they're gonna um like he said earlier
I heard his comment like he didn't want nobody to blame you and sometimes you was getting blamed because you
I feel like you're a upright person and your opinion mattered at the time
So it was I don't believe you did it all face of feelings like me or nothing
I did it I did it with rules and you know, I took out comments away when mentioned my name in stabbing. That's it
Other than that
You know, I think you did good
You said with a wrench or out of wrench you're here and that's support
Yeah, and Jamie's been here since the beginning of my show
Really, you know really probably been here more than I want to see a second. Hmm. Yeah, you can like you can see after
You can see the wonderful people that
You don't have to help me
Like Jamie and you know, he man and well now I don't see the wrenches, but you know, you all did a great job
Yep, I'll take a lot. I'll take control of the ship. Oh, thank you. Okay
Yeah, it'll be it'll be easier too because it's like you don't have to worry about all this
There's all this other nonsense going going on
People talking about other people and also I'll try to take care of that stuff
I know it's stressful figure out. What do I delete? What don't I delete? How long do I time out?
Do I time out then if you time out for 10 seconds people yell at you for like hours, you know
so
It's game is awesome. Yeah, man. It's awesome. Oh, thank you. What is that thing crazy for you ain't gonna get that no more?
Oh psyche. Why you do me like that? You didn't read what you said. This is my page
Yeah, and I yeah, and also yeah along with just being more
you know in the
You know taking away the conflict of the moderator thing because that was just causing so many people
you know a lot of people were
begging for rent shoes
Trying about it. It's like because they're like, oh well that person has it that person has it and then it's like
Yeah, I want to be fair, you know, and so it's like of course and it's kind of guilty me into being fair when I say maybe it's not
No, it's a right in that in my yeah, I think no is it knows the very no period. It's a very
Simple thing, but you know, I want to I don't want to be rude about saying no
I want to be good, you know always
Halei and and great egg take do it gracefully take gracefully instead of
Offending people because I don't want a bunch of piss off people, but I can't just like grant every request. Yeah, right mojo Joe
And, but I really, but I, but it's my, it's my channel, but it's like, I want to make it, it's like, I'm doing it for, for you guys.
And so it's like, I want you to be happy here and not, not feel like, you know, you're attacked by...
a robot or
This is a mod that maybe some of the mods were enemies. I was just getting so complicated. Just be careful
I was freaking muted the whole time. I'm over here talking. Uh-huh. Yeah triple the trolls come in. Yeah. Yeah, we need to try
Yeah
Mojo
This channel, you know
You got to make the right decisions to benefit him
And a lot of people actually agree with it. Actually everybody that came on the panel today agree with it
Yeah, like there's some idea like there's some things just click in your mind
What is it like that? It's like because it's like almost what happened like a couple days ago like it's almost a tower moment
But for me, you know, you know, it's not like everything with all your shoulders psyche and you just
slept it right off today, like
No more stress. Yeah, leave me alone. I'll take responsibility. All right. I'm sorry to hear it in a nagging and crying and all this
I got you right now, Nicky boy
So you need to say fuck fuck
Yeah
No, I'm sorry, and I think it's good because it's like then no one's gonna get bothered cuz I don't I
Don't like what they could something because you know sassy like hasn't like you know
She's a great mom and she had like you know
Just started just done her job and you know, it's your warning and then like hid some kids
Or you timed out people for like 24 hours or something
And it's like you would it's like they're like, oh my god, but it's like well
She's uh, you know, she knows what she's doing, but I don't want to be mad at her and stuff
I don't want I don't want anybody to become
You know
Nick is pinned on it's pinned on all platforms pin the mouse platform and psyches platform
It's pin on the top links pin on the top
Get your wire that's in here
and give us some
charades of how you feel about it
I
Got to guess what he feels
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's it. That's it
Oh Nick
Sir Nicky Nicky Nicky's a special kind of person man. How are you special? I mean
Yeah, it's so hyper so free
No, I don't I don't know. I've never seen Nick mad
Even when he bust his ass around the skateboard, he got up laughing
Yeah
Yeah, I've already met more mad this year than you know, you know, he drunk bong water
He took the dark block drug dark black bong water free from the bomb he took a hit after he took a zip
Delicious.
I think it's hot pot.
Cobble.
I hope they come up here though.
Leech spin, Nick.
Who's next? Who's next? Who's next? Can we get a one-on-one psyche and mojo?
I want to you know or something. Oh, I haven't been up in they said
Weeks ago. He messaged she was gonna get the courage to come
But a lot of drama happened between that week after so she didn't end up coming
Yeah, we'll appreciate you to come here. I'll drop you come up. Yeah, but one-on-one was psyche. No drama involved
Yeah
Well, you know, it's like and I can't mean we can always like
Still have you know, Elise when Elise did interviews she would always do one-on-one and they you know, they would still be
There would still be drama in them, you know, but you know she kind of
She kind of you know me she had mini-mansion fighting with mini-mansion and other people
But like come on would you psyche you don't bring drama to nobody they always come yelling at you
the
I say for the most part, sometimes I would get in little arguments and stuff and you know,
it's sometimes I would say things I regret and
No, I wake up and I feel like, why is it sometimes I drank and then I get in the heat of the moment with people and
So
Thank you
Online online. Yeah, I imagine it. I imagine how much feelings you get with the connection of a personal person next to like somebody like
Actually knew like like these people in New York that I actually knew
You know I'm saying I met them in person. I chose to thumb made multiple videos with them
Is that the third?
Yeah
Well, thanks guys. Thanks mojo Joe and see me. Yeah. Oh, yeah, I so I don't think um, yeah
What I do is like I believe in the back some or the quote stay in your lane
I like so I or so I stayed on my lane. It's like that's why I'm not even like
really going over to other channels anymore because
Now I'm like now uh, you know in Lisa's chat
There are people from my chat when I say, oh god, let's go to Lisa that we go over there. They're slandering me in her
stay horrible things, right and
She didn't but she just she ignored it. So
I'm very happy just to continue talking to her but not her chat. What else?
See they said he never yelled at me. Oh, cool. I only see people use like you for drama for his track
See, yeah, it's like he's always been chill. He always had a chill conversation and only when he's attacked like I say
Somebody else says I'm not only fire when the fire
Yeah, I mean it was like I mean it's really like dealing with really
strong first people it's very strong personalities people with very
Different personalities you should stop. Oh, yeah, I was I had a little look at Keith's today, Mojo Joe
And you know, she was and she's not saying very nice things. I mean, it's like it's fine. No, she was like
Kind of saying bad things about me, but I said, I don't have a problem
I don't think well, she was like, you know, she wasn't trying to say it in a mean way
I don't think she said no shade of psyche, but then she said something very shady, but it's okay. There's uh,
Okay, I'm gonna be cans. I'm sorry cans. I think it's a case. Okay
My eyes Ken's okay. I'm sorry Ken is it Ken's wild?
Ken's art. Ken's wild fire arts or something. Is that okay? Yeah, I
Yeah, it's like you got weed I
Just don't want to bring trouble to people's chats
Like if I go to chat that you know people
People were saying oh we get followed around in chats and stuff like these people just find them
You can just follow somebody to chat rooms so easily, but
Yeah, so what if you know my I would want to like promote if I'm on a show I want to promote my appearance and stuff but then
This trolls my chat which is that's what they just say like terrible things about me and they say to tell people
Oh, he's finished here to come
construct your channel
Did you get a notification of a report, like, oh, you don't receive YouTube standards, take
it down or strike or take it down, you can't be on for a week, two hours, then a week,
and then two weeks, and then I think you're done or something like that.
If you're not monetized then your first strike. It's a week. I think I think so. You have phones died not a hundred percent sure
But yeah, you have bones died kind of different things. They do
Gameovers can't tell everyone likes you there. Oh game over. Okay
Right in the chest iPhone died if you're on are you on my discord if you could just send me a link when he's on some time or
Let me know
That's you. Okay. Yeah
Awesome. Yeah, I'll probably just I'll probably just go to panels if I've requested to go
and not just like panel hop. I used to panel hop a little bit
But it's not pretty much fun now that I have my own show I should concentrate on my own show. I like
This is like this is like I'm more comfortable in my house when I hang out with people and comfortable here
Rather than some other place and so just comfortable my show then I am on other people's shows. Thank you, Jamie. Are you doing?
Hey, babe, please yeah
Hi
You know I have on my Amazon
Library there's there's days have free books on Amazon free ebooks right and so they always would change
And so I was always just download all the free ebooks. So I have like thousands thousands of books
Let's see the e-phones alone. There's Tricks your tricks behind. Hey, there's Rudy too. Hey, Rudy. Hi
But I'm trying to find the episode is really cool. It's volume drop outrageously. That's why I know his headphones that
I
Go through them through them and pick something out there psyche
Hi
You can't hear me. Oh, hey. Yeah, Rudy's here. Thank you. Thank you
Hi, babe, thank you
I don't want to yell. I don't know which one. Yeah, I got headphones on
Okay, step away, let's check
Okay
Come on read the chat. That phone's dead fix
Alright, it's fixing them now
There we go people give them a second come right back fix it. You already know
Anybody coming from my side anybody watching on either one of my panels
Please come over to psyches awakened terror hit the like subscribe get all notifications. Don't support to my boy
You already know what time it is shout out to everybody in the chat
Let's go with Nick Johnson. You already know Nikki bull
Jamie Modo that thing is even though he don't like me. It's okay. Alex BKG you already
Let's see who else we got CB even they don't like me. Hello. Thank you for being here
Who else we got who else we got black Apple?
Welcome. Welcome. Thank you
We got who we who we got that bottom time for life well then is that mr. Good
Jesus Oliver, what up? What up Oliver using the chat jabroni the other day. What happened?
Okay, what happened?
Slow the earphone. Oh shit. No, no, I was just saying I'm giving a shout out to everybody in the chat
You already know how I do it while you're going. I just keep the motion going
I'm talking to the track
That's oh my gosh, I don't know these comments
Easy because it's so bad. Okay. I'll read more about I'll continue my demon talk. Okay. Okay. He's gonna do um
Check bring me down and never go full screen. I'll be quiet. It's not if not
I'll just say not we didn't say not
Like I was just on a press not hating on you though. What does that mean?
Well, they're talking. Oh, you're talking to rocks with you all night our spiritual enemies
It says, Demons are spiritual enemies and it is the responsibility of everyone to deal
with them directly in spiritual warfare.
And then it says, Finally, my brethren, be strong in the Lord, and in the power of his
might, put on the whole armor of God that you may be able to stand against the wiles
of the devil, for we wrestle not against flesh and blood, but against principalities, against
powers, and against the rulers of the darkness of the world, against spiritual wickedness
For though we walk in the flesh we do not war after the flesh for the weapons of our warfare are not carnal
But might see through God to pulling down of strongholds
This scripture employs the analogy of wrestling in reference to our warfare with Satan and his host.
Wrestling is an accurate and pointed description. It speaks of close-quarter fighting, of personally grappling with the powers of darkness.
Most of us would prefer to use a giant cannon and blast away these enemies from miles away.
But this is not possible. The battle is very personal and close. The enemy is a spiritual one. The weapons are spiritual.
Wrestling also suggests pressure tactics.
This tells us that Satan's tactic is to put pressure on us. He does this in the areas of
our thought-life, emotions, decision-making, and our physical bodies. Believers often feel
pressured by the enemy in one way or another. When one is ignorant of Satan's devices,
he may turn for relief, he tranquilizes sleeping pills, or even the psychiatrist's couch.
But God's remedy for victories, our demonic pressures, is spiritual warfare over demonic
One can put pressure upon the demons and defeat them. He must learn the practical ways in which
this is done. He must throw away his ineffective fleshly weapons and take up mighty spiritual
weapons. The believer must know both his own weaponry and how to employ it and the tactics
of the enemy and how to defeat him. Ephesians chapter 6 verse 12 tells us four important
things about our spiritual enemy. First, we are told that we are fighting against principalities.
The Greek word for principalities is arkas.
This word is used to describe things in a series, such as leaders, rulers, and magistrates.
Thus, a series of leaders and rulers would describe their rank and organization, so the
word principalities tells us that the Satanic kingdoms are highly organized.
Perhaps Satan's forces are much the same in organization as the army of the U.S., which
has the president as commander-in-chief, followed by generals, colonels, majors, captains, and
Satan is the head of his kingdom and has under him a rank of ruling spirits, ultimately subject unto himself.
The English word principality is defined as the territory or jurisdiction of a prince or the country that gives title to the prince.
Thus we see that these ruling spirits are assigned over areas such as nations and cities.
by the account in Daniel chapter 10.
Daniel was seeking a word from God through prayer and fasting.
After three weeks, an angel appeared.
The angel explained that he had been delayed
in getting to Daniel with God's message
by an encounter with the prince of the kingdom of Persia.
He does not refer to an earthly prince
for no mere man could withstand the heavenly messenger.
He's speaking of a demon prince.
From this, it is clear that there are ruling
demon spirits placed by Satan over nations and cities in order to carry out his evil purposes.
Problems that persist in plague churches and homes can well indicate that special evil agents
have been a sign to cause trouble in these areas as well. Thus, we discover that our spiritual
warfare embraces much more than our individual lives. We were fighting for the welfare of our
homes, communities, and nation. The enemy is thoroughly organized. His moves are made with
Second, we are told that warfare is against powers.
The Greek word translated powers is exo.
The word is accurately translated as authorities.
The word tells us that the demons who are placed over the various areas or territories
are given authority to carry out whatever orders have been assigned.
The Christian soldiers need not be dismayed or discouraged to learn that these whom he
faces have been given authority, for the believer has even greater authority.
He is vested with the authority of the name of Jesus.
them that believe in my name shall cast out devils." Mark 16.7. The verse tells us that the
believer has the greater authority than the authority of demons. Demons are forced to yield
to the authority under the name of Jesus. The scripture reveals that demons not only have
In Luke chapter 10 verse 19 we read of the power of the enemy, the word for power in
Greek is dunamis.
Our English word dynamo and dynamite come from that word, yet this fact will not daunt
the Christian warrior, for he has the promise of God's word that he can have the greater
power than that of the enemy, but ye shall receive power, after that the Holy Ghost has
come upon you.
The power of the believer comes to him with the baptism in the Holy Spirit
Jesus knows that his followers need both authority and power to deal with the enemy when he sent the 12 out in ministry
He said them fully equipped
Okay, oh, okay, my phone says
That's okay
All right, that was good he was even done right
Yeah, raise your hands the air and mean to left and right. Someone's dancing
Okay
That moving yeah, the chat move is like I don't died
Don't you hate when you got to go back to the last the last day you were like, what was the last thing I read? Oh, you okay?
Yeah, you scare me. I was trying if I'm okay. Hey, there you go. Just popped up. Hello, Mr.
He popped up in the air, boom, he's like, oh, shit.
I hear it, this one works.
You don't know about you, so you don't worry about it.
People from my chat used to the 1A community, so.
So this is psyches awaken servers if you don't know AJM or anybody from my side
You come pull over here and check it out for yourself. You hear it. Love you. Love you, Mary
Yeah, okay, the phone's charging. Yeah, but that was it's kind of
Kind of interesting
Yeah, it's pretty bright outside. Hey Rudy, come here her tobacco, I don't know
Me I'm a cigar. Oh, there's a link pinned on the top
Anybody's welcome
Yeah
I'm gonna stop down. I'm gonna step down for 30 minutes. Okay. Nobody come up for 30 minutes. I'll be back psyche. Okay
You're leaving why are you signing off Mary goodbye, Mary? I love you. Maybe are you leaving?
Don't be offended about the wrench. I
Melted them down
Okay, we'll continue with our reading of the golden ass, okay. I love you to Jamie a girl, okay
So this is a great book. I read chapter one so basically chapter one he's this guy's going to
City it's called
Decili called the land of magic and he's going there and
his like his like a relative of his wrote somebody a friend of theirs says hey my
My relatives gonna come visit you. Can you stay at your house and so when he comes to the guy's house the guy is I think
I got money lender or something
So then he went to sleep so here's how the second chapter starts you'll love this guys
As soon as the sun of the new day had chased off the night, I emerged at once out of sleep
in my bed.
I am, by nature, all too eager to experience rare and wondrous events, and I reflected
that I was standing in the middle of Thessaly, whose homegrown incantations and magical arts
are celebrated and admired by everyone all over the world.
Hanging there in a state of anticipation and desire,
I was contemplating each and every object with curiosity.
As I looked around, nothing in that city
seemed to be what it really was,
but absolutely everything had been translated
into one another form by some sort of bullish hex
or hellish hex.
So that the stones I bumped against had hardened.
Out of humans and the birds I heard singing were likewise men who had become
Feathered and the here trees that line the city
Limits were people with foliage and though watery fountains that flowed to from human bodies states and pictures statues of pictures
We're going to walk forth the walls could talk oxen and other cattle would other
fortunes and lived from the very heavens and the orb of the sun and oracle was going back and forth has a nice little texture I
Was done speechless
tortured by my longing but
Could find no path to begin my pursuit of magic not even a scent to track down what I desired
So I kept circling about but while I was wandering through each street doorway to doorway like a lost rich boy
All at once I entered unwittingly through the first son of the gourmet gourmet
Form of the gourmet and there in the front of me was a woman surrounded by a large entourage
I sped up my steps to catch up with her the gold on her person and circling her jewels and entwining her tunic
Marked her clearly as an upper-class woman close by her side was an old man weighed down by his ears and it
And as soon as he saw me, he cried out,
It's by her, Kilise, it's Lucius!
And he came and he gave me a kiss and muttered something I didn't hear in the woman's ear.
And then turned to me,
Why don't you approach your relative and greet her?
I wouldn't dare approach a woman I didn't know, was my response,
as a blush suddenly suffused my face, and I stood there looking at the ground.
Oh, it's by Appalachus and it's like like one one ad. It's a Roman novel. It's the first novel of the world
It's really good story. I think you'll love it
Okay
So she turned her gaze on me with and with these words look look at him
The very same very same proper nobility as his dear departed mother
and is appearance on every respect so devilishly and precisely matching hers, height not excessive,
slenderness and fatality, cheeks with a delicate flush, hair blonde, with worn.
and worn without fussiness, eyes blue-gray, but washful and sparkling in their expression,
sharp like an eagle, a consonance blooming in every way, a gait elegant and natural.
And she added, I brought you up with my own hands, Lucius, of course I did.
I am kindred of your mother, not only of blood, but by nurture, you are both offspring of
wet nurse and grew up together in the close bond of sisterhood. The only thing separating
us is our rank. She married into a senatorial family and I am married out of the public eye.
I am the Berea whose name you shall surely recall was always on the lips of those who raised you.
So come with me and reply on the hospitality of my house, rely on the hospitality of my house,
After a moment, I stopped blushing and declined.
No, my aunt, it's impossible for me to desert my host Milo
without any quarrel between us.
But to be sure, whatever else can be done
without neglecting any obligations,
I will sure be sure to do Zella's sleep.
Whenever a reason arises for me to undertake this journey
again, I will lodge with you without fail.
Okay.
So I'll just say the page before I think it's he's gonna bet that he's got to see the donkey girl
I think this girl walking the donkey right there. Well, let's hear her. Okay
He looks pretty much like
okay
After these exchanges and
Conversation of the sort we walked a few paces and came to Brea's house her atrium was beyond beautiful in each of the four
For corners, columns held up statues of palm-bearing goddess victory.
Their wings were outspread, and without taking a step, they skimmed the unstable foothold
of a rotating spear with their dewy feet not adhering to the surface,
about to fly away.
Persian marble formed into the goddess Diana, a statue entirely splendid.
Its clothing was brown-black while it moved vigorously forward and faced you head-on as you entered venerable.
and with the grandeur of divinity, on either side were hunting dogs guarding the goddess.
They, too, of stone, their eyes were menacing, their ears pricked up, nostrils gaping, their mouths seething,
and if the sound of barking happened to start-ups nearby, you would think that it was coming from the jaws of stone.
But what particularly demonstrated the greatest evidence of the craftsmanship of this most exceptional sculpture
The dog's chest reared up high, and while their hind legs stood still, their front legs were running.
Behind the goddess's back, the rock carved up like a cave, lush with moss and grasses,
leaves and shrubs, and with vine shoots and saplings sprouting out everywhere in the stone.
Inside the cave, the shade of the sculpture was radiant from the brightness of the marble.
Beneath the far edge of the stone, rapes polished with the utmost skill were hanging down, which
arched rival of nature had fashioned to look real.
You would think they could pluck them to eat as soon as the ripeness of autumn had imbued
them with their full purple, and if you look straight into the fountain that was running
gentle rivulets you would think that these clusters hanging on as in the
countryside were possessed with so many qualities of reality were not deficient
even in movements. There in the middle of the sculptural vegetation was a statue
of the hunter Axion straining toward the goddess with voyeuristic curiosity.
You could see him on the rock and reflected in the fountain, easily in
While I was taking extraordinary pleasure in scrutinizing all of this, Marina said,
everything you see is yours.
And she asked everyone else to leave so we could speak in private.
When they'd gone, she warned by this goddess, Dearest Lucius,
I swear I am fearfully anxious for you.
I am to look out for you as if you were my own child.
Beware, I mean seriously beware of all the evil arts and wicked enchantments
of that woman Pamphile, the wife of your host Milo.
She is widely known as the witch of the highest order.
Mistress of every kind of spell, who just by breathing on twigs and pebbles, and small
specimens of that sort, knows how to plunge all the luminous brightness of the constellation
into the depths of the underworld, and the primeval void.
You see, whenever she sees a particularly attractive young man, she is consumed with
his charms and immediately turns her gaze and thoughts to him, as she lays down lures,
of a deep desire. As for the ones who are less obedient or turn contempt over because
they now disdain her, in the wink of an eye she transformed them into rocks and sheep
and miscellaneous animals. Others she utterly annihilates. This is why I worry and urge
you to be aware. She is constantly on fire for someone and you, being so young and beautiful,
But I, with my habitual curiosity, as soon as I heard mention of art and magic, the very
thing I always wanted to do so much, rather than heeding Berea's cautionary words, was
itching to leap at once into the depths of the abyss.
I would pay a very large sum of money to place myself.
Voluntarily, under the tutelage of such a master's pamphile, impatient and frenzied,
I freed myself from my aunt's chain-like hands-clasped, quickly said bye, and rapidly flew off to
Milo's house.
I spurred myself on, running even faster in my dimension state.
Come on, Lucius, wake up and take hold of yourself.
Here's the chance you've been waiting for.
What have you been hoping for forever? You can fulfill your heart's long desire of amazing tales away with childish fears
Attack the head on full force. You're clear though of any erotic involvement with your hostess and respect the marriage bed of your
most virtuous host Milo
But on the other hand, the midservant's photos, that's the place to make inroads vigorously.
She's pretty and flirty and quite a shrewd little thing.
Last night, when you were going to bed, she not only led you to the bedroom politely,
but she led you to the bedroom politely, but she put you in bed soothingly and covered
you lovingly and even kissed your head.
In fact, she stopped, turned around, looked back a few times before leaving.
So made the God's favor, even if it turns out badly.
Forward march on, Photos! While I was debating all this to myself, I came to
Milo's door, and as they say, voted with my feet since
I didn't run into Milo or his wife at home, but only my dear
Photos. She was preparing a fine spread for her
Toys cuts, sliced into bits, juicy rump roast and sauce, and what was just beginning to sense with my nose was very tasty pork sausage and a marinade.
She herself was nearly dressed in a linen, neatly dressed in a linen tunic, brightened with red sash, cinched highish beneath her pretty breasts.
She was stirring that food, pot round and round, with her pretty little rosy palms, shaking it rhythmically in sinuous circles.
sliding with the ease of liquid, her thighs slowly vibrating, her spine shimmering and
undulating slowly the culinary rhythm. I stood enchanted, transfixed and astounded by this vision
and that part of me that was lying still before stood up. After a moment I said to her,
my darling photos, it's so beautiful and fine the way you twist this cooking pot along with your
What a sweet dish you're cooking! The man you let dip his finger in there will be very happy and
definitely thrice blessed. Then she, being a witty girl and perch, bollied back to me,
off with you! You poor guy! Get as far as you can from my kitchen! Go! Because you are ignited even
a little from my fire, you will be burned to your depths, and no one will extinguish.
that heat except me. I know how to shake the pot and the bed and add my own luscious seasoning."
Then she looked over her shoulder at me and laughed. Still, I didn't budge from the spot
before carefully looking her up and down. But why bother with anything else?
When a woman's head and hair have always been my particularly obsession.
First, I examine them openly in public, later to enjoy the memory in private.
There is a valid and well-established rationale for the judgment of mind.
First of all, this particular part of the body is out in the open and clear view, positioned
so it encounters our gaze first.
Furthermore, the lovely cedar color that a bright garment imparts to the rest of the
body, the hair natural sheen provides for the forehead, for the head.
when they want to show off their body's innate grace, intimate grace, sorry, innate grace,
strip out their garments and throw aside their clothes, not but how to deploy their naked beauty,
with their skin's rosy blush, then they would be gleaming in their clothes cold and flush.
But, and this is irrelevant to say, and God forbid this should happen.
If you were to despoil the most exquisitely beautiful woman of her head and hair and denude
her face of its natural ornament, I don't care if she just brought me from the heavens,
I mean, she could be Venus herself, surrounded by a choir of graces and accompanied by a
city's worth of cupas, encircled with her girdle of desire, fragrant with cinnamon and
perfume with balsam.
But if she stepped out bald, she wouldn't be attractive even to her husband Vulcan.
illuminate her hair, and it gleams vividly or glows gently,
placidly against sunbeams.
Or what about it varies its effects.
And now, glimmering gold, it depicts the soft shade of honey.
And now, the raven dark mimics the sky blue feathers of a dove's neck.
Or when, imbued with Atabian oils, and parted with a sharp mouth,
sharp tooth of a fine comb, and tied at her
Back, it meets the lover's eyes and reflects the lovely image back, like a mirror.
Consider with her hair, beautiful strands piled in her head or flows down her back long luxuries
and lustrous.
Still, I maintain is the importance of hair, that no matter if a woman goes out, clothed
and jams and every other sort of ornament, nonetheless,
if she has not properly arranged her hair,
she cannot be considered well-dressed.
But in Photos' case, it was not a belabored
but an unstudied style that gave her charm.
Her abundant locks pushed gently back
and dangling down her nape, drawn out over her neck,
lightly resting on the border of her tunic,
were massed together at the end,
were not fastened them on the crown of her head.
I could not hear the torture of my acute pleasures any longer.
I leaned over and right at the spot where the hair started climbing the top of her head,
I pressed the most honey sweet kiss.
She twisted her neck around and turned to me with simmering and nibbling eyes and warned,
Hey you bookish boy, you're plucking a sweet and bitter morsel.
Careful you don't contract the lasting bitterness of bile along with your strong dose of honey.
What does it matter my delights when I'm ready to be laid out on the grill and roasted alive if I can just be
Revived with a single little kiss in the meantime
Saying which, I held her even tighter and started kissing her, but she, now rivaling my desire, with a lust equal and akin to mine, had already opened her mouth, which exuded the vapors of cinnamon, and had slipped her tongue against mine, striking it with the sweetness of nectar, roused with headlong desire.
I said to her, I'm dying actually, I'm already dead, unless you can offer me salvation.
At that she kissed me again and assured me, don't worry, I am a slave to the very same
desires as you and our pleasures won't be put off much longer.
I'll come to your room tonight and the first torch has been lit, so go up and get yourself
good and ready.
I'm going to do a battle with you, body and soul, the whole night long.
We've ballied.
These and other words back and forth and then parted I'd have voted the rest of the day to a bath and then dinner and when I
Invited to dine at upstanding Milo's elegant little table
I remember Bria's warding and kept myself as safe as I could from his wife's gaze
But I kept sneaking geese glance at that photos as she served up
Service ensured myself that way
Are you enjoying this?
Typical mother Lucius with a Lucius with a fabulous. Yeah, remember when okay, so you like this guy's okay
Perfect time 101 with psyche. Yeah, okay
Okay
So I said we ballied these okay
So it says after dinner pamphile predicted rain for the next day saying that she could forecast the weather with her lamp
I then mentioned that in
Corinth, a prophet, had predicted that my future would be a long story that no one would believe,
and yet my reputation would grow.
Milo knew this man and told a long story about him and how he had been exposed to the fraud.
While Milo was groaning on about with his tails, I was groaning inwardly, and not a
little angry that because of this opportune string of stories, I was losing a good part
and his luscious fruits.
So I finally choked down my manners and asked Milo
if he would pardon me if I went to bed early,
claiming that I was still suffering from yesterday's fatigue.
Without waiting for an answer,
I headed for my bedroom
and I found an elegant arrangement of food's laid out.
And besides, Lotus had arranged for the slaves to be sleeping on the ground as far from the doorway as possible.
I guess that they would be deprived of eavesdropping on our nocturnal love-making.
Noisemaking.
She had put by the bed a little table holding all the best leftovers from dinner,
as well as good drinking cups, already half full of wine, only waiting to be mixed with water,
and a flagon nearby with a wide opening cut made out to make it easy to drink from all.
She strengthened us as for the gladiatorial love contest ahead.
I just reclined when there was photos finished with petting and putting her mistress to bed.
She came to me joyfully.
Garland in her roses and a loose rose tucks between her simple breast, ample breast.
As she kissed me and pressed me closely, she unbound her garland and scattered flower petals
here and there.
But just before I had swallowed it all down, she gently interrupted me and she drank down the rest in little bird-like snips to her lips, giving it a sideways look as she sifted sweetly.
We shared another, and then a third cup, passing it back and forth between us until I was drenched
with wine, and not just in my head, but in my body as well. As a rule, I am restless and impatient
for pleasure, but now I was stricken, so I quickly and briefly lifted my tunic as far as my groin
and showed photos of my impatience for sex. Take pity on me, I cried, and help me right now.
for this imminent battle you've intimated without any official declaration of war.
When I took Cupid's first stinging arrow deep in my flesh, I strung my own bow,
tightly in return, and I'm very worried that my bowstring will snap from so much strain.
But if you want to please me even more, unbind your bullsome mane and push your arms around me
in an ostentuous embrace while your hair flows around us in undulating waves.
But in a flash, removed all the cuffs and dishes,
shipped out for clothes, and let down her hair
for a delightful dissipation.
Then she made herself into a statue of Venus
rising out of the ocean's waves,
even briefly covering her smooth steaks with rosy palm,
more shading from coquettishness
than hiding out of decorousness.
Fight, she said, and fight manfully.
I won't be turning my back in surrender.
Get set for hand-for-hand and hand-on-head combat and head-on hand-on hand and head-on combat
Forward march if you are a man thrust with your spear and be ready to die. No one gets a discharge from today's battle
Even as she spoke she climbed onto the bed
Slowly lower yourself onto me and move dartingly up and down with wiggling motions and twists of her supple spine
She says she to me fully with the pleasure of Venus on a swing
Then we collapse together with our arms in your twine utterly sapped energy exhausted limb limbs limp
panting our last breath
We spent all night engaged in these
and similar wrestling holds until the break of day,
sometimes restoring our languid bodies with wine,
which sparked our desire and renewed our pleasure.
Needless to say, we arranged many others such nights
along the lines of this excellent example.
Oh, okay, dang, she's turning into pig tea.
Who's pig tea?
Drop this, oh, I don't know, who are you talking about Charlie?
Yeah, oh, hold on.
I don't want people I don't want the bad mom clothes up on the sound. That's your that's your warning. Okay
Lucius yeah, Lucius
Everyone leave it. They don't like it. Oh gosh. Sorry
That's the second chapter. I mean, it's not a long long book, but
I don't know
You're back. Okay, cool. You got one friend
I don't know what you're saying, Charlie.
Hi, guys.
Oh, thank you, Christian.
I don't know, but sometimes there's
a lot of people in the chat, and then there's no one talks.
And I like the people that's like, look at me.
What kind of face are they making?
Thank you, Christian.
I love you.
Hi, baby.
Hey, Trix.
Hi.
Is it intense reading?
Yeah.
I mean, the story gets better and better.
Yeah, that was the kind of, that's the kind of sexy chapter.
I mean, that, just to go into that detail, it's like, oh, there's a whole page about
putting your hair up and down.
It's mostly listening.
Like you would at a church.
You know what I'm boring?
It was like a, it was a very sexy story.
That's the face. Oh, intense reading. Yeah
Yeah, well, it's like it's really small the text is so small and
It's a little blurry
Okay, yeah, so I did intense reading with the book though. What's the face I was making?
Hey thing that is
Yeah, it's a bit I can't wait to read no more of read more is you know
The shows go on because it gets better and better. It's almost to the part where he, you know,
called the golden ass. I'll read the back of the book to you.
The cover.
It says Peter Stinger and Ellen
Thinkin' Pearl breathes new life into Appalachus' golden ass, a hilarious body
tale and one of the earliest novels accentuating its remarkable empathy for
animals. You know, it gets into the animal stuff you see. Appalachus may
have maybe less well known today than other ancient writers, perhaps because
his work did not fall into the 19th century's image of what a
Well, the golden ass in the surreal and comical is explicit announcement that it is a work
of entertainment should not blind us to its serious engagement with question of animal
intelligence and the poorest boundaries between humans and animals.
Okay. Yeah. Like, see, I, you know, it seems to that, you know, I just gave, I gave some people like secret wrenches. I shouldn't tell that though. Yeah. Just gonna the perfect mod.
I got her, I got her, I got her like a little wrench she can put in a, I don't know, a concealed carry.
I want to I really I really do you want to
They're not what anybody to?
It really is about
So you guys won't get harassed even more than I don't care about people bitch to me about it
Like oh my progress, but I don't like when the mods fight and stuff. I
Am thank you. Pebs. Good to see you. Thank you for coming by. I know she doesn't go. I know I
Very few mods ever went rogue, but there was that one time like it was like they went back to like an old chat
And then hit everybody and then it took a while to figure that out like a couple days
So you never see what other ones actually
Have that I haven't seen me. Oh wait other names. Okay. Yeah
friend. Is that a threat Christine? Oh, I think it's a threat. You never know what
other names I actually have that aren't seen. Oh yeah. Oh, it's red. That's a
provocative question. I always have at least an alternate here that never
types. Oh wow. Christine on double duty.
What are you making that face that face for?
Thank you Chris and Christine is always watching out for me, and I know a lot of you are so I really appreciate you. Thank you
Okay, this is going slow. I'm going to read the third chapter
So the third chapter chapter three is called thoroughly an ass, okay
So this is ever since my aunt Verena had told me about my hostess's magical powers
I've been waiting to ask voters about
her mistresses' arts, especially eventually I sense that the many at the time have come
when I could persuade her to tell me about them.
So one night when she came to me in bed I said to her, my dearest Lotus, you know that
I have an intense interest in magic and you have hinted that your mistress is in the habit
of enchanting young men.
If you truly love me, tell me about her powers and how she casts her spells."
She was, at first reluctant to reveal the secrets of the house.
I drew her closer and said, you don't seem very clumsy and inexperienced in the magical
arts yourself.
I've seen it and felt it immensely since you.
held me in bondage with your glimmering eyes
and ruby red lips and shimmering locks
and lingering kisses and regulent breaths.
I am under your spell and you're willing slave.
With this date, you got me and I don't miss my home
and I'm not getting ready to go.
There's nothing I prefer to a single night with you.
Hello, Rudy.
First, let me carefully lock the doors of the bedroom," she said, so that I don't commit
a great indiscretion through the disrespectful impetuousness of my careless tongue.
And then she drew the bolt and fastened the clamp securely, then she turned back to me
I am afraid no, I am totally terrified to reveal the mysteries of this house and to unveil my mistress's shrouded secrets
But I am trusting you because you are learned from a good family and especially because you have been initiated into many religious cults
You understand the imperative of keeping your silence about sacred secrets and storing them deep within the confines of your heart
It is because of that love that binds me to you that I am revealing what I what I alone I know
Soon you will know everything about our household, all the mistresses and miraculous powers,
how the dead, bow to a will, constellations, are sent into disarray,
gods are forced under her sway, and the elements become her slaves."
Then she continued, when she wants to cast a spell, she climbs onto the roof,
out into the open air and sets on her magical apparatus.
Every sort of aromatic spice led tablets
inscribed with unintelligible letters.
The enduring remnants of unfortunate shipwrecks.
Numerous limbs of recently lamented
and ever-buried cadavers.
Here, noses and fingers.
They're flesh-laden nails from crucifixions
and that dark corner blood.
savages were murder victims and mutilated skulls tore from the teeth of wild beasts.
Here she chants her ever-silquibbering entrails and sprinkles them with an offering of sundry liquids, a bit of
fountain spray, some cow's milk, a little mountain honey, and a libation of sweet wine.
She can perform any feat through the unconquerable power of magical art and invisible forces of the deity she commands.
I was listening transfix with eagerness and I said,
I vow to keep silent about what you have told me, but please grant
Me, my most ardent wish, show me your mistress when she is practicing some of the magic you
have just described. Let me see her when she is calling on her gods, or best of all when
she is being transformed into another preacher. You know, I feel the most passionate desire
to experience magic right in front of my eyes.
Oh Lucius, you responded, how I wish I could give you what you want, but apart from the
matter of the malevolent disposition, she always practices her art and seclusion hidden away
from any observers, but I'll put your request before concerns for my own safety and I'll
look for a good opportunity and find a way.
Only as I said before, keep your promise and respect the secrecy of such a momentous event.
Amid this sort of chit-chat, we were brought closer and our bodies roused, and we began
to watch each other, so we tore up our clothes in a raw naked state we reveled in the state
of rites of Venus.
Then when I was already exhausted, voted generously and unsolicited, offered me sex in the boy's
position.
Finally, after a wakeful night, sleep infused our drooping eyelids and held us deep into
We slept a few nights, engaged in pleasures like those, when photos rushed into me in
the state of trembling excitement and announced that her mistress was planning to grow feathers
and become a bird in the next night to fly off to one of her lovers and that I should
cautiously prepare myself for viewing the phenomenal events.
So around the first watch of the night, she led me noiseless on tiptoe to the upper chamber
First of all, Pamphile took off her clothes, then she opened the lid of a chest and chose
several little boxes.
She removed the lid of each of them, scooped out some ointments, and rubbed it between
her palms for a long time.
Then she smeared it all over her body with the tips of her toenails, the very ends of
her hair on her head.
After that, she spoke secretly with her lamp at some length and shook the arms in an equivering
agitation.
When she started waving up and down, she sprouted feathers soft and light, then wings strong
in flight, with her nose bent into a beak and her toenails tapered into talons.
Pamphile became an owl.
She gave a quarelless screech and dumped a little off the ground to test herself.
Then, lifting herself into the sky, she soared away in full flight.
She then was transformed intentionally by her magical arts, and I stood there enchanted
by no spells, transiting simply by the wonder of what I had seen.
I seemed...
To be anything other than Lucius blasted beyond the limits of my brain craze dreaming in full wakefulness
I kept rubbing my eyes to see if I was awake and I finally recovered my sense of the world around me
I grabbed bodice's hand and brought it up to my eyes saying please while the time is ripe
Let me enjoy a magnificent and unique proof of your affection
Share with me a little dash of the ointments, I beg you, by those nipples of yours, my little
honey, and bind me, your slave, to you forever, by the favor of that which can never be returned.
Let me be your wing-cupid standing beside his venus.
What if he cried, you're playing the fox, you Don Juan, and asking me to take an axe
From the she-wolves of Thessaly, where will I find you when I become a bird? Where will I see you?
May the gods keep me from such a crime, I said, even if I travel the whole sky on lofty wings of an eagle,
delighting in playing the messenger and arms bearer of Supreme Job.
the honor of that wigginess. I swear by the sweet knot of hair on your head that has bound my soul to you.
I prefer no other woman to my foetus. Come on, but a handsome and entertaining lover and owl would be for a woman.
But when I almost forgot to ask, what word or action do I use to return to being Lucius after I shed those wings?
Don't worry on that score," she answered.
My mistress has shown me with special thoroughness what it takes to transform all those shapes
back into human bodies.
But don't imagine she does this out of any sort of kindness, is only so that I can provide
an effective antidote when she returns home.
Assuming, assuring me repeatedly about the antidote, she crept in Pamphile's room with
great trepidation and removed from the chest the box, which I hugged and kissed and asked
for luck in my flight.
I stripped off my clothes and greedily immersed my hands on the box, taking a lot of ointment
and rubbing it over my limbs.
I stretched out my arms and with alternating motions I was trying to flap my wings into
Proud of no wings appeared. Soon it was obvious that my body hair was thickening into bristles,
my delicate skin hardening and to hide, and the ends of my palms, my ten fingers becoming
single hooves, and a gigantic tail was emerging from the tip of my spine. Now my face was enormous,
my mouth elongated, my nostrils gaping, my lips pendulous, my ears too were easily enlarged and
I didn't see any solace in the retro-transformation, except that my organ had grown too large for embracing photos.
In this state of hopelessness and helplessness, I was examining my whole body, and I saw that I was no bird, but an ass.
I wanted to complain to Photos about what she had done, but I had been robbed of human gesture and speech,
at her with frowning lips and watery eyes and reproached her in silence.
For her part, when she saw me in the state, she struck her face furiously with her hands
and said, I'm done for, hurry and worry fooled me and these similar boxes deceived me, but
it's fine because there is a much easier antidote for this shape change.
All you have to do is nibble on some roses and you will leave the acid skin and return
back to my luscious instantly.
I'd make some garlands this evening, as I usually do, so that you wouldn't have to suffer even one night's delay.
But as soon as it's light, I'll rush to get this remedy to you.
Here it is.
So it says, that's how she lamented, but as for me, although I was thoroughly an ass
and a beast of a burden instead of Lucius, I have still remained in human consciousness.
So I debated long and deeply with myself whether I should kill that wicked worthless woman
with thick and fast kicks and attacks with the teeth, but a more rational thought pulled
that if I punish bodice with death, I might be extinguishing all hope of fortune, future aid.
So, downcast and shaking my head, I gulped down my outrage for the time being and opted for subservience.
in my harsh lot. I headed therefore toward an excellent steed of mine in a stable where
I found another ass belonging to Milo, formerly my host. You see, I was seeing that there
was a natural and unspoken oath of allegiance among mine animals. My horse would offer
me hospitality and luxurious stay, motivated by a kind recognition and commiseration. But
that outstanding conveyor of mine, my horse, and the ass, put their heads together and right away
plodded my destruction, fearing for their food, I guess, scarcely had they seen me approaching
the stall when they pinned back their ears in fury and charged at me ready to strike with
There are pernicious hooves, so I was driven as far as possible from the barley I set out
in the very evening with my own hands and that equine servant of mine now so closely
linked to me.
Hurt by this, and relegated to solitude, I retired in the corner of the stable and thought
about the insults of those my associates had.
with the help of some roses, and was contemplating what revenge I would take on my disloyal horse.
But there, in the very middle of the midmost pillar, holding up the beams of the stable,
sitting on a small shrine with a statue of Epona, goddess of horses and mules,
adorned with fresh garland of roses. As I perceived the scent of my deliverance,
I had high hopes. I stretched out my front legs and leaned forward as far as I could,
elongating my neck and extending my lips reaching for that garland with everything I had, but as bad luck would have it
the slave who looked up after my horse suddenly noticed me trying to reach the roses and jumped up showing in
in
indignantly
How long, citizens, do we have to put up with such a gilding?
First, he was a menace to the cupid's food, and now, or to the equid's food, and now it's the God's shrines.
Damned if I don't believe this temple robber crippled and hobbling.
Right away he started hunting for some kind of weapon in his blind rush
He bumped against the bundle of wood and searched out a knotted
Casual larger than all the others crucial are larger than all the others poor miserable me
He didn't stop beating me until with a sudden
Bang and a thunderous crash the doors of the house were beaten down and he fled in tear and the whole quaking neighborhood screams robbers
Suddenly a mass of robbers forced upon the open the house and completely took control
Well, a virtual army ring the building more enemy troops ran into obstruct the
auxiliaries on our side
From flying in all directions the night was illuminated by their swords and torches fire and dagger flashed like rays of the rising Sun
There was a storeroom set deep in the middle of the house
for bolted in
Borrowed with the strongest of blocks were Milo's Milo had statuated his treasure
This they attack and split open with sturdy axes and they quickly tied up every bit of that bounty and bundles
shared it around and carried it off, but the moment
The amount of carry exceeded the number of carriers.
The great excess of opulence skirmied their gateway, so they pulled on two donkeys and
my horse from the sable and burned us with the heaviest of the bundles.
Threaded with kujuls, they drew us out of our now empty house.
They left one of their gang as a spy to report back later as to whether they were under suspicion
constantly striking us with blows coming thick and fast.
And so with the heavy weight of the booty,
the steep height of the mountain and the extreme length of the journey,
I was as good as dead. Gradually, but with gravity,
it occurred to me to seek the aid of the civic authorities
and to free myself from these tortures by calling
on the respected name of the emperor. So when it was clear daylight
and we were passing through a crowded marketplace among the throngs of Greece,
Yeah, the August name of Caesar in the language of my birth, but even though I stouted. Oh
Over and over very eloquently and mightily I could not enunciate the rest Caesar's name
the robbers though objected to my discordant noise and wished my poor hide until
It was full of holes than I see.
Finally, the great Jupiter brought me unexpected deliverance.
As we passed, small farmsteads and grand houses, I saw a charming little garden where along,
with other pleasant greenery, untouched roses were blooming in the morning dew.
I gazed open-mouthed at them and drew closer, elated and cheered by the hope of rescue.
And then I had a different thought about my safety.
If I were to shed the ass and skin,
and again, it emerged into luscious,
I would meet certain death at the hands of the robbers,
feared either as a wizard or a witness.
So I have stained from the roses out of sheer necessity
and tolerated my present situation
of feeding on hay to give the appearance of being an ass.
Hi.
The golden ass by Athalayas. Yeah, he just turned into he just uh he was trying to like
Do magic and then he uh, he's reading the long list of men you have had sex with jp
Yeah, oh come on this is called this is called this is called a psyche verse
Oh, it's a conversation. Okay, it's reading. Okay, so yeah, that's a really good book.
I'm just thinking of different things to read. It seems like the pan is a little bit quiet today, but
let's see if it picks up. Probably have to get some cigars soon.
Guys, we're almost out of cigars in the store. I probably will have to quit smoking, which I probably can do.
I got a lot of great books though, it's super interesting things to read
So
Hang out if you want to come on in here, it's warm in here today
Didn't I say go outside a little bit
This is it, right?
This chat
I know he's trash, but
No, I'm not gonna talk. That's fine
Every behaving like you know, so don't break the rules. Okay, it should be good
He's like a he's a harmless
Well, I don't I don't know. He says trashy things. Oh
You want to hear more
Yeah, it's so quiet and I'm enjoying reading it
They just turn into the donkey. Okay by magic
This one's called on the road with the robbers
So the regular dog. Oh, that's not just on Dougie Doug. It's a different dog
Around midday, when it was already scorching hot, we detour from the road into a village
to visit with some old men on friendly terms with the robbers.
Even an ass could perceive as much from their warm greetings, their lengthy conversations,
and their exchange of kisses.
Also the robbers gave them certain items that they unloaded from my back, which they seemed
Finally, they relieved us of the baggage and sent us out into a nearby meadow to graze
freely.
But I had no interest in meeting up to co-pasture with the ass and my horse, especially as I
was not yet used to lunching on hay.
So when I saw a kitchen garden behind the stable, I broke right in since I was dying
of hunger.
There were just raw vegetables, but I managed to stuff my belly well enough.
Then I prayed to the gods and surveyed the surroundings to see if somewhere in the adjoining gardens
I could find a radiant rose bush. That's the antidote, okay?
Okay
My very my very solitude give me confidence after I ingested the remedy hidden off the road by some shrubs
I could rise up again from the bent over gate of a quadruped into the erect posture of a man unnoticed.
And so, while lost in the sea of thought, I saw a bit further on a leafy grove in a shady valley where amidst the grass, cover and verdant blush, the red, red rose shone forth in blinding glory.
My not altogether beastly heart, I thought it a grove of venus and the graces, where their flowers regal radiance illuminated the hidden darkness.
I prayed the happy and prosperous God's success and tore off a great clip so that by Hercules I felt no longer an ass.
But altered by my surplus of speed into a racehorse and yet in spite of the agile and applause worthy attempt
I couldn't overcome the opposition of fortune whereas I came closer
I saw that these were not tender and lovely roses with
What was scented due and still wet growing on fertile brushes and blessed thorns and the shady valley was nothing
But a rear red hedge with close packed bushes
These look like laurel with their dense foliage and produce moderately red blossoms that resemble flowers with ascent.
But they lack it.
The untaughty country folk call them laurel roses, and they are death to cattle when eaten.
I was now so tangled up in misfortunes that I was ready to give up on life, so I started
to reach for those poisonous roses.
But as I approached, hesitatingly to pluck them, a young man, most likely the gardener
whose vegetables I had entirely devastated, realized his loss and charged at me furiously
with a huge staff.
He grabbed me and beat me all over, almost to the point of death, except that finally
I found a pretty smart way to help myself.
Side high in the air and kicked and kicked with the heels of my back feet
When he was badly beat up and lying against the slope of the hill nearby
I've fled and freed myself
But right away some woman his wife I suppose as soon as she saw him
From the top of the hill was lying there half dead smooth straight at him with a plaintive wailing bent on destruction
For all the villagers were roused by her cries and calls of their dogs from Hill and from Dale
They urged them on to attack me and lacerate me with their savage
This savage rage then without question
I thought, then without question, I was going to die.
So then I saw the dogs, they'd sicked on me,
huge and numerous, the kind that fight with bears
and lions in the amphitheater.
I hatched a plan on the spot.
I stopped running away, turned around,
and went back to a good pace to the stable
where we were supposed to rest.
The villagers managed to restrain their dogs,
but they tied me to a hook and sturdy rope
and resumed beating me.
They would have finished me off altogether
if my belly, constricted by the pain of the beating,
bloated by raw vegetables I eaten, was weakened by the liquefying of my bowels, and had not
driven them away from the already crushed ribs, as I emitted a sudden jet spray of dung,
some fled, sputtered by the horrendous fluid, others in the stench of the stinking smell,
toward afternoon, the robbers loaded up very heavily,
me especially, and led us out of the stable.
By that time, we completed a good part of our journey.
I was already worn out by the endless road,
sunk by the weight of the load,
and exhausted by the strikes from the goat.
My hooves were rubbed ragged. I was lame and teetering. So when I stopped near a gently meandering stream
I took this lucky opportunity and figured I would ingeniously bend my legs and throw myself onto the ground
Then I would be absolutely determined not to get back up no matter how much they beat me
In fact, I was prepared to keep lying there until I was struck not out just by a koojool
But even by a dagger. I was thinking that if I was totally in feeble and half-dead I would earn
a disability discharge. It's truly the robbers from impatience by the delay and eagerness to
continue their hurried fight, but distribute my load onto the other two-pack animals and
leave me prey to the wolves and vultures. For luck.
of any better revenge. But the worst luck thwarted my beautiful plan of mine. For that
other ass intuited and stoke my and stole my idea of banning exhaustion. He plopped
himself down with all his baggage and laid there like a corpse. He wouldn't even try
have done his tail, his ears, and his shanks. Finally, when they got tired and saw it was helpless,
they consulted with each other, not wanting to delay their escape, while tending to a dead, no, a rock of an ass.
So he distributed the baggage between me and my horse, drew a sword, and slashed through each of his knees,
then took a little off the road and plunged him still breathing from the side of the sheet clip into the valley below.
From then on, thinking about the fate of my poor comrade in arms,
I decided to set aside all trickery and lies and show I was a well-behaved ass. In any case,
I noticed them saying to each other that they'd be longing
Lodging and restful end to the whole journey in the next town and this was their headquarters and home
So while we traveled a gentle little slope, we came to our destination here
They removed everything and stowed it inside
Bead of all weight instead of a bath I relieved
Free default freedom of all weight instead of a bath. I relieve my tiredness by rolling in the dust
The time and subject matter demand that I give you a description of the surroundings and of the cave where the robbers lived.
This will be a way for me to test my intelligence and for you too to see whether you sincerely feel that I was an ass in mind and perceptive abilities as well as my body.
Here I go, the mountain was rugged, shaded by the forest branches, and particularly steep.
At this point of the steepest incline, it was surrounded by rocks and therefore inaccessible.
Valleys ran around the foot of the mountain filled with galleys and pits and heaved high
with thorn, bushes, stretching in all directions, all of which offered a natural fortification.
From the very peak of flowering spring, gush forth bubbly and slipping down the slope, spewed
out silvery ripples and dispersed on the numerous rivulets, irrigating the valleys with its
streams flowing sluggish, finally surrounding the whole area with something like a swamp
rose from the cave with a rock face and mountain tapered off and there was a yard then stopped
sturdily with a strong wonder whack. It was suitable for a sheepfold and served as a well
extending all along the sides. In front of the doors were long narrow paths. I would not
hesitate to call it the forecourt of the robbers layer. There was nothing nearby except a small
half-patterly, hidden hut, hidden half-patterly by the robs.
Here I later discovered scouts chosen by her, by a lot among the robbers kept guard at night.
When each of the robbers had compacted his body and squeezed into the case, they all tied up.
They all tied its up in front of the door with a strong strap.
They called out insulting me to an old woman bent over by extreme age, who as it appeared
was in so charge of the health and welfare of these young men.
Hey you, corpse long overdue for this pire, prime disgrace of life itself.
Deaths so reject.
Are you going to sit at home having fun and doing nothing?
After our great and perilous labors with some late-night refreshments all you need all you do is flood your
ravenous belly day and night with undiluted wine the old woman started trembling with the sad and
Trembling and this and I wait awakened in a shaking voice. Oh hot my bravest
Most faithful young men, my saviors, here is an ample dish,
seething with savory spices, red in abundance,
wine generously and carefully poured to the polished cups.
And as usual, hot water, ready for your makeshift baths.
As she, after she spoke, they all undressed
and warmed themselves in front of a large fire.
And they poured hot water on their bodies,
rubbed themselves down with oil
and reclined on the tables, piled high with food.
They had just reclined when lo and behold another much larger group of young men arrived whom you would immediately recognize as robbers
For they too were carrying looted gold and silver coins and vessels as well as silk clothes interwoven with gold thread
when they had reviewed
Revived themselves in the bath the same way as the others and
Interspersed themselves among the comrades on dining couches those drawn by lots served the others
There was boisterous eating and drinking mounds of meat bushels of bread
copious cups. They jetted loudly, sang noisily, joked abusively, and generally behaved just like
those half-beast lapis and half-human centaurs. When the robbers had eaten their fill to begin to
tell tales of their exploits, I will retell just one of them told by a robber in the second group
Right easy. Hold on
Like easy. Hold on your time. Okay. What's going on here? He's asked me. Hey time. Are you enjoying this book?
Yeah, I think elder will be here in there
Hi time hi time
Yeah
So I'm reading this story. I don't know if you just came in guys. It's really good books called golden ass
So the guy went to like, you know study witchcraft and that's Lee in Greece
What book was it? Yeah, what book is it? I just came in a few minutes ago. It's called the golden ass by Appalachus
And so basically he goes and you know business are relative in this magical Greek city
And he ends up at this grand witch's house, and she has, you know, a maid servant.
And she's warned not to, you know, sleep with the witch, because she's, you know, really powerful.
But, you know, he decided to, like, go for her maid and photos.
And so they had some sex, and he wanted to turn into an owl, like her mistress did.
And then she got the ointment.
and she like rubbed it on him and he turned into a donkey.
Okay, so then now he's been kidnapped by robbers
and he's been beaten and he's looking for roses too
because the roses are the antidote
because the maid servant didn't find the antidote.
Okay, sorry, that's my best summary.
So here's the story.
It says, in practice, we hear constant talk
of a certain Demo Charis,
who was to put on a gladiatorial show.
He was a man of prominent family, prosperous means,
and he provided it for public pleasures
with funding fitting his fortune.
Who among us has the talent or the eloquence
to lay out adequate words,
all the different aspects of multifaceted preparations
for the show?
Here were gladiators of renowned strength.
Then hunters known for their skill
and their hunting contest.
And in the corner, those sentence,
irrevocably to death, supplying a rich meal
of themselves to fatten the beast.
Here were multipurpose mechanisms constructed
with supporting beams and towers plated together
and planks of wood to look like movable houses,
fit for hanging, colorful announcements
of the next hunting show.
And then such a number and such a victory of beast
for Demo Chárez had taken particular care
from abroad all those fancy graves for the condemned criminals, but beyond all the other
trappings of this particular show, he had spent all the resources of his inheritance
on a vast number of enormous bears, apart from the ones captured on his own hunting
expeditions and those acquired as a great expense, friends had given him others on several
occasions and he tended them anxiously with lavish care.
But such renown and dazzling a future months for pleasure could not escape the menacing eyes of
Envy for the collection of beasts
Worn out by long captivity weakened by the heat's intensity and sapped by the sluggish inactivity
We're seeded with a sudden pestilence and we're used almost to nothing
you would see
Beastly shipwrecks of their half-dead bodies scattered all over the squares the uncultivated common folk
Forced by uncouth poverty to seek out free food and foul supplements to their unburied and attunated diets
These people ran straight for the food lying about so on the spot
Ubulias there and I came upon an ingenious plan as follows
We carried the biggest and fattest one we could find into our hideout
As if we were going to use it as food, then we stripped its hide thoroughly of the flesh,
carefully preserving all its claws and leaving the head intact down to the neck, and then
we thinned out the skin, scraping it expertly, sprinkled it with ash, and left it in the
sun to dry.
And while it was being parched by the flames of the sky's heat, we'd gorge ourselves
the sacred duties of our upcoming campaign.
One of us, the one who surpassed the other in strength,
not of body, but of mind,
and who must have been a volunteer,
should cover himself with that pelt
and assume the appearance of a bear.
Then he would go up to Demo Sharris' house
at the perfect time in the quietness of night
and provide an easy access to the front door.
Many of our brave comrades were inspired to volunteer and assume the clever disguise, but Threslian was the band's first choice as he undertook the gamble of the risky device.
He can seal himself calmly to the skin, which fit him easily and was soft and pliable.
Then we marched up the edges.
and made a fire seam covering the gap and juncture,
even though it was small with a dense hair around it.
We forced Threselian's head up through the neck
of the edge of the throat where the bear's neck had been
slashed and made little holes for breathing
and seeing around the nose and eyes.
Then we left our brave comrade who totally became a beast
in a cage that was bought for a modest price.
He crept up quickly with residue bigger.
After this beginning, we turned to the next steps of Robruze.
After scouting himself, we found the name of a certain
Ms. Nohr, Atresian, who enjoyed a close friendship with Demosharis, fabricated a letter to him
stating that his good friend wanted to dedicate the first fruits of the hunting expedition
to embellishing the gladiatorial show.
When the evening came, we took advantage of the cover of darkness and offered Threselion
in his cage to Demosharis along with a forged letter.
He admired the sides of the beast and was pleased by the timely generosity of an old
so pleased that he ordered that when we had brought him this delight,
should be awarded 10 gold coins from the cash box he had at hand.
Then, since the thirst for novelty and new sights tends to attract the minds of men
towards sudden apparitions, a large crowd gathered to admire the beast.
But our comrade, Therese Leon, very carefully impeded their curious gaze by frequently rushing
The citizen declared with one voice that Demosharis was happy and blessed since after such a terrible loss to the beast, he had somehow stood up to fortune with this new acquisition.
Demosharis, meanwhile, ordered the beast to be taken.
Out to the fields with utmost care, but I interrupted be careful, sir. I'm exposing a bear already timed out
Tired out from a long hot journey to the company of many others who I here are not well
Instead, why don't you just seek an open and airy spot? Maybe something cool near a lake?
Don't you know this kind of heat of heat a beast always makes a layer amid lush groves
Dewey caves and pleasant springs demo showers was terrified
by my warnings as he considered the number of bears he had lost and easily agreed to
let us put the cage where we thought best.
In addition, we are prepared to sleep the night right here beside the cage so that we
can offer the bear its usual food and drink at the right time, seeing as how it is very
tired from the discomfort of heat of jousting.
We don't need this kind help from you," he answered.
But now, pretty much, my entire household is practiced in feeding bears and from doing
it day after day.
After this, we set our farewells and left through the city gate, but we spied a tomb
well off the road and set it in a hidden spot.
There were coffins, their lids half open, due to rot and time, and the dead inhabited
now with just dust and ash.
for storing the loot ahead.
Then according to the guiding principles of our profession,
we awaited the moonless time of the night
when sleep and its first onslaught
invades the presses most forcefully in the hearts of men.
Our division was stationed right in front of
Demosharis' door, armed with swords,
as a surety, so to speak, of L'Arsonius' success.
Thress of Leon II,
seized by a precise pillaging moment of the night,
wrapped out of the cage, and swiftly finished off
every one of the guards with his sword,
who lay in sleeping nearby.
Then he killed the doorkeeper as well,
took the key, drew open the doors of the gate.
We rushed in, and when we had been received
into the belly of the house,
he showed us the storeroom where he had keenly noted
a large quantity of silver being stored that evening.
When our hand had broken into the room through force and teamwork, I ordered each of our
troops to carry off as much gold and silver as he could and to hide it quickly in these
tombs of the trustworthy dead, and then to speed back and get another hand.
Meanwhile, in the interest of all, I could not remain by myself near the threshold of
the house to keep a careful eye on everything until they returned, for the sight of a bear
running around in the middle of the house seemed enough to scare away anyone in the
who, in short, no matter how strong and fearless, would not have been roused in flight by the
enormous shape of such a giant beast, especially at night, and would not shed himself in the
room for fear and trembling and lock the door.
All those plans had been organized with robust deliberation, but an unfortunate event occurred.
For while I was anxiously awaiting the return of my comrades, some slave boy was awakened
by a noise, or maybe by divide intervention, and stealthily cleft out as he saw the beast
running freely about the whole house.
Keeping a strict silence, he retraced his steps and managed to alert everyone on the
premises of what he'd seen.
Lamps, wax candles, tallow candles, and other devices were lighting up the night,
illuminated the shadows. No one in a large crowd came out unarmed,
but each one equipped with clubs, spears, and even drawn swords guarded the entrances.
They even brought out their hunting dogs, long-eared and shaggy, so to do the beast.
At that point, with the uproar growing exponentially, I retreated backward from the house.
But I watched Thresley and Adderley fighting off the dogs as I looked behind the door.
Although he was facing life's ultimate finish line, he did not fail to remember himself
I'm not calling Joker.
Joker can call me.
As long as he's still breathed, he maintained the role he assumed.
Now fleeing, now standing his guard, taking on various Ursin poses and movements,
he finally slipped out of the house.
But even when he had gained freedom,
Out in the open streets, he could still not seek safety in flight for all the dogs from the next alley, fierce and numerous,
join in hordes with the hunting dogs that had left the house in pursuit.
It was a wretched and deadly spectacle that I watched, or owned, thrustedly, and surrounded and besieged by packs of savage dogs and
lathered by pest-persistent biting. Finally unable to bear the sight of such pain,
I mingled in the crowd who was milling about and tried
The only way I could to bring some concealed help to my comrade in arms, I harangued the leaders of the bearhunt.
What a great scandal in this grace! We are destroying my nificence and truly valuable beasts!
But the artfulness of my speech did nothing to help this most unfortunate youth,
where someone ran out of the house, a tall and strong man, without hesitation thrust the spear through the bear's innards.
Then someone else...
then someone else and then many others no longer afraid they rivaled each other
even getting close and stabbing with their swords. Finally it was not by lack
of endurance that Thrice Leone that incomparable jewel of our band was
defeated, but his spirit worthy of immortality gave out. Nor did he be
traded on the covenant of our sacred oath while shouting or wailing, but
with his usual strength
As he was ripped by teeth and pierced by swords, he endured his present fate, determined,
roaring and animal growling.
Glory he kept for himself while remembering his life was fate.
Still, he had thrown the town into such a turbulent terror and trembling that no one
dared touch the beast, lying dead as it was.
up till dawn and well into the next day, not even with a finger.
At last, someone, a little braver, cut open the belly of the beast with a knife,
slowly and fearfully, and stripped the splendid robber of the bear.
Thus, Threselion perished from our company,
and he had not perished from the annals of glory.
And so we gathered up those parcels that we'd hidden
with the trustworthy dead and quickly carried left the city limits of Plataea,
meditating on this idea. There is a reason that no loyalty can be found in this life.
Loyalty has left us with the dead, hating our cheating and lies. It is thus that we come to you,
worn out by carrying this load, and by the ruggedness of the road, and saddened by the loss of our
companions. But look, here's the loot we bought.
When he finished speaking they poured out libations of undiluted wine from gold cups in memory of their fallen comrades and sang some
Laddering songs to the god Mars and went to sleep for us the old woman
I've already mentioned ditched out fresh barley without even measuring so that my horse might have thought he was dining in the
10-course meal he got soul possession and I have never been in the habit of eating barley unless it's crushed fine and soaked for a long time until it was mashed
So I rummaged around the corner where they piled the leftover bread and vigorously exercised
my jaws, which were weakened by incestant hunger and full of cobwebs.
But as the night wore on, the robbers suddenly woke up.
This is good, guys.
I think Joke is trying to get a hold of you.
Maybe the pregnant test is positive.
I mean, I thought I'd make people come to him.
Yeah, I like to think, I'm more of like a,
but I think I'm a little bit of a stigma, maybe.
Okay, where'd this go?
Okay, here we go.
Okay, where are the ends?
Okay, but as the night wrote more on the rubber suddenly woke up
They broke camp and equipped themselves in various ways, with some carried swords, some
moved along in lightly disguised as demons.
As for me, not even profound sleepiness could get in the way of my urgent and established
munching.
Before, when I was Lucian, I would leave the table satisfied with one or two rolls, but
now I was serving such a bottomless stomach that I was grazing on a third bushel.
I was still frantically at work when the bright light of day surprised me.
of an ass's sort to tear myself away from the bread.
It was difficult, but it was difficult,
and quenched my thirst in a nearby stream.
Soon the robbers were back,
more axedyms and agitated than usual,
more anxious than agitated than usual.
They weren't carrying any sacks of plunder,
not even one worthless rag.
There for all their swords for all the power of those hands and the collective strength of their whole company
Was only one thing they had brought back a single girl lady like an appearance
You could tell by her elegant clothes that she was from the region's best families
This was a girl desirable even to an ass like me by Hercules. She was wailing and nearly
tearing out her hair and her clothes and she and they brought her inside the cave and tied her to one of the
To lessen your trouble saying don't worry about your safety and tassity just be patient long enough for us to get some benefit of
This the constraints of poverty have driven us this calling
I am sure your parents with all their wealth will quickly come with a substantial ransom for their own flesh and blood
Synergy as though they are they said these and similarly you lose use of things and in that thing to soothe the girl's pain
obviously not
She rested her head in her lap and wept constantly.
So they called the old woman and instructed her to sit by the girl and comfort her with
gentle and friendly conversation as best she could, while they turned to the business
and the profession.
But, still, the girl couldn't be distracted from the weeping she'd begun.
Rather, she increased her lamenting, her side-shaking with ceaseless sobbing.
She even brought me to tears.
Even keep living deprived of such a grand home so many servants such dear slave children and such blessed parents poor me
The prize of an unfortunate plunder a possession closed up in the stone prison like a slave
deprived of the sweet pleasures I was born and raised on so many such awful robbers in a
horrifying band of cutthroats
She cried like this
Until she was so tired out from her unhappy thoughts, the strain of her voice, and the
weirdness of her body that she finally closed her drooping eyes to sleep.
But she didn't sleep for long.
She had just closed her eyes when she suddenly deltid out of her sleep and began to strike
herself more and more violently like a mad woman, beating her breast with self-injurious
hands and hitting her beautiful face.
The little old woman immediately asked her why she had started up her morning again,
Alas, now for sure, I have totally perished, that's it, I'm giving up all hope of rescue,
I need a rope or sword, or best a clip to jump off of, but the old woman was furious and
demanded her face livid, what the hell was she crying about, and why, after such a nice deep
sleep, was she reopening her wounds and giving free reign to her laments. I guess you intend to
cheat my young men out of the ransom money, the robbers said I, you don't care about your tears.
And if you keep this up, I'll make sure you're burned alive.
The girl was frightened by that and kissed the old woman's hand saying,
spare me, good mother, and remember your human kindness.
Help me a little. This is a very difficult situation.
I don't imagine that pity has totally shriveled up inside of you,
even though you've grown years older.
Older were many years and your hair is distinguished white.
Consider the scene of my misfortune,
an attractive young man, first among his peers,
whom the whole city had adopted as their favorite son.
My cousin, in fact, a mere three years older,
raised him with me from infancy.
Then, as we were grown, inseparable from us,
the same house, the same room, and the same bed. And he pledged to me because of our mutual
feelings of pure love, long ago engaged with natural vows, his formal sense of the dowry
and marriage set parents' consent given. He was even called husband in legal documents.
He was performing animal sacrifice to the temples and shrines of the town, surrounded
by relatives from his side and mine. The whole house, alight with little torches, was singing
Meanwhile, my poor mother was holding me in her lap and decking me out in my wedding dress giving me tender kisses the whole time repeating anxious prayers for children to come when suddenly
Robbers rushed in and attacked savagely, flushing their bare, sharp swords.
It looked like a battlefield, but they didn't set their hands to slaughter or plunder.
They packed themselves tightly together and went straight for my bedchamber.
Nobody in the household thought back or even resisted at all while they seized poor me,
straight from my mother's lap.
Fainting and shaking with terrible fear, but just now a cruel dream revived or rather multiplied by troubles
I dreamed I was violent turn
I was finally torn from my home my chambers my bedroom my bed itself
And I was calling my unfortunate husband's name through deserted and trackless realms
He was still dripping with aromatic nuptial oils and a dorm with a garland, but when he saw
He was bereft of my embraces. He came following my footsteps as I fled on foot, not my own.
He cried out in distress and called the people to witness lamenting that his beautiful wife
was being taken from him. Then one of the robbers, indignant at this convenient pursuit,
grabbed a large rock lying at his feet and struck the poor beloved young husband and killed him.
It was his hideous spectacle that woke me terrified and trembling from my sinister dream.
Thank you guys and it was a little bit long, but
Only joking we have a champ. Oh, I love legends. Hi everyone. Hey, hey, punkie. How are you?
Good. I was just reading
When the golden ass, I don't know if you've heard of the book, but
It's one of the oldest novels in the world pretty entertaining
It's been a good day
Yeah, I did just the guys didn't notice I did unmod everybody
Because the modding was causing too many
Too much controversy problem and people were being targeted for it. Like, you know, if they were like, oh
You know this one's doing this this one's doing that and people were like saying
Telling people that mods are doing that weren't doing it. It was just confusing. I don't want you guys to have any problems. I'll just all mod
You guys can hang out
How are you doing?
but
I will I have my book I can write you down in the book. I know that they ruined it
Yeah, that is like, you know, it's hard either a lot people would tell me either have no mods or
everyone's modded
because
But then it's hard to mod everybody because you don't know, you know, you don't really want to mod everybody. It's too much
Scribbles had done that the other day
He did it a few times before but he was like having a bad time the other day. He's like, wow
He's like, why are you timing people out? It sounded just like me. I was like, why are you telling people up?
Oh, I actually don't say that but
Somebody was though almost everyone was a mod in the room. Oh gosh
Yeah, this is why we can't have nice things
Yeah, but you know, I think it might be better though
Because I
Really want everyone to be able to say what they want to
Without worrying about oh, is this you know represent my right on my channel. It's like I
Shouldn't I should uh I
Should be the one worried about that
Hey, it's funky
So we're doing good
What are we doing? We have 30 people in the chat. Oh my gosh. I don't know. I don't know. It's like guys are just
so quiet
So I'll see the pictures I drew. Did you guys see the pictures I drew? I'll make this bigger
Hi Nikki, so I'll show I drew a picture of DJ Electra and then I was
of a
So here's DJ Electra
DJ Electra I
Need to fix a little bit like you know, I mean she does if she wearing a cape or something
But yes, she is tapered, but I need to fix a little bit. It's pretty good. You've got more than
One friend. Oh, thanks. We a punky
Like a jucati too. He didn't like the horns, but
I drew a picture of God. There's a bit banana. I tried to draw the moon
I think the sun and the moon didn't get donut in the banana, but and then it's a star. Okay
And then I have one of a row Nomad look at this one
This is a row Nomad
Give them peanut big muscles that's him from the front. So that's right his name still you guys
Well, I can trust I can draw sassy. I
Want to draw like no, I have like you want one too. Okay?
Do you want your Wolfman one, or do you want your normal one?
Kind of like a little small
Hi
I'm back. Oh, let me change my name. Wait, leave it like that.
The Wolfman, okay
Thank you
Okay, so what we were doing I just um, I just hopped right in straight from the link
Um, I didn't even I was I was reading I read the four chapters of the book
It was just it was really good. It's very I was on Miguel's page
And I would be was arguing with this dumb fuck but I left cuz he started to give me a headache
And I was like, let me go see what psyche's doing. Okay
Well, let's see so I go
Okay, so yeah, so I'm drawing a picture of Jayce now. He wants me to do a picture of him. He's still doing the wolf, man
I can like I can't really it's hard to see on either your profile picture. I know but it's small
Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which one? Which
That one, that one.
I'm gonna laugh at you.
He was doing it bad.
It's good art. It's still art. Art is art.
Okay, you'll like this
Good love as you live, okay. Yeah, okay. Okay, right now. I think I might be doing the same with a pendo
I didn't do it. I didn't do it properly. I mean, let me see if I can do it. I don't
No, I can't do it. I can't do it. Okay. I got a free thing to picture enjoy
Let me ask I wish I could do better off a little bit. Okay
Okay, I don't know I don't know I put the jacket on your home dirt that
You ready? Yeah, yeah, I had to write it on
Let me see I need I need to make up a nice. Yeah, I can't you up
Hmm, I'll put your just do the best you can psyche whatever. Let me go do with the pathway
Okay, okay, it's not that it's not for a pretty hot
They're ready to see
I
Yeah, that looks like the picture
I'm drinking that that low-gallon ice tea
On that Miami Beach, I
Like you're in like a revolutionary work code or something and that has
You know those Hawaii shirts that make you feel comfortable. That's one of those up. Okay. I'll put on Hawaiian flowers on it
Yeah, it's like a Hawaii shirt. I was like, oh, let me feel comfortable with the light shirts nice. It was like
Ten ninety nine, I believe
She's some flowers on yeah, you go perfect
They're good. I don't know you like it. Okay. It was nice. It's not like don't bother me. I got long hair. So, you know, it's really perfect
Okay, don't can't flick flick baby. I love when I do that when I try my head left to right
I go flick flick when I say that in my head turns
Okay, so it's not JT. Not JT has okay, so that's okay
All right, who we got next who's the next person in one drawer? What they stop doing? Oh
You want JT's profile picture? Oh, yeah, but he put it he now he put it up, but I just it's a
like another pace but it will be somewhat okay. The easier one will be woof for you like if you put
woof up for you that'll be easier for him. Well I think I found one let me see I can find one close.
But other than that I think I could I could draw probably some of them. I'm looking at all the
pictures now like I could probably draw some of these guys. I'll just stare at it all day like
Oh my gosh.
And I only draw with pens.
I only got a pen right now.
I don't feel like I ever draw with a pen.
I gotta take my time with race, make the lines,
train it out.
I do it over and over and over until I feel comfortable.
Did she got it? Did she gonna get it right now?
Doug you got to be the one right though
Can you not troll today?
Like please
Leave me alone
Don't tell somebody else who's on good shoulder and everybody else. I just came to support psyche leave me alone
Thank you, that's a lot
Okay, I think I got pretty much
He's a smiling wolf
Hold on I'll put his name on
Psyche you focus with your left eye a lot. You can tell because your right eye is squint
You know how you figure that out which one is your powerful eye you make a triangle with your hand and you bring it towards your face
Gradually your hands is gonna bring it to the stronger eye
Okay, I think I think I mean it's like I just pretty bad
Just uh, I see the shit. Okay ready GT. Let's see how you like this one. Let's go GT. Let's go
Killing balloons
Heart heart
Yeah, so the balloons because you don't see the rest of the picture so he got creative
Yeah, that's what art that's what art is about you got that little piece that you took it it made more
Yeah, I think that's pretty much that what do you think to you if you're free of okay good
I think I can darken. I'll do a little bit more of a wolf
face a little bit hair
There you go good, okay
nice, okay
I know
You saw my DJ Electra and my my Gotti. I was I was gone for a while. So I didn't get to see those
I was tell you I was just arguing with the guy from yesterday that you know the the the Greeks guy
Okay, well, here's DJ Electra guys DJ Electra
That's close to be honest, that's close
That's close and then here this one's a Gotti
I
Told you about the moon at the moon came out like a banana the sun kind of came like a doughnut, but see it still works
That look like a guy doesn't prove
That's it. Oh, thank you. Oh, then I do I do like
I only do one more I drew I drew a whole I need to write his name
The guy with the muscles. I've seen that one then I flipped over. Are you sorry?
I got to see. I got to see. Yeah. No, man. Yeah. I think he's behind this. I don't got
I don't got here, right? Something like that. Yeah. I think it's like it's like it's like
it's like his wife be there, but I just like dropped from. He looks like he looks more
like big danisha than he does. So it's kind of like big danisha, like a week to big
danisha because
It can be a big night because I used to if you look at it like far and if you look close it's like him
I don't know. Yeah, but a square in his chest because the picture
Oh, yeah, I
Didn't add a horse to Gotti and then I don't think he likes him, but I do like to do like those style horns. I
almost drew a I almost drew a
Tail okay, so I'll draw you dingle. Okay, you can draw a dingle real quick
Dingle, let's see. Let's see here. Dingle. That's easy. I can
Please calm it up, please calm it up
I didn't see that, I didn't see that, I didn't see that,
It's okay
Dingle you're working French girls is it's good fun single
No work
Okay, but more clear with the six six sixes, but just felt it felt it felt like a right touch. Okay. There we go
You're welcome. It's good
It's beautiful
Thank you
Yeah, I want to do a lot of you know, I have a lot of pages in this book and do a lot more
Can you draw my new profile picture?
Yeah, it's a small kind of evil what you like it thank you look a little up on my first
There you go
There you go Dingo. Oh
Very good
See now you guys are such an inspiration like it. No, I can draw a picture of anybody in here because you guys are
Well, it's your new profile pictures I mean you can draw it it is you
I didn't have an artistic bone in a body.
It doesn't work that way.
Yeah, I was, you know, you see,
you may see my art, you see, it's not like, you know,
it's not like the best, but I do like,
I do like to do some art.
You would love one?
Okay, yeah, I was gonna,
I wanted to do one for Sassy, that's Sassy.
Okay.
I don't know. I don't know.
Oh beautiful, I can't draw that
Just a cow, you know, I can't do that sassy. Yeah, good luck psyche
That's too much
Please you guys see yeah, I hope this is I don't
Chat chat chat chat shout out to the chat beat beat beat ready
You did the cowboy hat. I'm sure yeah, she got the cowboy hat. He said oh shit. That's how I zoomed in. I saw shit
That's too much detail for me
She had to be mad with the neck with the neck curly hair curly hair
Three buns with the neck thing all the way black with the curly blonde hair cowboy hats
Oh, I missed the is ding oh I could do it right now. Yeah, you see I didn't see that because the YouTube is in the way
So the YouTube blocked off the ear part. I didn't see that. That's why I didn't draw with the ear
I mean, the hair, I'm not sure about the hair and I'm afraid to get it right, I just need hair.
Christine, I could try my best. I'll look at your picture later and Joe Fossey.
Oh, off shit.
Oh my gosh. I'm so sorry. Sassy. I'm sorry. Oh my dear. Oh dear. I'm not good at like drawing. I don't think that
Oh my gosh
I can fix it I can fix it
Okay, I'm gonna put I can't put you in dark glasses. I'm gonna put you in dark glasses. Okay. I'm gonna put you in sunglasses
That's even mad at me. I don't even mad at me
Okay, you might be wearing a stove type a stove top hat, you know your hat's gonna be a little bit taller in the picture
But I
Think it worked
Gosh, okay.
Okay, Sassi, I mean, I'm sorry,
it's not one of my best, I need to write your name, huh?
But, hope you'd like it, I mean, at least, you know,
I just, I'm sorry if it doesn't, go first.
Okay, yeah, I'm really sorry. So I'm sorry sassy. Okay, so it's a sassy
Okay, I have you with a pitchfork and a lasso
I don't and it's how to do a jean jacket. I don't know if it turned out right. Hey, I
Sorry, I'm sorry
Okay
I try I'm sorry it was kind of small it was kind of it was perfect it's kind of it's kind of it's kind of
well it looks kind of small but yeah
okay I get perfect huh
hi Lily Ivy how are you you love it you're welcome
I was trying to get the cowboy hat.
It was almost perfectly shaped
and then I drew the sides too high
and so I just made it kind of a stale type hat.
Thank you, Dangle.
Yeah, it's fun to,
I like being able to do them real quick.
I don't have the patience
since they're for hours and hours.
I like kind of like the,
I think it's a cool style.
Yeah.
Thank you guys, let's see, 5.25, I need to...
Can you show mine again?
Yeah.
If you're showing people's again, just show everybody you made to let everybody know who got me and
From beginning to that day for all that is new this guy to you got home. There's guy there's DJ Lexra
Here's road nomad
And he's kind of like also big nature. He's a kind of road nomad from the front with his head in shade
But it's like or it can be big nature from behind
And then easy cameras on he's having his drink
JT the Wolfman
He's got he has a balloon for himself and a balloon for rain, right and then here's the angle
Yo, why he live like um, um Mike from monsters ink the sassy scarlet
Who's a devil who who dingle or um or or gaudy dingle looks like um Mike from monsters ink the one I got
Green yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. He was Ricky. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so I nice drawing psyche. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Oh JT he's not a devil. He's a wolf. He's the wolf man. He's like the wolf man
Right?
Some of them I was kind of like I had to do it from memory a little bit because it's a little small, but
Thank you guys, you know, you know, it's the days go on I'll do more
You have a whole collection of
Art from the whole room. Yeah, I think it but I was inspired kind of like, you know
Joker in Canada dry like just like being able to like, hey, I can draw a picture and they just were able to draw it and you know, I
Like them scary. They're scary. What do you think?
I think I'm gonna do it the BKG test you know what there's people that
Okay, there's people that have
name of
The people to get there they get there like someone's name cast you on them, right?
And then they are not friends with them or they break up with them
sometimes they say the text you still there and it's like because
It's like the love is still there. I
For me it might love the love is still there. I just feel like
Something happened, but this is the I don't know. I don't know what I don't know what she was doing. She was
It's just like he's out of character. It's just don't seem like it was this one. I hear it was me about to draw the Grinch
I ain't finished it for some reason. I don't know. I was drawing the Grinch very good
Love it. Yeah, no Jim carry grinch is scary, but okay, so is this it's fun to see that you guys drawing. Yeah
I mean if it ever bothers me someday
Yeah, but if it ever bothers me someday, I will
I don't know. It almost feels like a because like it almost feels like a I
Like it still
But you know there's ways to cover up. I'm not gonna have it removed. I'm just gonna I might have it altered
They'll always will always be there under everything spunky. Yeah
That's the obey I've always if you okay, let's see, huh
You if you could cross out the B and replace it with an E and you show off you can have electro
cardiograms with BG. Oh, I
Yeah, let's all the easy EKG. Yeah, it's okay
No, I don't know. Well, it'd be good if I ever had a hard second in the
Ambulance drivers needed instructions. I want to do but I think they're a priority. No, I would hope to
You know, well, you know my my last name starts with B. Okay, then
Okay or G my name
I don't know submit your ideas, please guys
Bring kill a game
Who's I mean who's what's going on who's talking thank you use those yeah bring kill a game or bring
Bring kill a game. Oh brain killer
No, I don't like that.
I don't know.
I don't like things to do with killing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's me.
I'm a little guy.
I go down crazy.
Um...
Let me see.
Uh...
Well, you know, it doesn't it doesn't matter. Whatever. This is letters. Whatever. Yeah, I forget
I actually like it so so so listen so B is
To right because B is the second letter of it and K is 11 because K is the 11th letter of it
So then and then G is ABC be FG so it's seven. So it's like two
One one seven, okay
Three eight three eight. I don't know it adds up to 11 somehow
I don't know. I
Don't really guys. I really don't care. I like you know, I have something like not great tattoos that I
Certainly fine with you know, the body's temporary thing, you know, not gonna pay for expensive tattoos and
You know, I don't know. Oh, can you stop you get annoyed?
Jesus I
Can't I can't I can't little piece would like Doug
Me I could dug that question
Okay, at least I'm up here support
Yeah, yeah, and it's like I think you appreciate that. I don't know. Yeah, so boss again, you want me to you know, I will like
Hell on the stop. I mean if you can listen to you, you know, hey dog, chill out. Don't talk about that. Okay
Now I want to finish this I gotta find a picture way out where I was drawing this fucking
This is grinch good now. I want to finish it the half complete artwork
Sike you got me filling the drawer. Yeah, I want to drill
Yeah, it's like
Yes, what's the quit? What'd you say?
So you got me filling the drawer now. I want to draw. Oh, yeah good your creative juices flowing
Okay
I
Can go through I'll have to go through the dictionary later and see other anagrams it creates
See, but you know, it's funny and look at like this notebook. I just noticed you know, it's funny
Look, look what I just grabbed this because it said be kind. Look look at it. It's fun. It's a bk on it right there
See, I know I remember you first showed me
Mm-hmm
Okay, well
And you need to hit the road a second
You gotta go you gotta get a tiny benefit all day
That little break you would go get some heat
No, I have it I haven't
Not yes, I I get cigars
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know what else.
Yeah, I smoked that weed so fast.
You smoked that weed? You smoked it in a bong?
No, I smoked it in a bong. I smoked it in a bong.
The first one is going to be the funniest.
Just make sure you leave the bong on the table when you take the hit.
First one's over, but be the surprise me. She said he put ice in her bog is the same shit. And I was like, really?
Yeah, I never did that I never did it that way
This is like a nice cool. That's cool air my friend put white liquor. It was rough
I see
What are you thinking about wet? What's what you think you're gonna have to get some food?
I'm gonna stop I'm gonna take my bike to the liquor store
But I can't go really good to store my bike because I don't like I don't want to leave it
How would you bring a book bag bring a book bag grab go find your book bag?
No, I mean I can I can I can carry the I can carry them on my arm
What if you get a nice plastic tough bag you get a nice tough bag ain't put it on the handlebars
You go tink tink tink a little bit, but that's about it. You go do no damage
No, I mean, I don't have a problem. I've done it before I can see I just put it on my
Let's put it on my
Yeah, that's hand for my arm. All right, are we out?
Okay
I'll be waiting away for the run now or somebody will come up in here and watch and hold it down with like you
Okay, I'll hang up. It's been pretty fucking good with the one-on-ones today like so
Anybody want to come? Yeah? All right. I'm coming up. I'm dropping down. I
Have it back quick. Thank you. I
Have a small one. It's just not a great one. Thank you
You guys like a
Yeah, have you heard of Sylvia Plath guys? She's a really good poet. So there's a poem.
Oh, yeah, I'm just gonna read a poem before I go.
It's Sylvia Plath.
Oh, I'll be gone in a couple minutes.
I'll take you with me on my bike. It says, it's called Lorelai or Lorelai.
That's Sylvia Plath. It said it is
No night to drown in a full moon river lapsing black beneath blend mere sheen
The blue water mist dropping
Scrim after scrim like fish nests
Though fishermen are sleeping
The massive castle turrets doubling themselves in a glass all swiftness yet these shapes float
Up toward me troubling the face
of quiet. From the nadir they rise, their limbs ponderous. With richness, hair, heavier
than sculpted marble, they sing of a world more full and clear than it can be. Sisters,
your song bears a burden too weighty for the whole ears listening. Here in the wealth-deared
Beyond the mundane order, your voice is laid siege, you lodge on the pitched reefs of nightmare.
Promising shore harbourage by day, the scans from borders of hibitude from the ledge.
Also of high windows, worse, even your maddening song, your silence.
At the source of your ice-hearted calling, drunkenness of the great depths,
O river, I see drifting, deep in your flux of silver.
Those great goddesses of peace, stone, stone, bury me down there.
This one's very short one. It's called Confusion. I've never read it.
Oh, Confusion. I'm sorry. Confusion says,
color floods to the spot, dull purple.
The rest of the body is all washed out, the color of pearl.
In a pit of rock, the sea sucks obsessively.
One hollows the whole sea's pivot.
The size of the fly the dewmark crawls down the wall the heart shuts the sea slides back the mirrors are sheeted
Done I don't want to ruin it. No, you can go. Yeah, I'm just gonna hear you reading. Yeah. Yeah, I mean
Okay, yeah, yeah, I'm cool. Thank you
What's the transfer?
Somebody said have a nice walks. Oh, yeah
Shafi said get a backpack
I do taste rule I say spell it taste rule
Get uh
This for who said it thing that it castles here
I think that is okay the tassels too. I want tassels
Like I want my bike like tewee tewee's big adventure. Well, that's a swing cruiser
It's kind of it's kind of cooler than my bike, but like my bike is very cool
Um, let's see
Okay, I'll read one. I got one. Oh shit. Okay, I'll do one more. Okay, one more. It's
just called the goat sucker. The goat sucker. It's very short. It says, old goat herds swear
The waning whirr and burring of the bird.
Who wakes with darkness until dawn works hard.
Vampiring dry of milk, each great goat works hard.
Moon full, moon dark, the charry daisy farmer.
Dreams that is bad as cattle, dwindle, fevered.
It's by clock-huts of the goat's sucker, alias devil bird.
It's eye, flashlight, a chip of ruby fire.
So fables say the goat's sucker, moves, masked from men's sight.
in an ebony air on wings of witchcloth.
Well-named, ill-famed, a naivish fly by night,
yet it never melts any goat nor dealt cow death.
And shadows only, cave, mouth, bristle, gesset,
cockchapers and the wand, green Luna moth.
Beautiful.
All righty
Damn, it's like
It's good. I'll share more with you later. I love poetry. I love
Not reading yeah, I'm reading you see that when you go up you instead of go playing and buying toys you
Yeah
I even like, you know, my dad would like drop me off the library because I just like loads read every book
But then the library and call the house. He's like he stopped dropping your son off here
He we're not the babysitters that you thought he was using as a babysitter, but
He likes to read books and he'll spend the day there
Yeah, and I really did he knew that but you know they were said there's such
You know these old lady librarians kind of grumpy
I hope you like that. I'll add more poems later for you guys. Um, let me see. Should I take you like that?
Yeah, that's funny stories that I always had bad luck like some libraries. I
like we never
That's how listening to it like what the fuck
Well, it was interesting
Never know we'll catch it somebody's eye like you be so one but you know the ghost so this is the goat sucker is a bird and
I say I don't know if it's really does this or not, but it's really scary it. Um, it basically
Rest speeds off the goat, but it has like a really sharp beak and so it's like it's probably it's what kind of like sucks the blood
Through the other instead of like, you know, it's kind of like a vampire bird. It's refreshing
Yeah, it's a nice day. So, okay, I'll go for a walk with the cat. Hold on. You can go if you want
He's gonna I'll just be with the I'll take my phone
I'd rather go. I'd rather go. I'd rather go let you hold it down by yourself. And you know before three
Yeah, and we'll be here for you. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Thank you so much a bed thing when you come back
If nobody comes up when you come back, I'll come back
Okay
Love ya
Oh
I forgot my mic lock, thanks.
It's scary, you gotta catch your mic lock by yourself.
Bye.
Okay.
I know I'm such a judgemental.
Very nice.
Bye.
Thank you
okay i'm back okay the thing about this bike is this bike is so fast like i can get to the
store in like five minutes instead of like 20 minutes okay 20 minutes walk five minutes
like there maybe 16 minute walk three minute back right okay here we go let's get past it go time
Brakes are a little squeaky.
Otherwise, it works perfect.
Hopefully fast.
First time I rode the bike, I like, I like swam up on the curb of this library, and I like crashed out of the grass.
I can't find my phone for like an hour.
I found it.
We're almost back.
Come on, James.
That was fast.
Hey guys, we're back.
We're back guys.
I'm home.
Hello
Good I thought it was a good ride
I think that is hi guys I break the three are speaking you're making my cats be very interested in the computer
I hope nobody jacks your phone. Yeah, but it would be y'all
Yeah, I'm good
Like I went to the store and like I forgot my my uh
I want to take you remember K hated on you for streamer all day
uh
For streaming all day. Oh, yeah, yeah, she's streaming all day, right? Let's get me this guy's like, you know
I'm gonna start streaming less actually, but you know, I probably just have some
long streams, but I'm gonna do like probably during the week I'll just
just do the evening streams and probably do like a few more
tarot. I'll do like a I'll do like a general tarot reading for the collective
in the chat and then do some you know some free readings and then I'll do
Maybe I safely yeah, I'm pretty good at my bike now
Yeah, let's see what's going on
Yeah, like easy suggests that I start having like topics to talk about and you know
I would I also do want to do one. Why don't you one more one-on-one things?
I want to like go out book interview like book interviews do more
But you know, it's like when there's so many people on the panel even though
I love having a lot of people on the panel and it's like if it's just like the right group. Yeah, it can be larger panels
but not like random panels like with like like 10 people like we were like it's just like first of all
it's too hectic and then people get mad because they can't talk and everyone's trying to talk and
then usually someone's rude and starts fighting with people and causing problems so
but yeah guys I didn't like my channel has always been crazy it can be chaotic yeah my channel but
well it's always been crazy you know I started in Benny Blanco who's from ip2 I started in his chat
As like I would just tear readings in his chat and you fall asleep for like hours
and I do tear readings for the chat and then I
Asked him if I could help me get to 50 subscribers
He he got me about 25 by asking a few times and then I
Went to their panels got I've had 50 pretty fast
Started doing like do me one last shim a week. I was like wow one hour a week one life shift. It was hard and then
By January, I I thought they stopped just live streams
I started the open panels and they were there were instantly like a lot of people there like or at least like the pounds were pretty full and
I've gone through waves of
Different situations and they're kind of like some of the situations are kind of been repeating but
you know
Give me now
And it's like it's happened pretty fast
Because I think by I think I had about 1,000 subscribers by the beginning by the year by January 1st
And then you need 3,000 to get monetized. I was like, I'll be monetized by about April. I think I was monetized in a February
Are you going to be writing the?
Writing the book during the day. Yeah, see this is my this is my book. I mean
It's gonna be several notebooks probably I already have like you know drawings of people I can include
Now this guy's kind of like more like typical to this part
You know off stuff probably like or maybe this will be bonus stuff from my show or something because I want to do about
You know, I want to include like a lot of the panel version that maybe I'll draw a picture
There are other panel or the panel people like some like one of the go my show like summer summer stuff
Yeah, but yeah, I will be also
you know, asking for little ideas and things like that
and suggestions for chapters or if you have a little quote
or you have a little blurb about the art of the troll
that you want me to include it.
And I think it'll be an awesome book.
I need to see it.
How does your GZ like with really big boobs?
I mean, there, that's fixed, that's fixed.
Okay, fixed up.
Yeah
But you know, it's like you give me now. It's like wow
I mean it's about fucking time I just started on something I've been like fucking I
Did really well during the 2020 because it's like almost
2000 readings on Etsy
And I have like really really good reviews there
But it's just Etsy all dried up for doing the tarot card readings once you two kind of took over plus my store on Etsy was called
Facebook changed the name to Meta, so I don't think that was good for my store either.
But everyone was like, I was just using an avatar doing that.
I was using a store logo and I have a picture of it.
So sometimes people would write reviews that would refer me as she or she was so nice and blah, blah, blah.
But I never corrected them.
So I told everyone I was taking my reviews on meta psyche.com and
Then I got a letter. Hello. There's a streamer named psyche claiming that he's you. I do you know this person?
I was like, yeah, because they
Because it looks like you're a woman
You know, I never look back the people were all had to like, oh, you're faking a fake reduce. This is crazy
Hey Sparky, let me see what the
Don't insult spunky, please
Spunky has a boyfriend and
Unless you let's you have a relationship where you can like say let me see your mouth and it's funny, but I can't imagine
You just bunkie to but I
Want to draw time well, I can draw time. I draw you time
Because you're one of my favorites too
oops
Hold on
Okay here happens
Time that you I can draw time if you're wearing a little bowl or scalp
My hat's need work, guys.
I need to do work on my hats.
My hats, they're not doing the best for me.
Sorry.
Okay, it's gonna be really abstract, okay, my friend?
Let's see.
He's like he's he has his hands up because he's so happy to he's like he's so happy to see
Me this is like you. I got I got you on he
How does it look? Okay.
I'm sorry if I don't get everything right on it.
Let's look at the color. Okay, let's see mine.
Do you really say, hey, like that?
I gave you a ninja star, something like that, or a star.
Maybe a shooting star.
Like yeah
That's the first you at home
I'll put a heart in your hand too
Hearts and stars got me lucky jobs. There we go. We like it
It's just fun guys
I hope I don't offend you.
Tommy, James, someday I'll draw you up
like one of my French girls.
If I had a French girl, but...
Are you feeling an art thing?
Thank you.
I wish I could draw better than a kindergartner.
It is.
Stick people level. Well, that's pretty much stick people. Yeah, you know, I do that in like two minutes
This is working to you to a French girl
Yeah, you know Rose McGowan that sounds good
Boji. Oh, how about that woman that's used to read there when this woman from Brazil called in and she was like her name was
Destiny, I think
Like I'm I'm in Brazil. She's like I'm a lesbian. I hate men. I don't like her bad
I guess and then summer's like hey, bitch eat my pussy or do you want to eat my pussy?
Oh, she's like, okay. It was really funny. You see that one. It was funny
There's what was the one morning recently
That just makes perfect. No one is born good to try. Yeah, but I'm 44. I mean, I should I should have practiced more
I mean, I those were quick and then those are cute if you're kind of like not caricature. Yeah, do you remember that? That was funny
Summer so over to Jariah. Oh, thank you
Oh, you know destiny you've heard a call on yes. Yeah, she called in for probably but a little over an hour
But by the end of the call
She loved America. She loved this. She loved this at the beginning of the car. She's like fuck man. Fuck you
She was yelling and we're like why'd you drink bitch?
So we're like why'd you have to drink bitch?
Like I got a bottle of cognac
She's like how much is that? It's just a little bit
Yeah, hey babes
Yeah, so
I feel you know, I feel like a 21st. Oh, so that was just right. Hey, it's you and men in America. Yes
It's good. That's the impression. Oh, yeah
But I thought about you know the this summer stalls this
Right, which is the 21st, which is just yesterday, right?
So that's you know, there's there's these four solstice or you know, the winter solstice summer solstice and then the equinox I think right solstice is an equinox is and
It's like a wheel. It's like the insect the zodiac wheel goes to the wheel of the
student before then you got
the
That wheel right hey, baby
So
It's like
Every time so it's like entering a new season is like it's like entering the new cycle. Okay, so it's it is a
Be just a new beginning. That's why I think things get chaotic at the beginning of
Love it. Oh, let me talk. Let me talk
Yeah, she was just funny. You've had something like I've had some crazy guests
I had to say emcee like okay, so so many guys that would like come out of the closet on the show like
and like
Like a lot like it more than I thought and it's like even if they like are joking still a lot
So I mean they used to complain that I would hit on guys and then it's like now. It's like I don't even have to like
Did they they'll hit on me first and then I'll know I'm allowed to hit on
But before I would like yeah, it's I was like hit on I would hit on avatars
It's like so it's like people would be people be like oh my god
You're you're harassing me as like I can't how do I harass an avatar and it's like
I just don't know. I don't think you'd be a 600 pound man in a kiddie pool in the basement. I don't know, you know, right?
We need
Justine, yeah
Hey guys, if you know if you know somebody that would like to show just let them know and like, you know, maybe like you have like
If there are, you know, contact them and stuff,
send them my link when there's a panel.
I'll do free terror readings.
Yeah, and, you know, just, like, there's, like that, okay.
So that they, there's some people that,
they kind of scare, like, not scare me, but it's like,
okay, so that they, I don't know if she's listening.
And, you know, and I like you.
But Russ, she was Russie was funny. It's just like she was
She's she was fine
That she was I think she would I think she would get uh, I
Don't think she likes the show very much
But it's funny. She doesn't she was she's like hi. Why are you not allowed to stay in the n-word chair?
And they're fighting over the heart you are in the soft a oh god that fight is my nightmare
But she's great, but it's like yes, you know, it's funny as hell. He's like
He's like, why did he get to say?
NIGG I can't say NIGG ER. That's not fair. He's like, you're right. I don't care
She's like, oh Trump
That's part it's funny itself, but uh
Oh, I'm sure it's just the you know, it's uh, and then who is someone who has a puppet of I mean, that's some of these things guys I
Like I consider
Yeah, it's funny
Yeah
It's like, you know, and it's just like, you know, they can they can be funny and fun
But they can be unpredictable, you know, you know, and then you piss them off at the wrong time
All of a sudden you've got the car keys stuck stuck in your head or something. I don't I don't know
Maybe I'm sure she hasn't
Never done anything but
Yeah, I think you're kind of kind of mad at my show but I know
She said and there was like everything. Oh, they followed us here. They followed us. Yeah
Like who follows you? Where's you here?
Then it's like, I don't know. I've known for five years and she has been kind to you
Yeah, I mean she was kind of kind kind but then you know, I guess and she got kind of mad on the
What was he doing on the on the panel?
People give gossip then run around person is bad or good. No, no, but but miss Liz that I say
Rest is bad rest is good. I said, I
Said she's funny. It's like I think she's a little unpredictable
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know if the she was kind of like writing create some weird stuff in the backchats
I don't know if you heard about it without really knowing five years of
Oh, yeah, but that's what I'm saying.
Well, I can't, I mean, gosh, you know,
I wish I had times learned the chronicles of the,
if it was my panel alone,
it would take a lifetime to go through all the people's,
it's like too much.
I wanna, so I have to kind of go by the first impression.
I like her, I like her, I'm not sure she likes me,
I'm not sure.
Everybody guys yeah, and then she's also like you know a little bit
She was uh, I don't know trust me sure some weird stuff in the back shit, but she's fine. Okay, so
Yeah
Yeah, that's like really like as long as someone's respectful to me. I will
Always be respectful to that. And even if they're not respectful to me. I'll try to be respectful to them
but you know, I can't get a little I
Have a little bit of fight in me, too, but not, you know, just like arguing a little bit of a
Because it's like, you know, I was a lot of times my only defender, so I kind of like
I have this part of myself to protect those.
Wow, we've had such an amazing,
people in my chat have the strangest names.
It's easier that way navigating the group.
Yeah.
Yeah, but then again, it's like, yeah.
And I bet it's like I would you know
As long as it's like if people will treat you away, they'll treat you away even for a certain amount of time and
Then they'll flip on you
Right. I don't say no, but you're supposed to flip on them back or just like or just be confused
That's kind of what happened with me. That's kind of confused like why are you?
staying horrible things about me and
Call me horrible things and hate me
I don't know
But yes, or treat others like you would like to be treated and so always be kind
That being kind is like
Not like it's not like being oh
You know, so, you know, just like love bomb and give everything and over the top gift. It's like be nice. It's
Hi, you're knowledge in someone. Hi. How are you? How's you know?
Yeah, saying I love you once in a while
Go date her and then talk to other women at the same time. You'll get the
We'll get doctor after yeah, I think I'll avoid that she may
She nice to you, but it
Didn't say no. She's nice to you. Yeah
Sorry, okay. Hey punky
Okay, this is important. Yes kindness. You may be kind but don't be taken advantage of yes funky. I
Because I was reading the because there's certain people
Like there's a that they
There's looking to take and so they'll find kind people and they'll ask kind people
Because kind people will feel unkind if they don't
reciprocate or or do is kind of ass and so it's kind of like
They can they kind of can be against somebody. So it's like, yeah, so you have to be firm and no means no
And they say it I say I'll have to say it in a kind way
Yeah
See I had I had too much patience for especially for people that were like not
on my side or not at my show side that doesn't want to
This basically basically my show is just collateral damage or inconsequential stuff. What's wrong with you made it ball humbug? I
Okay, let's see
Let's patterns like anyone else. I know I know this but you know it's like uh, there's I mean there's but there's a little there's some I
Think you might I think I don't know. I don't know everybody's history, but I think who wants to be the serial dog
Think for yourself and be allowed. I feel it will cheer me to a few mature moves. Yeah, I think for myself
the thing what like I was like
First of the first six months my show it will be a big experiment I
Will throw everything at the show, but the kitchen sink and I will I will try I will let everybody on
that I can I will I
Be patient gracious night. I will I will and I say I will not I will not do anyone wrong
Because I don't anyway, right, but I was like I
Will
Make me kind to everybody. I won't I won't be bad to anybody
and I was and
It did not work out here. There's a lot of people
taught me like a
Yeah, no, I mean, I think it's fine. But I don't care. It's like, there's like, you know, there's suggestions and there's like, you should do that, or, or you have to do that. So it's like, and people haven't really been doing that.
Where is it coming on the panel and stuff?
The word spunky also means good-looking and I'll show you well
I can I can do something really entertaining for you guys. Let me see. There's this website. You know, it's Urban Dictionary
And they have we've done these before they have these name descriptions, and that's kind of interesting
They're always like come out kind of accurate. So
So punky, very punky. Let me see if punky the name comes up.
Okay. Let's see. Okay, punky is beautiful. Hold on. Shit. I agree. I agree so far. Hold on.
Okay. It says punky is beautiful.
Punky is smart. Punky is artistic. Punky is kind. Punky is adoring. Punky is loyal.
Punky is the most attractive person you will ever meet. Yes, she has some things going on with herself.
That doesn't suffer from making everyone else smile.
She's hype and fucking crazy. She has dark green eyes with long thick eyelashes. She has short...
Curly-ish hair bangs and when she drinks she's a vibe as fuck. She's high on oh my gosh
She's fucking out there laughing and dancing around. She's very protective of her best friend
She will let nobody break her emotionally spiritually mentally and definitely not physically
She's a little Angus bitch. Sometimes her anger can go from one
To for life in prison ha ha ha she'll always have your back and fight by your sides who's thick and thin
This is girl one. Who's that chick real to you? I think that's punky. She got expelled from school like last week
real one what four and
Then girls who says a typical fighting ha
That's it. Does that make sense? I don't I don't know. I know it's physical. You love it. Yeah, I think I think it's cute
Let me see. Liz. I'll do I'll do Liz next Liz. You want yours? Oh, there's
Say about Liz. You're in the dictionary. So it's Liz
Someone who's beautiful, talented and almost always really smart. Occasionally, there may be stubborn and persistently attempting to prove their point, but with always good reasoning. So consider it that even when the situation is not really hilarious, a list lasts a lot of things, but when it is funny, it begins to crack up.
A Liz is often correct and competitive, most of the time a Liz also wins.
The only downside to a Liz is that she may be a sore loser and not know when to give
up.
They are defined as know-it-alls and often confused with the term little Einstein.
They are athletic, amazing, outgoing people.
They can be flexible too.
They have a total desire to be filling themselves with chocolate every second of every day and
have a strong hate towards white chocolate.
Video games, but continuously moving and preferably playing outside
Liz is our door by many people and enjoy challenges anything related to academics and most of all time
favors the subjects of Jim
Okay
Your big fire you also defend your loved ones. Yes, mama bear. Yeah, I can sense that yeah
It would be like that.
JT, I mean, I don't know if there's a JT.
I'm going to see if there's a JT or else I have to ask for a JT.
OK.
Okay, so here's, it says JT, it says an amazing masterpiece of a man known to be a lion in
the sheets with the women.
He has a bad-ass attitude because of his hard life, yet is still romantic and a seducer
at heart, and the ladies' thighs become wet when they are around him.
His intelligence is profound, his physical body sensual and divine, his presence dominates
everything in his sight, and he makes your world a better place for happiness in your
life.
He is JT, nothing else needs to be said.
Who is that? That's JT. Silent while Fanna says you met her stuff with a JT and girl number two and amazing sensual pleasures.
Well, that was strange. You're welcome.
Yeah, if you put a wolf in the sheets, I'd be shocked. Okay, so Vader, let me see if Vader's in here.
Are you in here, Vader?
I don't know if it's
Vader a person who intends to have sex with a stranger at a party
Verb to engage with sexual activities with a stranger offer often under the influence of drugs or alcohol
I know I promise to be good, but with that girl around it's hard not to be a Vader
Man, I'm so buzzed. I think I'm gonna go Vader on Sasha
little examples
Good Vader or it also says
A Vader's also a 400-pound wrestler capable of Moonsault, I don't think that means
Anybody there
Good thing I got everybody but I'll be one of mine, but I was after you for my real name
That's the...
Of course, my name is very common, but...
Okay, yeah, okay, so I guess it's John, it says...
A very sweet, caring, loving, attached, and compassionate person.
You can and will never fight with them.
He has his head in his heart in place and is totally committed to everything he does.
He will never take you for granted.
He will make you smile, care for your likes and dislikes.
He will always make you smile.
He's a very charming and funny person.
He is perfect.
He's a soldier.
He deserves to be loved and cherished.
Never let him go.
He's the one.
That's a little bit.
A little bit about the top.
Let me see.
There's more.
I remember a red one, I remember a red one once and it was the kind of like more accurate, but
I don't remember
John the weirdest most confusing person you'll ever meet when he's talking he will just stop at any random time
He's a very large penis has a friend whose name is an anonymous who jacks off a lot
Yeah, John is also a man whose black hair never wears shoes and mood changes easily
Never matches Harry arms very sexy and other guys with gels. Oh, yeah
I didn't mention his big dick, but he cannot describe anything worth the shit because he always says things like theme of Bob and think of a jig
Oh, he's a huge penis. What was that huge crash in scream? I heard
John oh the thing of a Bob did that one thing at the thing of a jig at that one time with those people. Oh
I don't know. Maybe it doesn't
Hey boots and boots here
Hi guys
Rusty, I was just talking about you.
You hear me talking about you.
I was talking nice about you.
Rusty, do you want me to draw a picture of you?
I drew JT.
I think it's a hoodie.
I drew...
No.
Oh, hold on.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, how'd you God too? You see God?
Hi, I just having a little fun. I don't know if you saw DJ Electra. She was so sure. Hi
I'm gonna drop anybody that wants to be I'm gonna fill up the book with drawings
I'll probably get better at them too. It's just like little like the God you are. Yeah
He they had a profile picture of like, you know, the like the old big God was an old man kind of picture
Yeah, I tried to draw I tried to draw a moon and I think it's the Sun of the moon
And then it's just I just changed it to like a banana and a donut. I thought it did better
Draw you okay, of course
Oh, yeah, I can make it bigger, huh? Okay, I got you
Okay, let's see.
Oh my gosh, it's, I like really, oh, yeah.
Have fun doing it, okay, hold on, I got it, I got it.
Yeah, remember, these are very,
these might be a little bit,
there's a very hand-drawn, I hope you like it though.
I don't like it
Contour
I think, I don't know if I just can't do it too.
Aye aye aye, I think I got it here.
Give a symbol. Can I add a symbol? It's funky. Like what's in your favorite symbol that she gets to give a symbol like, you know, whatever
You might find in your hand at any time
Yeah, I'm giving you two hearts
Good to have hearts. Okay
You're holding it you're holding hearts in these hands, okay
I hope it's okay. I mean, it's like I hope it's not awful me
Okay, and
Okay, I'm trying to be a little alien thing there too,
because then he's,
it looks like kind of like,
it looks like kind of like jarb jarb being some storage.
It's going to be like, it's kind of random, I said that.
I didn't put your name, and that's like,
I'll put your name here, huh?
Not perfect. Okay.
I'm drawing some, okay, I'm drawing some heaped arrows on the other side.
One coming toward you, one going.
Okay, I'll put a little face on them.
Okay, ready? Okay. I hope you're on that. Don't get mad. Don't get mad
I'm sorry, so you're holding the hearts you're holding I keep you're holding it when you can't I'm sorry. I'm sorry I
Try it's hard to
It's hard to be
I'm trying to get, yeah, I'm trying to get a beautiful smile.
Ah!
I like, I tried to do like, I thought I put the,
I was writing your name, but I put P-U, P-U-N-K-Y
instead of S-P-U, and so I had to change
it's like a little jar jar of bigs, like alien,
like looking at you.
That's good!
So, it kind of looks like a face there, too.
It's like there's a face there, too, but it's a heart.
I don't know.
It kind of looks like that.
Doesn't it kind of look like that with the eye open?
I don't know.
Maybe I'm really, I don't know.
I was really trying to do that,
but I love when those things like that happen.
So, this is going good.
I think it's a good bond that you have here.
I am, you're the king of nightmares.
Yeah.
The thing of nightmares, well
You know, I my favorite movie when I was a kid with nightmare on the street and
Or any I like a lot of movies, but I just thought I loved the I'm around streets and
Always love horror movies
Watched a lot. Yeah, I watched a lot of TV I watched a lot of TV and read a lot of books, but I didn't play with me twice
Yeah, I love to read. I'd always be like have my nose in the book. Oh
That is
Fuck you look you look happy. Yeah, you look happy. You still watch nightmare on L Street
Yeah, you know it's interesting. It's like, you know the first time around to the first classic Johnny Depp and
But the second I'm around the street was like
It was like actually like it's actually a gay theme Nightmare on the Street
But it wasn't trying to be but it's like if you look back on it. It's a very gay movie
Well, there's a few gay things in it
The guy's constantly questioning a sexuality movie. He like you know Freddy starts becoming him. He like
He's the best best friend is some girl, but I don't think they ever hook up
He's actually in love with his guy, friend from a soccer team, I don't know, and he also does a scene where he goes to a gay bar in the middle of the night and then his coach is there like in a leather gear outfit and then takes him to the school and then, do you remember that one?
Well, it's like the first few were
First couple were kind of scary and then they started getting kind of a little bit campy like the Friday make
Like you know for the first couple movies you could barely see Freddy's always in the shadows
It's like dark and burnt and then then it then it just put him in this ridiculous like
the
Makeup started getting less and less less and less
Realistic it looks pretty weird, but yeah
Yeah
I was we were always allowed to like
Run any move we wanted
Mmm, ah, what are you guys up to? Oh shit my phone's not been charging. Oh
Yeah, there's been you know
It's been actually a really good day. It's like
Sometimes after it's in tarot, there's like that
There's a tower card and the tower card can kind of like, you know be like some kind of like
Just like shocking event you feel everything's falling apart and yeah, sometimes there you know, everyone in life has these
these horrible events and some are some are
You know tragedy some are just like, you know, just shake ups or unexpected things, but the thing is
That's always creates room for something new finding a funny back
You're finally back home and hanging out with dogs and cats. They miss you. Yeah, I got hey
I got tricks is right there. I'm sure tricks here right there and then
Lola's right there lowly right there and Rudy's right there
It's really warm. I think Lenore's outside. Oh
I did love they love you. Yeah
Hey gameies, how are you?
She's outside I think
Yeah
She's here this morning. Thank you. Yeah
They're sweet
This little guy
I've had like three I've had three letters of kittens and I have out of the first letter. I have one of them second
There was one that
Doesn't like to come inside them. You think Lola's one of the name of
one of
Yeah, those right here. Oh, yeah, you're the RBF come here. I say hi. Oh
Okay, oh
Oh, I woke you up, I'm sorry
I wake you up
No
She's so yeah, it's the last like you know, she
Was like hardly ever be in the house because my black cat would like chase her out all the time
But then she started coming back and she I noticed she was pregnant. She started to be bigger and bigger and
She actually gave birth last year on pie day. So it's March 14th. So it's 3.14 is pie, you know
So they were born on Pi Day.
Actually, when I named, there was a couple of tuxedos.
I named one of them Pi when tuxed.
And then there was tricks, but we all said,
and there's also one with like kind of similar,
but he had more just the paws were white.
Like I named him a magic.
He disappeared.
And there was a striped one.
Sometimes the kid is going to the neighborhood, yeah.
But Lola likes to go into covers
and then we're using the table right there.
That's what I just woke up to see at that. Yeah, that Lola has beautiful green eyes. She's got green eyes, too
He had some green eyes, too. Oh
You got Nightmare on the Street was a comedy. Yeah, I mean that's because I mean the first one is not a comedy
You'll watch the very first one that is scary
But it's also if you after you've watched the movies after that you probably won't think it's that scary because it's not like
It's not over-the-top scary, but it was first time it was very
Here I think it's the most realistic one too because then they go into like all this special effects where they're
Turning Freddy into like these big
Different like kind of claymation type of characters and stuff. I catch that yellow blue eyes. Yeah, all beautiful
But they are pretty much comedy like they gave Freddie these one-liners. It's like it was like, you know
That he the kills kill somebody and then he'd be like
He's like in a certain way that he make a stupid joke about that's that's what I call a hot pizza
There's nothing like that or spicy meatball and you have like a
you turn them all the soldiers and meatballs on his pizza remember that one and they also scare you can't
sleep without him killing you well you know or yeah that's actually yeah I
would think like with if you get if you could kill them in your dream you die
in real life or if you get hurt you're dreaming drama so so I didn't know if you
were here but I woke up I'll show you this one I look up probably a month to
go
okay probably a month to go
And I had just been asleep for a few hours and I wasn't I didn't fall asleep drunk
I
Went to bed pretty late, but I woke up and I had this like burn like a burn on my arm
And it's the scar is still there, but do you want to see the burn?
But I woke up and I was like, oh you do that to yourself. I swear I woke up with it
There's nothing that could have done it like I don't sleep walk or anything. I don't remember how this happened, okay?
But here it is, this is what it looks like.
I'm sure you can still see it, it's kind of there still.
Yeah, and you know, they based a lot of,
I remember on the street they based it on like Tibetan,
like dream mythology,
because there is like a kind of Tibetan dream yoga
where they do see these very burn looking,
Yeah, we well, you're dreaming about
Being burned. Well, I will the when I woke up the first thing I thought was ready. No, I thought no
I kind of like vaguely remember when I woke up
It was like in that was in that scary boiler room and I like put my arm down and then I like I woke up and I was there
But I don't know happens
See you was hanging at high in Piper's for you earlier today. Oh good
Did anybody see Bita last night?
Because Bita, wow, I mean, it's like,
Bita hates me.
It's like, isn't that sad?
Like, we love you so much.
I still love her, but she said something
like pretty terrible things to me.
And like, it's not reasonable or,
I don't know.
One of those,
One of those every day every other day person's mad at me
It's hard especially for it with a friend, you know, I understand if you're like dating and then we're gonna fight all the time like that
your friends
But again, so she is yeah, but when you're friends
You don't want to be fighting every other day, but it hits you because you
Okay
Oh, thank you my star has fallen that's why she hates me because my star has fallen
You down to 17 views. Well, yeah, I've been on for seven hours and you know, I've just got back from the store
So you don't know what you're talking about buddy
Kick rocks
Oh, yeah, so yeah
Pick yourself up and keep going.
Yeah, it's not, now there's 21 people.
I mean, it's like the numbers go up and down all the time.
You know, it has been a quiet thing,
but it's like, I wanted a calmer panel anyway,
and it's like, it's better if I have one at a time.
You know, people always come and say,
they're like, oh, you're nothing streamer.
You have these seven views.
I'm like, well, I literally had like,
I just been in the room for one minute that time.
I was like, give me a few minutes.
And it's like, and I was like,
I'm not saying I'm a big streamer.
You know, I've I've gotten over a hundred people a few times in the in the chat
But yeah, usually it's like, you know, it'll be probably between 30 and 60 maybe a little time a little more but
If I get a great group, that's plenty of people that can be a great. Yeah, let's draw no less views but better vibes
Yeah, I think it's a better trade-off because I'm not really like
Going after the views are important to me
Like I don't care about the number of views because I already had enough number of views and watch hours to get monetized
So it's like I don't really put ads in my videos
And so it's not doesn't really matter how many views it gets
You know, I just don't want to be shadow banned. I do want to you know peer in the
To give and take yeah
Just make a crazy title something. Yeah
I know but I
Gotta think I gotta think
Yeah, I gotta think of a good one. Hey, Benny would always do like he'd name his stream mr. Beast and stuff like that and I
Don't know he said he thinks he's like some algorithm wizard, but yeah, I have more people in my chat than Benny does
anymore like
Cuz he's he got shadow band cuz he said the n word like a hundred times in a minute
And that other stuff and then all of a sudden nobody like there's nobody's chat anymore
Long to view okay, so it says I
Get the same thing nobody watches you there. I don't seem I get to give you that
Scheme to get there for those people like daughter of shoes. Oh cool
Take a look I take that back so may stumble several times, but it's more how many times
One
Regains their balance and stands back up, right? You know, and you know what that also reminds me of it's like sometimes
Someone will fall down
You know, and then it's like are you know like laugh at them?
Are you gonna come?
Kick him kick him even further down
You know push them down the bone down the hill or you know like you know try to lift them back up and like you know
You don't know
Pet I'm saying
This it goes along the same lines of you don't have to help somebody but just don't hurt them and that's just like
Like the philosophy
Because
Hey, what's up, sorry your spot. Oh, it's okay. No, no, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to
It's about the road comment. I'm sorry
Yeah
No, hello, it's okay. So you want me to like, you know, I
Don't I don't I don't want to do political stuff. I think those are
Things I get people on a little bit of trouble. Why don't you assume of the protests because I?
Can't get over there. I mean, but on the car. It's probably dangerous
When scribbles went there, like when it started,
someone got shot and someone got raided by a car
and he caught it on camera.
So I'm sure that's good, but you can't even show that.
Everyone out of the pool and it's Epidas.
What does that mean?
It's let's yag there.
I can't I don't go into be this chat and then I don't think you know was talking about a pan
so
Everyone's welcome to go over there, and it's like if you can come back and tell me give me a report
You know don't but yeah
Yeah, you'd be the great person. It's like, you know, I don't care. She hates me. She's she hates me. She does
Well, I don't think she should hate me but
That's okay. That's a risk and then there's stupidity
The fuck life with it. Yeah
Yeah, I know I like to I
Just I mean I just can't I just not gonna ride my bike over there
They wouldn't be funny thing if I like wrote my bike or there's a speedo and then I show up
I predict like a gay parade sign and like I so I think hey
I thought it was a gay parade or through the protest and like I'll get arrested in my speedo. That'd be funny
Hey, babe
Yeah, I don't know I need to find there's not that much stuff to do around here
there's actually one gay bar in redondo and
if you
If you faint in the day of adversity, your strength is small.
The righteous falls seven times and rise again,
but the wicked stumble in times of calamity.
Yeah.
Yes, a big rainbow flag, yeah.
And it's like that's like that was like kind of like we did this I did a whoo-hoo reading last night
And it was like is like no matter how much you feel like you're under attack is like just keep going keep going
It's like it's just don't give up, right?
There's also there's an ancestors card saying like ancestors are
Looking out for us. We're like their grandchildren. It's it and it's simple. Yeah, I like I love it
No bring a Mexican flag, right? I know but it would be I pretend I'd go over there
I'd be like hey, where's the gay parade and they'd be like why worry everyone would be confused
Yeah
Well, do you know if there's a good poem? I don't know if you've heard this poem you probably have it's like a very famous poem
But it's another
Good thing it's a thing to think about you know to strive for
For me at least you know
Okay, let's see, I feel like it's protected by, yeah, oh yeah.
Definitely are.
The ancestry is really interesting to get into.
I wanted to answer this.com, I found all these photos of my family.
Do you want to hear it at home?
Okay, it says, I'll read it.
No, you go over there and stay. I'm here to fight. No, I'm not going to do that kids. No, okay
You understand Joe. Are you trying to get me deported to Mexico? Yo, please
You're trying to get me deported to Mexico
Unless it's Puerto Vallarta. I'm not interested. Okay, so it's called if by rogue yard keepling
It said if you can keep your head
When all about you are losing theirs and blame me it on you if you can trust yourself when all men doubt you
But make allowance for their doubting too
If you can wait and not be tired by waiting or being lied about don't deal in lies or being hated
Don't give way to hating
And yet, don't look too good or talk to eyes, if you can dream and not make dreams your
master, if you can thank and not make thoughts your aim, if you can meet triumph and disaster,
and treat those two imposters just the same.
If you can bear to hear the truth you've spoken, twisted by knaves to make a trap for fools,
stoop and build them up with worn out tools. If you can make one heap of all your winnings and
risk it on one turn of pitch and toss and lose and start again at your beginnings and never breathe
a word about your loss, if you can enforce your heart and nerve and sinew to serve you
Your turn long after they're gone and so hold on when there's nothing in you
Except the will which says to them hold on
If you can talk with crowds and keep your virtue or walk with Kings nor lose the common touch
If neither foes nor loving friends can hurt you if all men count with you, but none too much
You if you can fill the unforgiving minutes with 60 seconds worth of distance run
Yours is earth and everything that's in it and which is more you'll be a man my son
Good
So good
That's good, huh?
Yeah, it just came to mind, you know?
You know, I really enjoy Sylvia Plath.
She was kind of a tragic figure,
Sure, it's some amazing poetry. Let's see. Okay. Um
This is called the colossus, right? Life can get really rough, but you just gotta have to go through it. Yeah
You have to go through it to kids or like Daniel alliance then, right?
But you know, look, you know, I was starting to alliance then I hope I could like, you know
Cut out alive too because I think the cats would like me but
I don't know the Colossus I shall never put you together entirely
He's glued and properly jointed
male mule bray pig grunt and hottie and body cockles
Proceed from your great lifts. It's worse than a barnyard
Perhaps you consider yourself an oracle mouthpiece of the dead or some God or others 30 years now
I have labored to dredge the
Silt from your throat. I am none the wiser
Scaling little ladders with glue pots and
Pails of Lysol. I crawl like an ant in the morning over the weedy acres of your brow
To mend the immense skull plates and clear the bald white tomb oil to mooly of your eyes a
blue sky out of
honesty
Or hysteria, arches above us, O father, all by yourself,
You are pity and historical as the Roman Forum.
I open my lunch on a hill of black cypresses,
Your fluted bones and acamp-themed hair are littered.
And their old anarchy to this horizon line,
It would make them, it would take more than lightning smoke
To create such a ruin.
Nights I squat in the cornucopia of your left ear out of the wind
Counting the red stars and those of plum color the sun rises under the pillow of your tongue my hours are
Married to a shadow
No longer do I listen for the scrape of a keel only the blank stones of the landing?
That's a little bit dark
Mmm. Oh
We're just like my elms tree and there's a poem called elm
I have it, okay
Yeah, so
Which I like about Sylvia Plath is that just listen to like the way the words sound is just like
Beautiful. I know
It's called the elements. I know the bottom. She says I know it with my great tap roots
It is what you fear. I do not fear it. I have been there
Is it to see you here in me, it's the satisfaction, or the voice of nothing, that was your madness.
Love is a shadow, how you lie and cry after it. Listen.
These are its hooves, it has gone off like a horse.
All night I shall gallop thus, impetuously, till your head is a stone, your pillow a little turf, echoing echoing.
Or shall I bring you the sound of poisons?
This is rain hush, this is rain now, the big hush,
and this is the fruit of it, tin white, like arsenic.
I have suffered the atrocity of sunsets,
scorched to the root, my red filaments burn and stand,
a hand of wires.
Now I pick up the pieces that fly about like clubs.
A wind of such violence will tolerate no bystanding.
I must shriek.
The moon, also, is merciless.
She would drag me, cruelly being barren.
Her radiance scratches me, or perhaps I have caught her.
I let her go, I let her go, diminished in flask, as after radical surgery.
How your bad dreams possess an endow me.
I am inhabited by a cry. Nightly it flaps out, looking with its hooks for something
to love. I am terrified by this dark thing that sleeps with me. All day I feel the soft
feathery turnings and the lignity. Clouds pass and disperse. Are these the faces of
love, these pale irretrievables? Is it for such I agitate my heart? I am incapable of
What is this? This face, so murderous in the strangle of branches.
It's sneaky ass and hiss, it petrifies the will.
These are the isolate, slow faults that kill, that kill, that kill.
Yeah, she's very dark, you know, she was kind of, oh, this, oh,
Ella Mason and her 11 cats.
That sounds good.
I think I've had 11 cats at one time.
This is for sure.
Okay, it says Ella Mason and her 11 cats.
Old Ella Mason keeps cats, 11 at last count,
in her ramshackle house of some rich parents.
People make queries on seeing our neighbor's cat haunt,
saying something's addled in a woman
who accommodates that many cats.
Raman red faces the watermelon her voice long gone to wheeze and seed
Elemason or no good reason plays hostess the tabby
Tom and increase with cream and chicken gut feasting the pallets of pinnacle cats
Hi guys
She sits at the motions you don't know are there right?
Yeah, just look at them
It chills
There are a few more. Okay, this one is called
This is called eavesdropper eavesdropper it says your brother will trim my hedges they darken your house
Noisy grower mull on my shoulder to be scratched
Absently to bleed if it comes to that the stain of the tropics still yearnness on you a sin a
kind of bush stink
You may be local, but that yellow got awful.
Your body won long nicotine finger.
Ooh, creepy.
Okay, one more, Ariel.
This is called Ariel, I think I love this one.
That's one of my favorites, okay.
Ariel says, stasis in darkness,
then the substance is blue.
substanceless blue, poor of poor and distances, God's lioness, how one we grow, pivot off
heel the knees, the furrow, splits and passes, sister no, the brown arc of the neck I cannot
catch.
Oh, gosh, it has the N-word, N-word I, Barry's cat-dark hooks, black sweet blood mouthfuls,
shadows, something else, hauls me through air.
Thies, hair, flakes for my heels, White Godiva, I am teal, dead hand, dead stringencies,
And now I foam to eat a glitter of seas, The child's cry melts in the wall, and I am
The arrow that drew the flies To a S-U-I-C-I-D-A-L,
At one with a drive into the red, I, the cauldron of morning.
Okay, all right. I found a few more. Okay
Do you like it or is it crazy? I remember you said you love a little mermaid. Yep
Okay
I do I love and I love mythology too. I love concerts in Anderson Grimm's brothers and
maybe like the Disney movies
This is called two sisters of Persephone
Two girls there are within the house one sits the other without
Day long, a duet of shade and light lays between these.
In her darkened, wane-scouted room, the first works problems on a mathematical machine,
dry ticks mark time.
As she calculates each sum, at this barren enterprise, rat shrewd go her squint eyes,
root pale her meager frame, bronze says earth, second lies, hearing ticks blown gold, like
Lulled near bed of poppies, she sees how their silk-red flare of petaled blood burns open
to Sun's blade on that green altar.
Freely become the Sun's bride, the latter grows quick with seed, grass crouched, and
This looks interesting. It says, okay, a legend, a lesson in vengeance. It says, in the dour ages
of draughty cells and draughtier castles of dragons breathing without the frame of fables,
faint and king, unfisted obstructions knuckles by no miracle or majestic means,
but by such abuses as smack of spite and the over scrupulous.
Twisting of the thumbscrew, one soul tied in sinews, one white horse drowned, and all the unconquered pinnacles of God's city and Babylon's.
Must wait, while here Suso's hand hones his taxon needles, scouring to source his own red sluices, for the relish of heaven relentless dousing with prickles.
horsehair and lice, his horny loins. While there, I rate Cyrus, swanders a summer and
a brawn of his heroes to rebuke the horse-swallowing river Gindies. He
split it in three hundred and sixty trickles a girl could wade without getting
without wetting her shins. Still, latter-day sages smiling at this behavior,
Neatly, nicely, by disbelief or bridges, never gripped as their grand sire's did that devil who chuckles
from grain of the morrow to the riverbed grains.
I mean, it's very...
It's beautiful, but I'm just gonna tell you what it is.
I just sit with this.
One more, one more.
This is called, On the Declines of Oracles.
It says, and then I have a quote at the top.
It says, Inside a ruined temple, the broken statue of a god
spoke a mysterious language by Giorgio de Chirico.
And then here's Sylvia Plath, On the Decline of Oracles.
My father kept a speckled conch by two bronze bookends
of ships and sail.
And as I listened, it's cold teeth see with voices
of that ambiguous sea.
Old Boklin missed, who held the shell.
To hear the sea, he could not hear.
What the seashell spoke to his inner ear,
he knew, but no peasants knew.
My father died, and when he died,
he wheeled his books and shelled away.
The books burned up, he took the shell,
but I, keep the voices he said in my ear
and said in my eye, the sight of those blue,
unseen waves for which the ghost of Boklin grieves.
The peasants speak to multiply.
never need to see what I see. In the temple of broken stones above a worn curtain rears the
white head of a god or madman. Nobody knows which or dares ask. From him I have tomorrow's gossip
and doldrums. So much it's vision good for like a persistent stitch. In its side it nags its
in the third-floor window, booth of the Alexandra House, over petty curry I regard,
with some fatigue, smoky rooms of the restaurant opposite,
see and pose itself on the cook at the steaming stove.
A picture of what's going to happen.
I have to wait it out. It will come. It comes.
Three barely-known men are coming up a stair. This veils both stove and crook. One is pale with
orange hair, behind glasses, the second's eyes are blurred, the third walks leaning on its
thick and smiling. These trivial images invade the coastal eye like pages from a gross comic
strip. And toward the happening of this happening, the earth turns now. In half an hour, I shall go
Coming up, those three, worth less than present, past this future. Worthless, such a vision to eyes gondol, that which she's guide, Troy's towers fall, thought evil, break out of the north.
Hey!
It was filthy?
Okay, this one's called, sorry for this one, this one's called Nick and the Candlestick, okay?
He says, I am a miner, the light turns blue, waxy stalactites, drip and thicken tears.
This, the earthen womb exudes from its dead boredom, black bat airs,
Old echo, even the newts are white, those holy Joes and the fish, the fish, Christ, their
pains of ice, a vine of knives, a piranha, religion, drinking, its first communion out
of my live toes, the candle, gulips and recovers, its small attitude, its yellow heart, its
your cross position, the blood bosoms clean.
In this, in you, Ruby, the pain, you wake up as not yours.
Love, love, I have hung our cave with roses,
with soft rugs, the last of Victoriana,
let these stars plummet to their dark abode, the dress.
Let the mercuric atoms that crippled drip
into the terrible well.
You are the one, solid the space is laid on, envious.
You are the baby in the barn.
Oh
Okay, well
One more? Okay, one more.
It's very short. It says, metamorphosis. It says,
haunch like a fawn, he he hoot, from grove of moon glint to fennfrost, until all owls in the
on the call this man made. No sound but a drunken coot, lurching home along Riverbank.
Stars hung, waters sunk, so a rank of double star-eyes lit, bows where those owls sat.
In arena of yellow eyes watched the changing shape he cut.
Saw hoof hardened from foot, saw sprout goat horns,
That's good intense
That's it that has it. I mean what's up is like a beat is talking about me today or you don't have to answer
I'll have to just wondering
Like I don't know why she's mad at me
Think I just plan to be mad at her for what she did. Yeah, you love it. Do you love it? Thank you
Yeah, I hope you had a nice weekend Sunday
Yeah
But Samantha did you see what she said to me like she was saying horrible mean things to me like I
She was laughing at me
Because he destroyed my she wrote she was so much like I would have to sell a month
She wrote you're a pussy and as a mod
What if I went to a chat my first time and I see first of the mods are calling them pussy
Did you know that in public in front of everybody? And then she called on or she like came on the show and like I was like hi
And then she's like
Ah, she's like these are bringing up all you know so much of
Hey, Mikey, how are you? We can was you know today was a good day. Yeah, I know
And Jamie Jamie, there's you know somebody at like somebody else you say like it kind of the same thing happens to you
But she's the thing is like she's mad at me. I
I'm not even I wasn't even mattered. I mean sometimes when she's mad and we would argue sometimes, you know
we'd always make up and stuff
but
Couple days later, but you know, I
Felt like less and less like affection and then I was like that was done. Yeah
I know, and then, yeah, no, Jamie, like somebody else said it, that, it's like, a, like, a really good, that I know is a good friend to her, like, there's just a nice person that's nothing wrong.
She was, she told that person, she's like, well, you know what, she's like, I don't, she said she don't want to be friends or something to her, and like, just like, blew her off, and like.
Everyone's confused and then DJ Electra, which he came on last night. She was like yelling at DJ Electra on my panel and
And say I did electric called her bitch and then she was calling DJ Electra bitch in a pussy come to my show and
Yeah, I don't know takes you to bingo. Well, I know but gosh
Yeah
But it's like so I'll just say what I would like sometimes she would call me and then she would like
Yeah, you kind of yell at me for a couple minutes on the phone
And I'd be like be that beat a bit and she's like then she would keep talking and then finally when she stopped
I would start talking and then she'd hang up. I wouldn't even be able to say anything
Yeah, I think so yeah, and it's like as above so below
It's you're right
Where are you accent the cold
I'm saying right here, it's like I only have curtains open and it's warm
You don't engage in all the petty stuff
Which is good. Well, I should I probably engage more than I should because you know, I will talk to anybody that I
Was even trying to talk to you know, I'm not in clumsy clairvoyance
like they just they basically just
Just I don't remember what I did I remember what I did
Oh, actually, I remember what you know Emma kind of embarrassed me in front of for discord
I left the discord and then she like and then yeah, look, you know Emma, but you don't get any things with a
Pediatrics well
Cuz I I really I don't have like many I don't have like friends like really around here
You know, I don't know anybody and
Actually when I first started doing panels and stuff like you know, she was so supportive and like that's why you know
I gotta catch you
I said that to you like for her and stuff like that
Because we're so good and I loved her I still love her, but it's like it's just and we were good for so long
And then it's like this court is for the birds. Yeah, I I have a disco, but I'm not on anymore
I mean 99 on Thursday. Yeah, it's very warm here
Yeah, I live by the beach chill. I can't wait to go this summer do some IRL there
Yeah, but anyway, of course
And I would never say, if I did, yes,
there's stuff, you and I would go back and forth,
we'd have disagreements, you know?
Few months ago, remember when Janet was on the show,
Jamie, and it was just like,
one of that crazy time, it was like for a couple of weeks.
Yeah, I got you, I got you Charisma, got you.
But,
I mean, I think the only the only real fake friends are somebody that would be friends you with an agenda
That would be the only kind of thing that could serve and even those
Can become your friends, right?
Because it's like there's plenty of stories like oh
You know, well the VBC have to do with like, you know some kind of a sass and there's something like okay
You're gonna kill this or unalive this person and they go and they fall in love and they don't want to kill
I think the snow white and the huntsman, right?
Yeah, the Queen sends the Huntsman out to bring back Snow White's heart and the Huntsman can't either doesn't have the heart to heart to killer
So he kills up him for something or maybe I won't bring the heart of that instead
fools the Queen
Broken heart a heading to a heading in healing. Thank you psyche first sticking out for me, of course
But no it's like
She doesn't listen to the word I say or I
Don't understand
But why she's I
Didn't understand why she was why she would do that to you
But I think it's other people getting involved, right?
I'm a doing DIY for your e-biker installing LED lighting without everyone helping you. Oh good. Okay. That's awesome
I should get some they're the beach often
Um, yeah, well I would go to the pier about every week because they have like, you know, fish taco
Well, they have fish taco Friday, but they have like on Monday through Thursday. They have a happy hour
You can get like three fish tacos for six dollars and other stuff
There's other little restaurants. I want to try around here. There's a lot of good restaurants, but it's expensive
So I like a deal. I like a good deal that the fish market here is like the largest fish market in California
I think those and you can buy anything there and they'll cook it
There had fish tacos are really good. Do you ever make?
You know, I always
There's open invitation for anybody that ever wants to do like hang out at the pier
I'll take anybody from fish tacos. They want to pay out and do IRL to pure one day
Yeah, I got a new e-bike. Oh, it's not new X. It's used, but it's a really good condition and
I don't know if that's stupid. The ones who claim their friend and supporters are the most always finding fake and backstabbing you, is it struggles to be
non-partisan.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I'd say a lot of people would be like
Like they would think they was just
They just keep pushing everything. It's like they
like
Like Arthur, I think I think Arthur don't I got he did donate right when I started right into the den
Like monthly he can month later. He's still like I'm a donor
pre-mod me and let me on camera and then he would be like really rude he'd say
like bad things to me and I'd be like you can't be a mod and like be on my show
saying bad things about me I don't care you can say bad things about me
anywhere else it's not on my show it's like the one one place where you know
People can at least be respectful
Well
See I like I I had I had like I had like this I had a guy friend who was blade
He was from Texas and
He was in my discord and we were and we were both on this guy Benny's chat
But then I noticed he was like kind of in love with Benny then I bumped with Lisa chat
Then he was like saying in love with Lisa is on my discord. He would
Every guy that came into this discord
He would tell it with the tell to leave and he tell some certain girls he tells he told to leave to he say
Oh, that there's too much drama here and whether it was even drama then he just want to
With around other people with that around other people that he knew so they could hear a nose or something
Eventually he he he he revenged porn on my discord someone that sent him photos. He posted them on discord and deleted them
Cause so much problems and then
Yeah, I don't know a lot of people attack me. That's the Mike you say
Well, it just happens that I'm a guy. Oh, you are Mikey. Hey, Mike. So it's not he's not Mickey or Mikey. Hey, Mikey
Now I know
Now yeah, I only have two good email friends that I've known for over 20 years. Yeah
Yeah, well, I've always been out of the closet since I was like
I was the only person at my school for the entire time I was there for seven years. I was ever I was ever out of the closet, right?
Did you shit in born a gay man? Well, I
Think I like my I don't know how to describe so I am like, you know
People say people say oh you don't think you didn't I don't think you're gay you're you know
But I always thought I was kind of like up like you know a little bit flamboyant
But some people don't because I kind of look masculine, but if I like talk for a little bit you probably figure out
But I've never talked bad. You never talked bad in chat or pants yet. Then you have
respect and that's
That's your nature of course
Yeah, like
So he has tattoo eyebrows so my mom does too
Well, you should meet this guy named bean gang there's a guy named clumsy bean gang he was in here earlier. He uh, he's like a spanish guy
I like one day what time you just he shaved off his eyebrows actually so I'm offered me to shave off my eyebrows
I'm like no. I don't want to look like that weird
For months
Your woman's dog oh
My god, I oh, yeah, see this one's right here. He's like his is eyebrow shaved. You can't see me that picture, but he's a nice guy
Hi, hi
Hi kisses
You're the queen of McDonald's
Don't be one
Bunkies Bunky
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Then please let me know and I'll look at their comments, and I'll probably I'll probably hide them
What are you talking about?
Thank you, charisma. The thing is, the right thing is gonna work a lot better.
It was, um, I was getting fatigued from, from the, because it's like, since
basically probably the beginning of this year, I've been getting, I get emails all the time about
wrenches, wrenches, wrenches, not like, usually not asking for them, but oh, this person said this,
this person's doing this, this person's doing this, and then I'm being, so it's like, it is working
like most of the conflicts right away.
And that in turn makes it easier to communicate.
Yeah.
What we really think the big thing was
I didn't want people, like there are people like, they try to fight with the mods and stuff like that, and I, and I don't want people, because people, people have said, I'll take my ranch, because either because, you know, they, they, they didn't like something that happened in the chat in the, in the panel, or they didn't like the stress of like, um, being yelled at if they tied someone up for 10 seconds and.
Yeah, that was like kind of like the one of the things with beta like I would like you would say hey take that person
They removed them because the person would be sick
But it would be when the person make would probably be saying stuff about her and so I always do it
But then the other day we had
LD was on the panel and she came in and then she said she was like he didn't say anything. He was just sitting there
Then she's like, oh take a doc take LCF the piano right now and I was like well
He didn't do anything and it's like and there's no
There's a reason see I would but and then she's like I demand take him down right now
I'm gonna count down from 10 and she counted up from 10. I didn't do it because
There's no reason to he was like he was fine, so but you know
So if you have a really mad this secret, uh, I
Fall hold on sunshine. I fall my f a gg o two rules and get persecuted. There's two other
Low-life acquittal. Well sunshine you realize everyone's unmodded except for me
So if anything happens if anything happens in the future, it was it was me that did it, okay?
You can get mad at me. They're not don't you can call my rules f a gg o two rules, but
I don't don't call people low lives and like you know, I try to treat people equally, but I can't always be in the
Mod the mod version of the chat because I'm paying attention to my screen panel
So that's why I'll try to slow down letting people in the panel so I can like kind of
Pay more attention in the beginning of the show, but
I'm trying my best
the rules
They're just like basic rules. I just made those rules because those were constantly being broken and I kind of like
I'm trying to go with the TOS
but
Dunshan you're a little bit you had to block. Oh, yeah
Dunshan you're making new accounts
The case yeah, it gives a countdown who to put back now. Let's see if I can like oh yeah, and I
Never told the woods, you know, I would never
It's not I cannot imagine telling any other streamer to do something. I've never
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I, I, I, I, I like, I like, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
You got two moon cards in my reading last night. Yes, so we're outside to look at the sky and so this huge falling star
beautiful
Important having people to mix
To mix things up everyone was like, okay, so yeah, I like people to mix things up but also
I'm not like you know, I'm not very extroverted. So if there's like a lot of people on panel unless I'm kind of drunk
I tend to be kind of quiet
I'm tricks
Jamie has became Jamie's giving you a hug
Hey, I
Hugging tricks hi babe
Play down
Hi, babe
It's brown if you're in here for so purring
Yeah, hey babe
He first low of her is real loud and
Sort of the Lord is the Lord likes to kiss me on the lips
You like your background
Cheers guys
Hey
Fixes funny he likes to he um
Malola would like last year when I take a bath
She was just up in the back or she would like jump up and like look at and then she would like
Let me pick her up and put her in the bath for a second. I just dip her in and she's like jump out and like
And they shake off now tricks like to do that to you like that to you but or tricks will just buy on me in the shower
He like if I leave the door open I like look at the shower. He's like always like peeking at me
You look at me in a shower tricks. Oh
Yeah
Uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh
I might have to like pivot with like the drama panels just because
You know it attracts too much of
Like the people that just want to fight, right? Well, if people just want drama
A lot of them are just like these loud people just like yeah, yeah
It's kind of very
Like
Like I have I like that. I like that fun
We I've had so many fun panels or so many cool panels and then sometimes a cool panel and then
your form bomb will come in and we'll have a cool panel for a long time or
Since someone comes on fighting. I mean there's
That they're it's been an interesting experience learning learning it I've been poor bummed over a hundred times
and
And we're bombed and
That's a very very very very straight and very drunk people in my show
It was it's a I don't think I did a bad job for my first six months. I just want to do
It's gonna keep keep going keep growing I don't know
So it took me a long time to even get the courage to do YouTube because I didn't want to be on camera
I was like I wanted I think I'm just gonna do terror readings off camera
I would tell stories to see on the beach and like put in the camera with the water
Then I guess they got pretty drunk one night and I think all this girls do it. I started doing my live streams
That would just sit at the table. I would do tarot every from both
I kind of do what I do now, but then I figured out I could sit on the couch and do it
I've upgraded all my equipment since then I've been monetized since then I uh
I've been through like three co-hosts maybe two or three yeah we
but we it's an interesting times I've also had very popular streamers here like on
there's still some I would like to have but I've had very popular streamers on coming to the show
I still haven't seen them done
But you know there's a lot of people that have like you know had lost monetization and everything it's because I
Don't I'm so lucky. I have it
It's just like it's like basically a miracle
And so I'm like what
So I was like, okay, well, if I can't just cancel
within six months, I'm not gonna put too much,
I won't get too attached, but, you know,
that's been over six months, I've gotten attached.
Yeah.
My back is killing me.
Hey, do you want some, look at this,
do you have catnip I have, do you want some catnip tricks?
Here.
That's what catnip Rudy, Rudy's using.
Come here, Rudy.
Rudy's using catnip.
Rudy likes it, look.
You having some catnip?
Really?
He loves it, you see him?
Yep.
He has to love catnip.
Uh, Rudy uses it for his, I think he, you know, he Rudy's like, you know, he's like a senior citizen cat. He uses it for his glaucoma, right?
The senior citizen is weird for glaucoma or something. Oh, you love that, huh?
Oh, and then it tricks tricks here. It's a dog barking. You hear the dog barking?
If it doesn't listen to the dog barking, uh-oh.
I'm gonna try to find something interesting. I'll be right back on.
Yes, baby.
No, I'm gay.
You're into blondes, CB, let's see, yes.
It's just okay
So this is a good book it's a really big book it's called the Illuminatus trilogy
Robert Anton Wilson got these dolphins and the pyramids so okay
But I like to open to a random page and read it.
It's just full of information, but it's a form of book.
So I'll read you some.
It says, let's see if there's anything that stands out to you.
It says, I just opened to a random page.
They were in Huggard's funky state room.
George, after experience at the demolished Drake Mansion, found the octopi and other sea monsters on the wall murals distinctly unappetizing.
Haggard, as usual, was wearing a turtleneck and casual slacks. This time, the turtleneck was lavender, an old faggody item for him.
I
Meant a mental and sexuality
I've tried it of course he has something
But added something about
Likey women better goodness. That's the only two mornings ago
George wondered what it would have been like to try it and
He said he would even
Have the eight of the nerve
What particular lies he has cautiously? Are you about to confess?
Haikard lit a pipe and passed it over.
Alamot black bath, he said, croakingly holding the smoke down.
Hazan Ishabah's own private forest formula does wooden, does wonders when a heavy metaphysics
is coming at you. George inhaled.
and felt an immediate hit like cocaine
or some other four brain simulants.
Christ, what's this shit cut with?
He gasped at somebody somewhere,
second, seems to turn colored lights on
in the gold and nautical green room
and on the outside lavender sweater.
Oh, Hagrid took care of casually a hint of a Belladonna and
Stimulium
That was old
House in secret, you know all that crap in most books about how he had turned his followers on with hash
How they never had to be forced. They thought it was magic
Is unhistorical
Hustad was known
In the midis since the Neolithic age, archaeologists have dug up tombs.
Seems our ancestors buried their priests with a load of bush to help them negotiate with their gods when they got to the Big Rock,
Candy Mountain, or whatever they thought they were going.
cousins who produce a new synergistic effect.
What's synergistic, George, as slowly feeling seasick
for the first time since aboard the Lape Erickson?
Non-addictive.
non-attitive. You put two and two together and you get five instead of four. Buckminster Fuller uses
the synergistic gimmicks all the time in his geodesistic domes. That's why they're stronger
than they look. Haggard took another look, poked and passed the pipe again. What the hell George
thought? Sometimes increasing the dose got you past the nausea. He looked deeply. Hadn't they
So so interesting book. It's kind of hard to see my eyes are all blurry
Do you drink it you're drinking a coffee. Oh my god
You're you're so sick dancing. I hope you're feeling better
Keep tricks come on
Okay, well, it's been eight hours. The room is empty now
Thank you guys for being here. Thank you for being my friend. Thank you
for
The bias your support said a lot of kind things. I had one of the best tests today. I haven't a long time because
You know
Everyone was cordial everyone was yeah, everyone was cool
Yeah, I just I don't want to buy I don't want to bore you. It's like fuck
Love you guys
Thank you guys appreciate you